<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-NI-29-42 NI-296000-429000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>NI-296000-429000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>414905</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-07-04T12:32:23.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-04T12:32:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>NI-296000-429000</dblock_id>
<original_item>20</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21William Pinkerton Memorial Primary School</title>
<content>

In the William Pinkerton Memorial we have a Playground Leader scheme.  The children in P6 and P7 are all playground leaders.  We have various duties to perform at break and lunchtime.  It is our job to help the younger children and make sure the children on the playground are playing fairly.  If anyone gets hurt we take them to the staffroom for first aid.  At lunch time we set out the games for that day and supervise the use of them.  When the bell rings we have to make sure they are put away properly and that no games are missing.  If the younger children don’t know how to play with the games we show them.&lt;br />&lt;br />On wet days the playground leaders split up and go into separate classrooms to look after others.&lt;br />&lt;br />We work in groups of three.  Each group has a certain day when they are on duty.  Playground Leaders wear special caps so as they can be easily identified.&lt;br />&lt;br />On Tuesdays, Wednesdays and Thursdays we have breakfast c lub at school. It commences at 8.00am and finishes at 8.45am.  When we arrive the first thing we do is have breakfast.  We have a choice of cereal and fruit juice as well as tea and toast.  At the end of each term we get a special breakfast of scrambled eggs, sausages and bacon.  James and Dorothy prepare the breakfast for us.  After we have eaten if it’s dry Judith and Louisa take us outside to play football or dodge ball. Sometimes we play in the school park.  However if it’s wet games are organised for us in the assembly hall.  We also watch DVDs or CBBC.  Some people like to play with Lego.  At 8.40am we tidy up and get ready for another day at school.   &lt;br />
Tristan, Demi,  Kenny and Timothy</content>
</page></content></entry>