<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-NI-29-42 NI-296000-429000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-29-42/NI-296000-429000-23.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>NI-296000-429000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>414907</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-07-04T12:32:23.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-04T12:32:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>NI-296000-429000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23A Day in the Life of Natalya</title>
<content>

My name is Natalya. I live in Dervock and I am 11 years old.&lt;br />&lt;br />When I get up in the morning I get dressed into my school jumper and yellow polo-shirt.  For breakfast I have Rice Krispies, tea and toast.  Before I go to school I watch a little TV.  Then I walk to school by my self or sometimes I go on my bike.&lt;br />&lt;br />When I reach school my friends and I talk for a couple of minutes before the bell rings at 9:00am.  Our day usually begins with Maths but on Tuesdays and Thursdays we go to assembly first. At breaktime we go to the tuck shop where we have a choice of toast, pancakes, scones, apple or orange juice and milkshake.  When we get our break we go outside and play for 15 minuets.  At 10:45am we go back to class for Literacy time. &lt;br />&lt;br />I have a school dinner at lunchtime.  Our dinners are extremely nice!  After dinner we go outside and play with the playground games that the PTA bought for us.  My favourite game is Tug of War because lots of the pupils come and play it and when we all fall down it is really funny.  &lt;br />&lt;br />In the afternoon we do different things like Art, P.E. and Technology.   Then at 3 o’clock we go home. &lt;br />&lt;br />Whenever I get home I do my homework and watch the TV.  For homework we do tables, spellings, reading and written work.  Then I watch my favourite programme called Merlin.  Sometimes I go outside to play with my friends Brandon and Tristan.  We have a hide out which we go to nearly every day.&lt;br />&lt;br />On a Tuesday and Thursday I go to Judo and it is really good fun.   It starts at 7:30pm and finishes at 8:30. I am a red belt &lt;br />&lt;br />Before I go to bed I get toast and tea.  &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Natalya</content>
</page></content></entry>