<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-20.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-NI-33-39 NI-336000-396000-20</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-20.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-20.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>NI-336000-396000-20</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420543</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-09T15:27:29.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-09T15:27:29.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>NI-336000-396000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>20A day in the life of a P6 child at Toreagh Primary School</title>
<content>

On a Wednesday, I would wake up at roughly 6:40am or 7:00am. Usually I would dander into the kitchen, still half asleep. First of all I would feed my dog, Maisey, her breakfast which she wolfs down in no time. Now it's about 7:25am and it's time to make my breakfast. I have Coco Shreddies which are shredded wheat squares coated in chocolate. Once I've finished, I get dressed while listening to music on my iPod. Usually I have some spare time until I go to school so I watch one of the many channels on my flatscreen T.V. in my living room.&lt;br />&lt;br />Today it was sunny and warm so I walked to school because I don't live that far away from it. When I arrive at school, I sit down and copy down my homework for the day off the interactive whiteboard. In the morning, when everyone has settled down, we do our daily spellings and tables. We do Numeracy until break time. For break we eat healthily so I have an orange. Oranges are my favourite fruit. After break we do Literacy and sometimes we do a set of mental maths which I quite enjoy. Now it's lunch so we all get out our lunchboxes. I normally have ham and cheese sandwiches and a biscuit. Before I started, I changed my library book. We no longer have school dinners so everybody takes a packed lunch. When everybody goes outside we all play British Bulldogs except our version is different. We all run up and down the playground and if you get caught, you help the other person to catch people and at the end the person who hasn't been caught wins. The bell rings and everyone lines up and we wait until Miss Morrow, the Principal and P6/7 teacher, comes back from her lunch. We work and when we are finished we are allowed on the laptops.&lt;br />&lt;br />At the end of school, I walk back home with my dad and my dog. When I get home, I change out of my school uniform and into my normal clothes (usually skinny jeans.) I go outside with Maisey and throw a tennis ball for her. Then, if it's too warm to stay inside, I play on my dad's laptop outside. When evening comes I stay up for a while and then I put on my Sponge-Bob (a cartoon character) pyjamas and I go to bed at about 9:00pm or 9:20pm. I read a book until I fall asleep.&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Lyn Morrow</content>
</page></content></entry>