<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-18.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-NI-33-39 NI-336000-396000-18</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-18.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-NI-33-39/NI-336000-396000-18.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>NI-336000-396000-18</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420539</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-09T15:27:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-09T15:27:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>NI-336000-396000</dblock_id>
<original_item>6</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>181986 to 2011</title>
<content>

From 1986 to 2011 the way of reading books has really changed!&lt;br />&lt;br />Inventors have invented new ways of presenting books, it is called a kindle. A kindle is a computerized book. It can store over one thousands books. You download the books from the internet at a cost. You have to buy the books of the "bookstore", an online shop. It has to be a book that has already been written. You can get all different colours of kindle - white and black.&lt;br />&lt;br />Over the years the computers we use in school have really changed.  In 1986 the school only had a couple of BBC computers. Nowadays we have PCs and laptops in every room.&lt;br />&lt;br />The laptop is an electrical portable device that is used for storing information (just like the old computers).  It is useful for carrying around with you and you can set it on your lap. That is why you call it a laptop! &lt;br />&lt;br />Most families have a laptop or computer at home.  Sometimes it is used for homework, playing games, spreadsheets, databases and even watching DVDs. As you can see, every member of the family, young or old can use the laptop for different things. &lt;br />&lt;br />We like using the laptop for:&lt;br />&lt;br />watching TV programmes we have missed&lt;br />&lt;br />	playing games like Mine Sweeper and Pinball&lt;br />&lt;br />	getting information&lt;br />&lt;br />	sending emails to our friends&lt;br />&lt;br />These are just a few of the ways! :-)&lt;br />&lt;br />The iPhone is the thinnest phone at this point in time. It can be used as a normal phone.  To work it, you simply touch the screen. It has apps, which are applications for different items eg, games, radio stations or supermarkets. On the iPhone you can text: texting is a way to communicate with others who may have a mobile phone instead of ringing them. The iPhone is a very useful object and is very popular if you can afford it. The iPhone can connect you to the internet, YouTube and facebook. It also has a camera and has a built in iPod. The iPhone 3G 8GB is worth £428 and the iPhone 4 16GB is worth £510.&lt;br />&lt;br />How expensive is that!!!!&lt;br />&lt;br />1986&lt;br />&lt;br />There were no DVD players, only video players. They were big and chunky and only played video cassettes. It was used for watching videos and producing entertainment. It was an electrical wired device.&lt;br />&lt;br />Nowadays we have Blu ray player- they play DVDs and Blu ray discs in high definition. They are very high tech but are very easy to use and also like the Video player it produces entertainment. One wire to plug in to the wall and one wire to plug into the television.   &lt;br />&lt;br />An iPOd is a device that you can listen to music on. In 1986 they used tapes instead of iPods. It's easy to download music and apps from iTunes.&lt;br />&lt;br />iPods have apps which is short for applications. Apps are games, shopping catalogues, information sites and much more. Tapes were put into tape recorders but now we have hand held iPods.&lt;br />&lt;br />A HD plasma television is a screen you can watch. There are a lot of programs on it to watch. HD stands for High Definition which means better quality picture. Many people now have flat screens. Most plasma televisions can be put up on the wall.&lt;br />&lt;br />In the 1980's the televisions were bulky and small. You could only get four channels and it was in black and white now they have all changed.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
P7 Class, Toreag Primary School, 2011</content>
</page></content></entry>