<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-33.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448007</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:04.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33BUCHLYVIE UNITED FOOTBALL CLUB - updated 2011</title>
<content>

The present day club was formed as a result of a meeting called in September 1946, when the following office bearers and committee members were appointed:&lt;br />&lt;br />Chairman - John Cameron, Secretary - Robert C Stewart, Treasurer - James Higgins, Committee Members - Roderick Morrison, George Brisbane, William Leslie, William MacLachlan, Alex Buchanan&lt;br />&lt;br />The club's minute book from that time reads "It was proposed that the newly formed club be called Buchlyvie United Football Club and it was unanimously decided to run the club independently from any other body." &lt;br />&lt;br />The club's first competitive match was played on 25th April 1947 when we drew five each with Drymen, in the opening league match of that season. &lt;br />&lt;br />The village has had a football team in various guises for over 100 years, indeed Buchlyvie was one of the founder members of the local Forth &amp; Endrick league in 1910.&lt;br />&lt;br />The existing club has had some successes over the years, although not as often as the players or supporters would have liked. Most notable successes included the existing club's only Cameron Cup success in 1957 and the only time any Buchlyvie team has ever won the league title in 1982. The McGregor Ferguson Cup has been won 5 times, with the Telfer Cup having been won once in 1984. The club has also won the Garvie Trophy on numerous occasions - which is presented to the local team with the best discipline record.&lt;br />&lt;br />At the time of writing (August 2011), the club continues to exist with the encouraging signs of youngsters wanting to play and emulate their fathers and, in some cases, grandfathers!&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Evan McLean</content>
</page></content></entry>