<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-29.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-29</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-29.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-29.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-29</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447999</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:03.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:22.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>29VILLAGE SHOPS IN BUCHLYVIE - updated 2011</title>
<content>

Some of the shops described in the 1986 survey survive, namely the village store, now a Costcutters, and the butchers. Among the casualties have been the Co-op and the Central Farmers. Others have appeared and gone in the intervening years. Rockhill on Main Street became for several years the site of a second general store and the home of the Post Office. For a short number of years the village boasted an Antique shop. Some of the shops developed into outlets for other goods or services. The premises that housed the Co-op became a pottery shop and now incorporates a coffee shop. The general store based at Rockhill was converted into a village tea room on the ground floor and artist's studio while the upper floor was used for producing prints of the paintings generated. After a change in ownership the print manufacturer and tea room operators moved out and the property was placed on the market and awaits a buyer. &lt;br />&lt;br />The closure of the Central Farmers' store was the result of the building being unable to cope with the increased demands for goods and materials. This property is also on the market, as a housing plot. The business was moved to other premises nearer to Stirling. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Arthur Benns</content>
</page></content></entry>