<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-34.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-34</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-34.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-34.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-34</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448009</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:04.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>34BUCHLYVIE COMMUNITY COUNCIL - updated 2011</title>
<content>

In 1986, Buchlyvie was administered by Central Region. In 1996, this region was divided into three separate districts, Stirling, Falkirk and Clackmannan, with Buchlyvie in the Stirling Council area. The Buchlyvie Community Council meets regularly to discuss issues affecting the village, most of which come from Stirling Council (such as planning applications). The amount of traffic passing through the village has greatly increased and the Community Council is active in promoting speed restrictions and traffic calming methods. Responsibility for the appearance of the village and the maintenance of its flower tubs, etc. is gradually passing from the Community Council itself to other organisations within the village, such as the Village Hall Management Committee, the Community Association and the Local Paths Group. The latter was established to maintain the Core Paths set up by Stirling Council through the Land Reform (Scotland) Act 2003. These paths will eventually be signposted and waymarked, with gates replacing the previous barbed wire fences and stiles. The most important of these Core Paths are the disused railway lines to Aberfoyle and to Arnprior. This Aberfoyle route is now regularly used by walkers, cyclists and runners and has recently been designated a link to the National Cycle Network Route 7 (Lands End to John O'Groats).&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Bob Sparkes</content>
</page></content></entry>