<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-27-58/GB-276000-588000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-27-58 GB-276000-588000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-27-58/GB-276000-588000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-27-58/GB-276000-588000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-276000-588000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412247</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-09T18:48:46.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T18:48:46.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-276000-588000</dblock_id>
<original_item>19</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21May 2011</title>
<content>

Exactly 26 years after leaving school.........&lt;br />&lt;br />While I don't quite remember winning "various competitions" I do know that I did indeed enjoy cooking (and still do) but this was not the way that my career was to go.&lt;br />&lt;br />Soon after the article must have been written I started working at Maxwelton House assisting Willie Addison with the gardens and grounds.  This was a short term placement for 8 weeks only; which incidentally was exceptionally wet for all but three days.......I'm sure that put me off wanting to work outdoors for the rest of my days though I did manage to work with Davie Houston for a few months in the forest at Dalmacallan.&lt;br />&lt;br />Ultimately a move was needed to secure full time regular work (University was not for me) and so I left the village for Edinburgh.  After a relatively short period of time I was employed within the Lighting Industry where I remain today as the Managing Director of our company.  Inter estingly the man that gave me my first job in lighting all those years ago became an employee of mine some 23 years later.  Strange how things go full circle!&lt;br />&lt;br />I still return to Moniaive with my son as often as I can, though probably not as often as I should, mostly to visit my mother who still lives there but also because I still think of it as being home.&lt;br />&lt;br />I feel that the village has changed greatly from when I was 16 and probably for the better but without seeing it on a day to day basis this may not be the case. &lt;br />&lt;br />Reading about the Primary School I had to smile at the comment about Mrs Robson - an "incomer" to the village and school (sorry Moira) but there is a lot more of those "incomers" there today.  Even with my absence of nearly 30 years I will always be able to say that I am a local, and who knows maybe one day I shall return to live within what was always was a fantastic place to be.&lt;br />&lt;br />Jim Steedman&lt;br />Edinburgh&lt;br />&lt;br />May 2011&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>