<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-35.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448013</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:05.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35BUCHLYVIE VILLAGE HALL - updated 2011</title>
<content>

As it was in 1986, the Village Hall continues to be an integral part of the community and the hub of many village activities. The Hall is in use on five days out of seven,  hosting , on a weekly basis, the Mother and Toddlers' group, OPALs  (Older People, Active Lifestyles) exercise group, Zumba class, Army Cadets, Pilates class and, from September to December, Pantomime Rehearsals.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Buchlyvie WRI continues to meet on the second Tuesday of every month from September to May, and it is also in use for the Gardening club on a monthly basis. Summer Ice (played indoors with rules similar to curling) is still a popular pastime, meeting in the winter months. Committee meetings and AGMs for village organisations are held in the Hall as are Community Council Meetings and surgeries by local MPs, MSPs and councillors.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Hall is a popular (and cheap) venue for Anniversary and Birthday parties and also for Wedding Receptions. Twice a year it becomes the Race Headquarters for the Buchlyvie Half Marathon and the Buchlyvie 10K.&lt;br />&lt;br />In the course of a year there will be Jumble Sales, Coffee Mornings, Race Nights, Family Bingo Sessions, Halloween Parties, concerts, discos and ceilidhs and for one week in December the rafters resound to the sound of cheers and laughter, hisses and boos as the Buchlyvie Pantomime Group produces its annual show.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Hall Car park has recently been dramatically improved by the building of two drystone walled gardens with a stone statue ‘Clive of Buchlyvie’ overseeing the area. These walls were built by Buchlyvie resident and master craftsman Irwin Campbell and his friends from the Dry Stone Walling Association.&lt;br />&lt;br />A new wooden fence at the rear of the car park keeps children using the adjacent play area safe from cars using the car park.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Hall continues to be managed by the Hall Management Committee, a group of residents who represent the interests of many of the organisations using the Hall. This group works hard throughout the year to raise funds for the upkeep of the hall.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Anne Stewart</content>
</page></content></entry>