<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-22.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447431</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-26T14:41:26.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-26T14:41:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22HEALTH CARE IN BUCHLYVIE</title>
<content>

Around 80% of Buchlyvie residents attend one surgery centrally located on Station Road adjoining the Village School. This Medical Centre was built in 2006 by Stirling District Council as a Community Build, one of the first in Scotland.&lt;br />&lt;br />It is served by a team of four doctors, two practice nurses, two receptionist/dispensers, a health care assistant, midwife, district nurse, physiotherapist and podiatrist.&lt;br />&lt;br />Other services available are Minor Surgery, Well-Woman Clinic, Well-Man Clinic, Diabetic Clinic, Travel Advice, Asthma Clinic, COPD (lung clinic), Healthy Heart Group and, once a year, a 'Flu Clinic.&lt;br />&lt;br />The remainder of the residents attend practices in neighbouring villages.&lt;br />&lt;br />For hospital services, patients must travel 15 or more miles. In 2011 Stirling Royal Infirmary closed for In-Patient care. It is now called Stirling Community Hospital and has various Out-Patient clinics and a Minor Injuries Unit, X-Ray Department and Out of Hours Service.&lt;br />&lt;br />The new Forth Valley Royal Hospital at Larbert was opened by Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth in July 2011 for all In-Patient care and some Out-Patient Clinics.&lt;br />&lt;br />Homecare for the elderly is organised by the village general practitioners in cooperation with Stirling District Council Social Work Department which supplies carers.&lt;br />&lt;br />Pre-school children have all vaccinations and examinations done by the health visitor.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Medical Centre also has a ‘Friends of Practice’ and a ‘Patient Participation Group’ which raise money to buy equipment for the Medical Centre and also arrange talks on various topics to do with health.&lt;br />&lt;br />A wildlife garden established around the Medical Centre and the School is used as a joint resource.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Betty McLaren</content>
</page></content></entry>