<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-25-69 GB-256000-693000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-25-69/GB-256000-693000-24.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-256000-693000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447991</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:00.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:22.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-256000-693000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24BUCHLYVIE PRIMARY SCHOOL  - updated 2011</title>
<content>

Buchlyvie Primary School is the only Primary School in the village of Buchlyvie. The school meets the educational needs of the 5 - 12 year olds in the village and surrounding farms. After an excellent report from Her Majesty's Inspectors of Education (HMIE) the school now also attracts children from outwith its catchment area. The school was refurbished in 2006 and is now part of a small campus which includes a medical centre. There are 3 full time teaching members of staff, 2 part time teachers and 3 part time support for learning staff members. The 3 classes have a total of 70 children. There are also fortnightly visits from a music and a P.E specialist.&lt;br />&lt;br />During a typical day children will work at integrated topic work, work in groups for mathematics and some language activities, have a personal reading project, evaluate their work, enjoy music and art activities and take part in a minimum of 2 hours physical activity a week. The school also has a school parliament elected by the children where decisions affecting the whole school e.g. school trips, homework etc. are discussed. A Parent Council is elected in the autumn of each year.&lt;br />&lt;br />The children have a morning break of 15 minutes and a lunch break of 45 minutes. Most children remain in school for lunch or bring their own packed lunch. A few go home. School finishes at 3pm.&lt;br />&lt;br />Judging by their smiling faces, I would say the children enjoy school.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Jean McGuigan</content>
</page></content></entry>