<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-79/GB-368000-795000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-79 GB-368000-795000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-79/GB-368000-795000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-79/GB-368000-795000-22.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-368000-795000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420749</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-08-12T12:13:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-12T12:13:15.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-368000-795000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22A day in Primary Five at Banchory Primary School</title>
<content>

We learn about different things such as Rainforests,Castles,River Dee,Ancient Egypt,Romans and Vikings. We have Smartboards which have projecters to make what ever is on the computer appear on the Smartboards and you can touch the Smartboard instead of using a mouse and theres special pens so that you can draw and write on it. We have an I.C.T suite which is full of computers and thats where we go to research different things. We enjoy learning because we do different things every day. Our favourite subject is Maths, Literacy, Music and Language. we play Maths games, Literacy games and Language games. In our homework we sometimes make games which we can play in class and share with everyone else. We play Education city which is a site that helps us learn about different maths strategies and different mathods. We have lots of clubs such as Quest club, Spanish, Eco, Music club, Chess club, Mountain biking club, Rock climbing club, Basketball club, Netball c lub and After school club. At lunch time we have plastic trays with a section for your lunch a section for your knife and fork a section for your juice and a section for you pudding. You have to pay for your juice and chocolate, strawberry or plain milk.   &lt;br />
Dom and Thomas</content>
</page></content></entry>