<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-70/GB-312000-702000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-70 GB-312000-702000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-70/GB-312000-702000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-70/GB-312000-702000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-702000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435119</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:11:03.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:11:03.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-702000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Update to Andrew Hewitt &amp; Family</title>
<content>

I am now 38 and living in Yorkshire in a housing association flat, my parents live close by. I moved to Yorkshire in 1996 with the rest of the family when my dad changed his job.  My father has retired now and my family and I are about to return to Scotland. &lt;br />&lt;br />Shortly after I wrote the piece for the Doomsday book I became ill and over the next four years my life deteriorated. After sitting my O Grades I became severely ill, housebound and mostly bedbound, then in 1991 was diagnosed with ME. I never made it back to school to sit A Levels or achieve my ambition to go to Art School. My dad and older brother were unaffected but my mum, sister and younger brother all went down with ME too. In the last few years I have improved enough to be able to do a little painting but I am still very ill&lt;br />&lt;br />I enjoy being in my flat and occasionally planting things in my small garden and visiting the nearby shops. I have help in my flat for a couple of hours twice a week and I help at a craft and card work shop for 2 hours on Friday. I have to sleep for a lot of the rest of the time. I go on an occasional outing to local places of interest and to a holiday cottage with the family once a year. I still especially like the coast. &lt;br />&lt;br />Going back to Scotland will be a challenge for me, having to start over again, but I hope my life will improve more as time goes on.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Andrew Hewitt</content>
</page></content></entry>