<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-30-64 GB-308000-645000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-23.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-308000-645000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>442935</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-18T15:31:23.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-18T15:31:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-308000-645000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Some Birds in Dolphinton update</title>
<content>
The past 25 years have produced some changes to the local bird populations and the number of species observed in this area. Changing habitats and different weather patterns have both played a part.&lt;br />&lt;br />Several large ponds have been created and provide nesting habitat for Mute Swans and more recently Greylag Geese. For more than a decade these ponds have also benefited Mallard, Tufted Duck and Teal plus Little Grebe, Moorhen and Coot. These species appear to be declining although Grey Heron numbers remain constant. Wintering Goosander are now regular along with Goldeneye and occasional Cormorant.&lt;br />&lt;br />The valleys continue to act as routes for skeins of wintering geese to pass between their roost at West Water reservoir and their feeding grounds. Mostly Pink-footed seen with occasional Barnacles. There are no recent records of Whooper or Bewicks Swans.&lt;br />&lt;br />Common Buzzard numbers have increased but Kestrels have faired badly. There are regular sightings of Sparrowhawk and Peregrine with occasional Merlin and Hen Harrier. Marsh Harrier, Red Kite and Osprey are spotted occasionally. Tawny Owls do very well but Barn Owls are rare now after two severe winters. There are some reports of Long-eared owls but no recent Short-eared.&lt;br />&lt;br />Carrion Crows, Rooks and Jackdaws are common. Ravens now breed locally and Jays have been seen recently in the breeding season, as have Magpies. Collared Doves are well established and Wood Pigeon breed commonly but no recent reports of Stock Dove.&lt;br />&lt;br />Redshank and Lapwing have declined as breeding species and Curlew, Oystercatcher, Ringed Plover and Common Sandpiper numbers vary annually. Woodcock and Common Snipe also breed here and winter in greater numbers along with Jack Snipe and occasional Water Rail. Other waders seen include Green Sandpiper and Golden Plover.&lt;br />&lt;br />Gulls have had mixed fortunes with a large colony of Black-headed growing over a decade and then mysteriously disappearing. Others such as Lesser Black-backed breed regularly and Mew (Common) Gull continue to winter nearby in large numbers. Terns have not been seen recently. &lt;br />   &lt;br />
Alison McArthur</content>
</page></content></entry>