<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-85/GB-300000-855000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-30-85 GB-300000-855000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-85/GB-300000-855000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-85/GB-300000-855000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-300000-855000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412517</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-13T15:31:58.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:31:58.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-300000-855000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Social Concerns - Shopping</title>
<content>

Fine Fare eventually did open, then was turned into WM Lows, before being taken over by Tesco.  Tesco eventually closed the old store and opened a new one on the Nairn Road - a much bigger store which sells most things.  As for the High Street, the East End Post Office has closed, leaving only the main Post Office at the West End of the High Street.  The Co-op is still there, as are 3 butchers, Murdochs, Macbeths and Frasers.  There are no fruit and veg shops left on the High Street.  Mackenzie and Cruickshanks - the popular ironmongers and department store is due to close on July 2nd 2011, whilst Smiths the Jewellers is still open.  Macleans the Bakers and Ashers the Bakers are still on the High Street, and Boots the Chemist has made an appearance.  There are banks - the Bank of Scotland, Royal Bank of Scotland, Clydesdale and LLoyds TSB. There are a couple of ladies dress shops - however, there is nowhere to buy mens or childrens clothes in Forres.  The only mens outfitters in the town closed in the mid 1990s.   There are alot of charity shops and hairdressers.  This is shopping in Forres in 2011.   &lt;br />
T</content>
</page></content></entry>