<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-66/GB-320000-669000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-32-66 GB-320000-669000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-66/GB-320000-669000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-66/GB-320000-669000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-320000-669000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439753</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:54:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:54:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-320000-669000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21The Union Canal</title>
<content>

The Union Canal has moved away from it's origins as an early 19th century transport link for industry and in modern times is predominantly a recreational area.  The tow path is bustling with the frantic feet of joggers and the wheels of cyclists' bikes.  The canal itself hosts long boats on leisurely cruises alongside canoes and rowing boats.  The water is busiest on Wednesday evenings as the crews of various of the cities universities and schools descend on the canal to practice, at the same time a local canoe club meets further down the canal towards the city.&lt;br />&lt;br />At night the tow path comes alive to the sound of joggers as those people working all day descend for their evening jog.  The tow path is now lit for a way through the city by small lights at each side of the path to guide the way in the darkness. &lt;br />&lt;br />The ultimate destination on the canal is now the Falkirk Wheel, finished in 2002 at a total project cost of £84.5 million, a rotating boat lift that replaced the original 12 locks that linked the 24 metres of difference between Union Canal and the Forth and Clyde Canal.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Joshua Turner</content>
</page></content></entry>