<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-69/GB-328000-690000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-32-69 GB-328000-690000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-69/GB-328000-690000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-69/GB-328000-690000-21.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-328000-690000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412525</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T13:52:22.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:49:21.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-328000-690000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Kirkcaldy Old Kirk</title>
<content>

The Old Kirk, the oldest building in Kirkcaldy, contains the history of the town. Its earliest record is of its consecration in 1244 to St. Patrick and St. Brisse (Bryce) but we know there was an earlier Celtic church on this site after Celtic monks brought the Christian faith in the 6th century. The early church had "lafts" or galleries for the trades associations.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Old Kirk had strong connections with the Town Council and the Kirkin' o' the Council took place annually from 1560 to 1973, with magistrates entering their own gallery through the Robing Room in the tower.&lt;br />&lt;br />The 15th century tower has fine views from its parapet over the town and River Forth. For over 80 years until 2005 there was a tradition on May morning that Old Kirkers climbed to the top to sing Easter hymns to sea and land. The tower houses the bell, the church's oldest possession, dating from the 16th century and recast 3 times. It was still ru ng before services until November 2010.&lt;br />&lt;br />In 1807 the dilapidated sanctuary was replaced by a new one but in 1828 disaster struck when the famous preacher Rev. Edward Irving came to the evening service. The gallery of the packed church gave way and 24 people perished in the stampede to get out. &lt;br />&lt;br />All the gravestones in the churchyard have been recorded by the Old Kirk Heritage Group. The earliest legible gravestone is dated 1585. 29 Provosts are buried here; also Michael Nairn, who began the linoleum industry, and the owners of the Wemyss potteries. Adam Smith, internationally famous economist, was christened in the Old Kirk and Rev. George Gillespie, famous Scots Covenanter, is buried underneath it. Robert Adam, renowned architect, was educated by Thomas Carlyle in the Kirk Wynd school below.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Old Kirk has a magnificent set of stained glass windows flooding it with light, from Burne-Jones designs executed by William Morris to those of modern artis  ts John Clark and Crear McCartney. Around the top is a unique set of stained glass portraits of post-Reformation churchmen, including John Knox and George Gillespie. The memorial window to Jean, wife of former Minister Rev. John Sim, was dedicated at the 750th anniversary of the Old Kirk in 1994.&lt;br />&lt;br /> In 1968 the church was renovated inside to the design of Wheeler &amp; Sproson and renewed after fire damage by vandals in 1986. In 2000 the congregation was re-united with St. Brycedale Church, the former Free Church which had left at the Disruption and the Old Kirk was declared the principal place of worship. In 2005 to accommodate a disabled toilet £240,000 was spent on remodelling the sanctuary to face west instead of east. In 2010 St. Bryce Kirk closed the Old Kirk and Kirkcaldy Old Kirk Trust was set up by local people concerned to preserve 1000 years of the town's history for the community to access and use. The Old Kirk Trust hopes to acquire the building in 2011 to realise this future for it.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: C. Rosemary Potter&lt;br />
Kirkcaldy Old Kirk Trust </content>
</page></content></entry>