<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-60/GB-308000-603000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-30-60 GB-308000-603000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-60/GB-308000-603000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-60/GB-308000-603000-23.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-308000-603000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412505</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-13T15:31:57.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:31:57.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-308000-603000</dblock_id>
<original_item>15</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Moffat - Scotland's 1st Walkers are Welcome town</title>
<content>

Now in its 11th year, the Moffat Ramblers' Walking Festival is the second weekend of September.&lt;br />&lt;br />Since becoming Scotland's 1st Walkers are Welcome town, seven new walks have been signposted.  Each walk is colour coded and there are marker posts to follow.  All walks start from the car park opposite Station Park.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Southern Upland Way passes very close by Moffat and information is available around the town.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Annandale Way long-distance walk from the Beeftub, north of Moffat on the Edinburgh Road to the Solway at Annan, follows the course of the River Annan.&lt;br />&lt;br />Other major events include a Weekend of Traditional Song and Music in April, Moffat Book Events in April and October, a Fun Day in Station Park for children the last Sunday in May, the Moffat Classic Car Rally over the last weekend in June, a Mass Garage Sale towards the end of July, the South of Scotland Tennis Tournament (an LTA event) over the last ten days in July, an annual Art Exhibition at the Old Well Theatre at the end of August, the Lord Dowding Memorial Service in September and a Christmas Festival the last Sunday in November when the High Street is transformed into a Street Market and all manner of fun things happen around the town leading up to the switching on of the famous Moffat Christmas lights at 1700 hours.   &lt;br />
Marilyn Elliott</content>
</page></content></entry>