<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-30-64 GB-308000-645000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-64/GB-308000-645000-22.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-308000-645000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>442933</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-18T15:31:23.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-18T15:31:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-308000-645000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22More Birds in Dolphinton update</title>
<content>

More  Birds in Dolphinton update&lt;br />&lt;br />Cuckoos are rarely heard now but Great-spotted Woodpeckers do well in the woodlands. Green Woodpeckers are also seen and heard along with newly colonising Nuthatches. Treecreepers breed in small numbers but Spotted Flycatchers and Redstarts not around recently after many years of successful breeding.&lt;br />&lt;br />The numerous burns support both Dipper and Kingfisher although recent hard winters have had a bad effect on them. Grey and Pied Wagtails plus Wrens are also low in numbers at the moment. &lt;br />&lt;br />Starlings and House Sparrows both do well here now whilst Swallow and House Martin numbers vary annually, down now after several years of growth. Sand Martins continue to take advantage of the local sand deposits but Swifts are seen only occasionally.&lt;br />&lt;br />Woodlarks are absent now and Skylarks have almost disappeared. Meadow Pipits are no longer common but a few Wheatears still breed in the hills. Stonechats were doing well but no sign of them or Whinchat or Tree Pipit recently.&lt;br />&lt;br />Migrant warbler numbers are generally good. Blackcaps and Willow Warblers are most numerous along with Garden Warbler and occasional Grasshopper Warbler. Chiffchaffs now also breed here and Whitethroats are occasional but no recent Wood Warblers. Sedge Warblers do very well at pond margins and Goldcrests are found in tree belts.&lt;br />&lt;br />All of the tit species breed in good numbers. Coal Tits do particularly well in the woodlands alongside Long-tailed Tits, and Greats and Blues are easy to see. Gardens and scrub support good numbers of Blackbirds but Song and Mistle Thrush are down again recently. Wintering thrushes like Redwing and Fieldfare vary each season depending on food supply and Waxwing are occasional. &lt;br />&lt;br />There are healthy numbers of Chaffinch, Greenfinch and Goldfinch. Bullfinch do very well and like Yellowhammer have benefited from young tree plantations. They also use recently established hedgerows along with Reed Buntings. Siskins breed very successfully here now along with Lesser Redpoll but unfortunately Linnet numbers are down. &lt;br />&lt;br />   
Alison McArthur</content>
</page></content></entry>