<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-17-54/GB-176000-54000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-17-54 GB-176000-54000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-17-54/GB-176000-54000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-17-54/GB-176000-54000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-176000-54000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435117</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:11:02.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:10:14.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-176000-54000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Overview of Perranporth in 2011</title>
<content>

Although Perranporth still has many cafes selling Cornish cream teas, there are also many takeaways serving food from India, China, America and of course fish and chips. There are still many surf shops as well but also a variety of shops providing residents? daily requirements. With the increase in Perranporth?s population (over 3,000 today) well-known high street stores have moved in (Co-op, Boots and Wetherspoons) but family-run businesses, like the butcher, baker, hardware, motor repair, fuel and post office, remain. There is even a health food shop.&amp;#13;&amp;#10;You can still do the same activities as in 1986 though parachuting has replaced gliding at the Airfield. New activities include kite surfing, kite buggies and power kites in restricted areas of the beach, and there is a dog control area at the busiest time of year. On a sunny day in August there can be as many as 10,000 people on the beach. This makes it a busy time for the lifeguards who are now organised by the RNLI.&amp;#13;&amp;#10;Today there are fewer hotels, guesthouses and Bed and Breakfast places as self-catering holidays are more popular. For much of the year the self-catering properties and second homes are empty. It is hoped that the tourist season can be extended to the &amp;#39;shoulder months&amp;#39;.&amp;#13;&amp;#10;Winter in Perranporth is busier than it used to be. The 3-mile long beach used to be quiet in the winter but is now popular for walking, running and even surfing and many other outdoor activities. Surf schools now teach surfing skills throughout the year. Lowender Peran is an inter-celtic festival that takes place every October in Perranporth, celebrating Cornwall&amp;#39;s distinctive heritage of traditional music, dance, songs, story telling and our links with Brittany, Ireland, Isle of Man, Scotland and Wales.   &lt;br />
Karin Easton</content>
</page></content></entry>