<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-28-69 GB-284000-69000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-22.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-284000-69000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412497</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T13:52:22.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:31:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-284000-69000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22An Overview of Newton Abbot</title>
<content>

Newton Abbot is a thriving market town in Devon situated at the head of the beautiful Teign estuary. The pretty river Lemon meanders through the centre of the town, its origin being a small spring bubbling out of the ground on the wilds of Dartmoor.&lt;br />&lt;br />The shops in Newton Abbot give a wide choice to both residents and visitors. There are a number of well-known supermarkets. In Newton Abbot town centre part of it is a pedestrian precinct giving shoppers easy access to a number of well-known chain shops as well as individual independent shops, including butcher, bakers and fruit and vegetable shops, florists, jewellers, bookshops computer stores, hairdressers, beauty salons estate agents, newsagents, stationers and many more places to shop and browse. After all the shopping there are pleasant cafes and restaurants, somewhere to sit down and chat about the day. All the major banks have branches in Newton Abbot as well as Building Societies. N ewton Abbot has a hospital situated at Jetty Marsh which opened earlier this year(2011) &lt;br />&lt;br />Newton Abbot is graced with beautiful parks, Forde Park , Courtenay Park, beautifully planted with a colourful array of plants and shrubs, Decoy Park with its lovely walks around the lake, and Bakers Park with playing fields and wonderful walks through the Bradley woods.&lt;br />&lt;br />For those with a sporting interest Newton Abbot has a rugby club and a football club and golf courses at Stover, Dainton and Hele, which is a public course. Newton Abbot also has a race course which lies between Newton Abbot and Kingsteignton. The race course offers summer National Hunt meetings as well as playing host to many functions throughout the year, such as surf sales, antique sales and car boot sales.&lt;br />&lt;br />Newton Abbot Leisure Centre has a heated indoor swimming pool and also has classes in karate aerobics and other exercise classes running. Full details will b  e available from the Centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />One of the major attractions of Newton Abbot is its location. Not only is it placed at the neck of a beautiful estuary it is only 15mins drive to the moors or the local beaches. Dartmoor National Park is a place of outstanding beauty with extensive panoramic views. Areas of interest include Becky falls, the quarry of Haytor, Dartmeet and Widecoombe in the Moor which is a must for any visitor to the region. The moorland towns of Bovey Tracey, Ashburton and Buckfastleigh all have their own unique character and quaintness.&lt;br />&lt;br />The seaside village of Shaldon and its neighbouring town Teignmouth have lovely beaches which sit either side of the mouth of the river Teign. Teignmouth has a wonderful promenade with a pier, swimming pool and an adventure park for the children. So Newton Abbot is the place to visit if you want to have access to the wilderness of the moors or the rugged coastline with its many coves and beach  es. There is lots to do and explore including scenic coastal paths which will ensure you see south Devon at its best.&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Victoria Coban&lt;br />
Contribution by: Victoria Coban
</content>
</page></content></entry>