<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-28-69 GB-284000-69000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-28-69/GB-284000-69000-24.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-284000-69000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>438385</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-09-29T14:53:35.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-29T14:53:35.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-284000-69000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24Newton Abbot Railway</title>
<content>

Newton Abbot railway station is situated at the east end of Queen Street. It is served by both local and long distance services.&lt;br />&lt;br />Newton Abbot railway station  The South Devon railway reached Newton Abbot in 1846 and changed the town from being just a market town with associated trades (leather and wool) to become a base for industry. The station was opened by the South Devon Railway Company on 30 December 1846. A branch to Torquay was added on 18 December 1848 and one to Moretonhampstead on 26 June 1866, although the latter has since closed to passengers. Isambard Kingdom Brunel used the Teignmouth / Newton Abbot section to experiment with his atmospheric railway. The experiment failed but the remains of pumping house buildings still survive at Starcross and the old Dairy Crest milk processing factory in Totnes. In 1876 the Great Western Railway bought up the railways and developed the repair and maintenance sheds into a substantial works that employed over 600 people to start with but by 1930 over 1,000 men were involved. Extensive sidings were also built making a large marshalling yard. The present station was rebuilt to its current form in 1926. The large clock was gifted by the people of the town.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many other industries were set up beside the railway station: a timber yard, iron and brass foundries, engineering works. The town's population increased from 1,623 in 1801 to 12,518 by 1901. Terraced streets were built to house the workers and attractively styled villas sprang up around the town for the wealthier professionals and retired people.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Recent history&lt;br />&lt;br />The town was bombed twice in air raids during World War II, killing a total of 21. There was a severe flood on 27 December 1979, the latest in a long series, when the River Lemon burst its banks after prolonged rain.&lt;br />&lt;br />Tucked into a corner of the racecourse, Newton Abbot's stock car t rack flourished for nearly 30 years, and attracted fans and drivers from all over the South of England. A short 300-metre oval track, it featured races for the cars of the BriSCA organization, as well as saloons and "bangers", under the promotion of ex-speedway rider Trevor Redmond.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Victoria Coban</content>
</page></content></entry>