<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-41/GB-364000-417000-15.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-41 GB-364000-417000-15</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-41/GB-364000-417000-15.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-41/GB-364000-417000-15.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-417000-15</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439829</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T17:51:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T17:50:08.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-417000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>15Geology of the Chorley Area</title>
<content>

The Chorley district straddles solid rocks of two distinct ages: the Carboniferous and Permo-Trias. Overlying both of these are Recent unconsolidated deposits of till, sand and gravel, mud, peat and alluvium.&lt;br />&lt;br />The older Carboniferous rocks are sand- and gritstones which mainly outcrop in the higher moorlands to the east while the younger Coal Measures rocks generally occupy the lower ground and include thinner sandstones and shales in addition to coal seams. In places, the dominant NNW-SSE trending faults have reversed this arrangement. The strikingly red Permo-Trias rocks mainly underlie thick glacial deposits of the Lancashire Plain and outcrop only rarely. They were produced mainly under hot desert conditions while the Carboniferous rocks were deposited in a association with a large and shifting tropical river estuary.&lt;br />&lt;br />During the last glacial episode, ice covered the highest ground since rocks transported by it from Scotland and the Lake District may be found there. Lower down, the large deposits of sand and gravel were laid down by huge meltwater rivers.&lt;br />&lt;br />Apart from coal, lead has been mined sporadically in the uplands; the sand- and gritstones have provided massive amounts of building stones and sand is also worked locally for the construction industry.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Keith Williams</content>
</page></content></entry>