<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-32.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-32</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-32.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-32.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-32</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420049</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:49:57.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:49:57.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>32Farming</title>
<content>

There is only one farm left in Satterthwaite (Bowkerstead Farm) and one at Grizedale (Home Farm). Both are owned by the Forestry Commission and are tenanted by the Threlkeld family. They have sheep flocks and beef herds for meat and animal sales, but no longer any dairy cattle because of changes to the European Agricultural Policy. Silage is the preferred method of ensuring winter food supplies.&lt;br />&lt;br />The wool produced by the hill sheep has no value and is usually discarded, although a small amount is now being used for carpet and rug making by a local firm, and as insulation in new-build houses.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are no battery hens. A few residents keep hens to supply themselves with eggs and to raise a small amount of money by selling the surplus.&lt;br />&lt;br />Farm incomes are low and farmers are encouraged to diversify. Bowkerstead Farm has done so by adding a popular campsite, which so far has proved more lucrative than bree ding animals. There was a riding centre but this closed about two years ago, although livery stables and ‘bring your horse on holiday’ are still in operation.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>