<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-24.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420025</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:41:34.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:39:51.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>6</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24Transport</title>
<content>

Most families in the valley have at least one car, with many owning two. Ulverston and Ambleside are the nearest shopping centres, both twelve miles distant, although there is a convenience store in Hawkshead. Some people like to go to bigger towns such as Manchester, Lancaster, Kendal and Barrow.&lt;br />&lt;br />The only alternative to using a car is a demand-responsive taxi service called ‘Rural Wheels’. The postbus service ceased to operate about five years ago when Cumbria County Council removed its subsidy.&lt;br />&lt;br />Two school buses operate, one taking infant and primary school children to Backbarrow, the other taking the secondary school pupils to Ulverston, but neither bus is available for use by local adults.&lt;br />&lt;br />For most people, cycling to access shops and jobs is not a viable option as the area is mountainous. Neither is walking, due to the distances involved and the rugged terrain.&lt;br />&lt;br />Senior citizens rely on family and friends who have cars. There are no longer any OAP outings organised by Age Concern and the local OAP Committee has ceased to exist.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>