<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-28.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-28</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-28.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-28.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-28</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449705</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:54.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:54.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>28Family Life</title>
<content>

Of the 34 people we surveyed only 10 were born near Timsbury.31 of these people have children but 3 do not. The average age of the children is 9 years old. A lot of children are of school age. Most people in Timsbury have lived there for 6-11 years but some have lived in Timsbury for 15 or more.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />The people living in Timsbury are mainly living in a 4 bedroom house the least popular is a 3 bedroom house. A few people have a 6 bedroom house, 5 bedroom house, 1 bedroom house and a 2 bedroom house. &lt;br />&lt;br />From our survey we have discovered that Tesco superstore in Paulton, is the most popular place to shop for the people who live in Timsbury. Sainsbury and Asda is the next most popular. &lt;br />&lt;br />When we asked people if any of their family lived abroad there were 6 families who had. 2 families have relatives in Ireland , 2 others have families in France and Canada and 1 New Zealand. &lt;br />&lt;br />The most popular food in Timsbury is fish and chips, the 2nd  most popular is roast dinner the 3rd most popular is curry. 7 people said that they went to the pub 3or 4 times a year, 6 people go once a week. The most popular drink in Timsbury is lemonade then it is cola and water.     &lt;br />
Charlie, Georgia, Paige, Connor &amp; Chloe</content>
</page></content></entry>