<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-17.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-17</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-17.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-17.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-17</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448035</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:11.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>17Ennerdale Water update 2011</title>
<content>

Ennerdale Water is a stunning natural asset in the valley. At two and a half miles long and just under one mile wide, it is a prominent feature in the landscape. The lake is designated a SSSI for its high biological value and characteristic flora &amp; fauna typical of an oligotrophic (nutrient poor) lake. This includes a rare fish, the Arctic Charr, with a fragile population which was in decline but thanks to the significant efforts of the Environment Agency artificial rearing charr from eggs and changes to the management of the valley through removal of conifers the population appears to be climbing. 2011 saw the best char spawning in decades.&lt;br />&lt;br /> The lake is reputed to have some of the cleanest water in the country, fed by the River Liza which flows the length of the valley. Records of human activity on the lake (extraction of water, raising water levels, fishing, transporting of raw materials) date back to the mid 1800s. Water extraction dates back to 1848 and the level of the lake has been raised on a number of occasions since, to meet increasing demands for water from West Cumbria. &lt;br />&lt;br />Recent declines in industry have significantly reduced demand. &lt;br />&lt;br />United Utilities (formerly North West Water) now owns the lake and a new pumping station  was built at Bleach Green in 1999. THis serves 60,000 customers daily. Water levels fluctuate as a result of water extraction and there are several associated structures which detract from the landscape. Most notably is the several hundred metres of stone and concrete revetment along the lakeshore, along with structures around the outfall site and the fish pass. Ennerdale falls within the "Quiet Lakes" area of Lake District National Park. Recreation on lake is limited to rowing, canoeing &amp; angling (no sail craft or motor powered craft), managed through a permit system by United Utilities. Lakeshore walks are also popular with visitors. Water extraction is by far the most economically significant activity in the valley.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>