<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-30.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-30</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-30.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-30.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-30</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449719</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>30Hairstyles in Timsbury</title>
<content>

This is about a survey that we took home and interviewed our parents and here are the results that came back to school about peoples favourite hair styles. &lt;br />&lt;br />One person liked Lego hair the most.  7people preferred bobs.  7 people liked long hair.   The number of people who loved pony tails was 3. &lt;br />&lt;br />I person liked D.A.s they're cool he said. 1 person liked a bald head. 1 person liked army cut hair style.&lt;br />&lt;br />By Rhiannon and Holly&lt;br />&lt;br />Traffic Survey&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />2 weeks ago on a Monday morning at 9.30am, we completed a traffic survey, next to the Co-op in North Road. This is one of the busiest roads in Timsbury and one of the smallest. We counted the cars, motor-bikes, vans, cars, truck, tractors, scooters, bus, land rover and range rover. &lt;br />&lt;br />Here are our findings of the vehicles that passed us in the half an hour:      &lt;br />&lt;br />0 motor bikes    &lt;br />&lt;br />15 vans                   &lt;br />&lt;br />55  cars     &lt;br />&lt;br />2 trucks&lt;br />&lt;br />1 tractor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br />1 scooter&lt;br />&lt;br />1 bus&lt;br />&lt;br />By Sam. Jake and Jordan.&lt;br />&lt;br />We found out that cars are the most popular vehicle in which to travel to work.  8 people said they  worked in  Bath,   1 person worked in Bristol, 3 work for sales,   1 person  works at home  , 2 people work at St Mary's. However, there are some important businesses in Timsbury which we went to investigate further.  &lt;br />
Luke</content>
</page></content></entry>