<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-38/GB-356000-387000-16.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-35-38 GB-356000-387000-16</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-38/GB-356000-387000-16.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-38/GB-356000-387000-16.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-356000-387000-16</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435995</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T10:27:27.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T10:27:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-356000-387000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>16Fiddlers Ferry before the power station</title>
<content>

Rather than commenting on Fiddlers Ferry as it in 2011, I wish to give a personal picture of what it was like before the building of the massive power station. I was born in 1940 in Highfield Crescent, Farnworth, Widnes and my grandfather lived in Stocks Lane Penketh. As children, well before the power station was built, one of the places to visit was Fiddlers Ferry which we travelled to on our home built bikes. We swam in the water there, fished for tiddlers and refeshed ourselves with jam butties and a bottle of Tizer. Fiddlers Ferry was a rural retreat away from the chemical and soap works which polluted the area. The Stocks Lane area of Penketh was and remains a pleasant area in which to live. Then serviced by the Crosville bus service which ran between Warrington and Liverpool Pier Head the areas of Sankey, Penketh and Widnes were sources of labour for the vibrant industies of the area. Education facilites were of a high standard and many a young person was able to achieve a high level of academic success benefitting from a free higher education service. The concentration was on science and engineering to service the local industry.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Norman Sandland</content>
</page></content></entry>