<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-18/GB-392000-186000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-39-18 GB-392000-186000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-18/GB-392000-186000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-18/GB-392000-186000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-392000-186000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436011</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T10:40:26.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T10:40:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-392000-186000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Our Dad as a Fireman</title>
<content>

Our names are Naomi &amp; Louis Harvey; we are 19 and 7 years old. Our Dad has been a Fireman at Malmesbury Fire station for 9 years. We are proud that our Dad is a Fireman and helps others, however sometimes it is frustrating when he gets a fire shout and can be gone for hours at a time. Every September our Dad works very hard to put together the Emergency Services Show- which raises thousands of pounds for charity, at the same time as giving the public the chance to see what exactly the Emergency Services do. &lt;br />&lt;br />In April 2008 our Dad received an award from the Queen because he helped to save somebody's life; this made us extremely proud of him. We do get worried about him being a fireman- but we know that he is doing it to help other people. Our younger sister thinks it is cool that our Dad is a fireman and likes to tell all her friends at school. It's exciting to see our Dad driving the fire engine in the carnival too. &lt;br />&lt;br />Our Dad enjoys being a fireman as he has grown up in Malmesbury and feels he is giving something back to the community. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Naomi &amp; Louis Harvey</content>
</page></content></entry>