<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-19.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448039</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Ennerdale Tourism Update 2011</title>
<content>

The geographical location of Ennerdale is a key factor influencing the nature and scale of tourism provision. As one of the most remote and least visited of all the major Lakeland valleys, the tourist infrastructure is modest when compared to more popular neighbouring valleys (with easier access &amp; more facilities) such as Borrowdale , Buttermere and Wasdale.Ennerdale is designated a "Quiet Area" within the Lake District National Park and as such has stricter development control policies in terms of tourist attractions, marketing and visitor facilities. &lt;br />&lt;br />Tourism does however play an important part in supporting the local economy and livelihoods in Ennerdale, with an infrastructure which includes B&amp;B's, Inns, holiday homes, self-catering cottages, camping/caravan sites, a Field Studies Centre, two YHA's and a bunk barn. The long distance Coast-to-Coast walk attracts a large proportion of visitors supporting accommodation outlets in the Ennerdale &amp; Kinniside Parish, along with two YHAs in the heart of the valley. Additional support comes from "business tourism" much associated with Sellafield Nuclear Processing site. A field study centre at Gillerthwaite draws on a different market, with outdoor activities and education the main attraction for groups. Tourist related facilities are minimal; a village shop and information board in Ennerdale Bridge and two car parks at the west end of the lake. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Wild Ennerdale Partnership carried out a survey of visitors during 2006 using various beam and pressure counters and estimated the number of visitors at the time at 60,000. &lt;br />&lt;br />In 2011 the Wild Ennerdale Partnerships website saw over 11,000 visitors and the Partnerships Flicker photo sharing site saw nearly 20,000 visits and the Partnerships facebook page has 501 fans and saw over 200,000 views in the last 12 months.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Partnership is working with the local community to develop an Information centre in  Ennerdale bridge and has produce 7new guides to the valley that can be downloaded from the website or purchased at local Tourist Information centres.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Partnership runs around 15 to 20 events and activities each year from Guided walks to canoeing, horse riding, children's events and an Easter Festival.   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>