<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-23/GB-388000-231000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-38-23 GB-388000-231000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-23/GB-388000-231000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-23/GB-388000-231000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-388000-231000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412291</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T12:41:35.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T19:20:04.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-388000-231000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Tewkesbury Medieval Festival</title>
<content>

Tewkesbury Medieval Festival began 28 years as a local, one off event, with home made weapons and costumes. Today it is widely regarded at Europe's biggest and best medieval spectacular.&lt;br />&lt;br />Around 2000 re-enactors from all over the world, many in full armour, now take part in the re-creation of the battle of Tewkesbury on part of the site of the original battle of 1471. Most camp in full medieval style for the weekend.&lt;br />&lt;br />Their camps, including that of King Edward, welcome visitors.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is also a large market, where craftesmen and women demonstrate skills from armour and sword making to needlecraft and making  gingerbread.&lt;br />&lt;br />A wide range of entertainment fills the day with colour, and the Bright Knight Tent provides medieval themed activities for children.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are caterers a plenty and beer tent well stocked with real ales and mead.&lt;br />&lt;br />It all takes place on fields off Lincoln Green Lane on the second full weekend in July, and is fully signed from junction 9 of the M5.&lt;br />&lt;br />Entry is free, with a small charge for parking, and the festival opens at 11am on both days, with an official opening at 12 noon on Saturday by the event's patron, actor and historian Robert Hardy.&lt;br />&lt;br />It closes at 6pm on Sturday, when the activities move into town, with a re-creation of the storming of the abbey, and the trial and not  -to serious beheading of captured Lancastrians.&lt;br />&lt;br />It is followed by the service of Compline  the last service of the day for the monks, in the Abbey - and 5pm on Sunday    &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>