<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-42/GB-352000-429000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-35-42 GB-352000-429000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-42/GB-352000-429000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-35-42/GB-352000-429000-21.xml/5" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-352000-429000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411969</as:updateIndex><as:revision>4</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T13:52:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:10:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-352000-429000</dblock_id>
<original_item>19</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Red Rose Radio - Now Rock FM and Magic 999</title>
<content>This article is correct as of Thursday 12th May 2011.&lt;br />&lt;br />Red Rose Radio split to become two radio stations on 1st June 1990, Rock FM and Red Rose Gold (Transmitted on 999 AM or 301 meters Medium Wave).  Red Rose Gold would later to become Magic 999.  The station still remains in St. Pauls Church at St. Pauls Square in the middle of Preston City Centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />Rock FM is Broadcast on the FM Frequency 97.4 MHz and on the new broadcasting System DAB (223.93 MHz). DAB Was not in existence when the initial article was written.&lt;br />&lt;br />Rock FM and Magic are owned by Bauer Radio (Previously EMAP Radio). Rock FM has as a 1.4KW based on WInter Hill. Magic 999 is has an AM Transmitter based in Longton, Lancashire off Liverpool Road.&lt;br />&lt;br />On Magic 999 the Breakfast show on is the only local content, all other shows are simulcast from sister stations in Manchester, Liverpool and Newcastle.  Local News, Travel and Weather Continue.&lt;br />&lt;br />Rock FM have more local content and only take a couple of simucast shows (notably the Sunday Chart Show).
&lt;br />
Contribution by: Ben Pintilie 
</content>
</page></content></entry>