<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448037</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Ennerdale Forest Management</title>
<content>

Looking far back in history to Mesolithic and early Neolithic times (8300 to 3200 BC),  evidence tells us that the landscape was significantly more covered in trees than we see today, perhaps as much as 60% of the valley would have been wooded. Woodland in Ennerdale would have been predominantly oak, alder and birch. Subsequent episodes of forest clearance occurred and by the post Medieval period (late 15th C) the landscape was dominated by pastoral sheep grazing, with only a few remnant woodlands left on The Side and Latterbarrow. &lt;br />&lt;br />The 1860 first edition Ordnance Survey map shows some small conifer woodland was established around Gillerthwaite and Lingmell before the end of the 19th Century. &lt;br />&lt;br />The bedrock of forestry policy in the 1920s was the need to rebuild and maintain a  strategic timber reserve. Stocks were so depleted by the demands of the First World  War  that the new Forestry Commission was given a good deal of freedom to acquire  and plant land. Planting began in Ennerdale in March 1925 and continued through the 20th Century with the final acquisition of land around Clews Gill in 1978. Once again (as with the original woodland clearances), the valley was being shaped by the needs of society - this time a need for timber in case of war. Towards the end of the 20th Century the Forestry Commission started to widen its remit culminating in 1998 with the publication of the England Forestry Strategy. This saw the focus of forest management shift from timber production (linked to falling market prices and competition from Europe) towards rural development, economic regeneration, recreation, access and tourism, conservation and the environment.  &lt;br />&lt;br />Ennerdale has long had negative press associated with conifer plantations. Times are changing however and great effort h  as gone into creating more mixed woodland habitats through native broadleaf planting and thinning/clear felling of monoculture conifer forest. &lt;br />&lt;br />The forest provides a haven for wildlife and is an asset for public enjoyment. Visually detracting pockets of plantation forest do still exist and will be addressed as Wild Ennerdale evolves in the future.   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>