<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-320000-387000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-32-38 GB-320000-387000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-320000-387000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-320000-387000-21.xml/5" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-320000-387000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411943</as:updateIndex><as:revision>4</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T13:52:22.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T15:27:30.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-320000-387000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Red Rocks Nursing Home - update</title>
<content>Whilst once a private villa residence first owned by William Edward Moulsdale from 1913, it transferred ownership to a Major James Bennett in 1936 and was subsequently purchased in 1948 by the Sanne family, when it became one of the first nursing homes in Wirral (Cheshire) to accommodate elderly clients.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Sanne family originally resided in Wallasey where they ran a fresh fish store and greengrocers. They used to cook meals for their more vulnerable clients when they became ill and these were delivered by bicycle - probably the first meals on wheels service. Having taken a closer interest in personally caring for their customers, Mrs Sanne eventually decided to open a residential home in the area.&lt;br />&lt;br />The family and some of their residents subsequently moved to Ellesmere (Shropshire) during WWII, because of the regular damage being inflicted on local housing by German bombing raids of the River Mersey. After renting Ellesmere Grange, they returned to the Wirral after the end of WWII, when they purchased Red Rocks.&lt;br />&lt;br />Red Rocks Nursing Home currently employs approximately 50 staff and accommodates 22 elderly residents in single rooms, and is still operated by the 3rd generation of the same family, now Vaughan.&lt;br />&lt;br />It is widely respected as being one of the best nursing homes in the region and is renowned for its excellent quality of nursing care and cuisine. It has won numerous national and local awards for both its care and environmental practises.
&lt;br />
Contribution by: Mr Michael Vaughan
</content>
</page></content></entry>