<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-23.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448045</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Wild Ennerdale</title>
<content>

Ennerdale is a spectacular upland landscape with rock outcrops, extensive woodland, dynamic natural rivers, a glacial lake and highly valued flora &amp; fauna.  Established in 2003 Wild Ennerdale is a partnership of people and organisations led by the principal landowners in the valley, The Forestry Commission, National Trust and United Utilities with the support of Natural England. There is a partnership website which gives more information. &lt;br />&lt;br /> The Wild Ennerdale partnership has a vision "to allow the evolution of Ennerdale as &lt;br />&lt;br />a wild valley for the benefit of people, relying more on natural processes to shape its landscape and ecology"&lt;br />&lt;br />Wild land is a relatively new concept in the UK and involves giving natural processes greater freedom to develop our future landscapes. Nature conservation in England is generally focused on small-scale interventions, Wild Ennerdale is one of the UK's largest wild land projects allowing ecosystems throughout the valley to evolve with greater freedom. Its experience in managing land through minimal human intervention is already widely recognised and shared by others.&lt;br />&lt;br />This remote Lakeland valley is 9 miles long and extends to an area of 11,640 acres (4711 ha). The valley narrows from west to east and is surrounded by dramatic ridges which include some of Lakeland‟s highest summits such as Great Gable and Pillar both over 3000ft high. At the western end of the valley lies Ennerdale Water which supplies over 60,000 customers  with drinking water.&lt;br />&lt;br />The area is highly significant for its rich legacy of archaeological remains being described as the Lake District's best remaining example of a settled medieval valley. It is also home to diverse habitats for flora and fauna,  which range from regional to international importance. Over 40% of the area is designated as "Site of Special Scientific Interest" and "Special Area of Conservation". The continuous transition of vegetation types, from lakeshore through woodlands and open heath land, to the mountain tops, is spectacular.&lt;br />&lt;br />As the valley develops, it is hoped that there will be a series of naturally evolving and interacting ecosystems across the valley that are far more robust in the face of stresses such as climate change, Farming and forestry will maximise ecology and landscape value. It cannot be predicted exactly how biodiversity may develop as natural processes are given greater freedom. However, being able to observe these processes at work, over generations, will be one of the marvels of change in Ennerdale, and ensure that the lessons learnt will have a resonance far beyond the boundaries of the valley&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>