<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-26.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420031</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:41:35.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:41:35.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26Satterthwaite Village</title>
<content>

Satterthwaite village has a church, a parish room, an inn, and a recreation ground. The village shop closed in 1988. There are approximately 50 houses of which 50% are second homes or commercial holiday lets.&lt;br />&lt;br />The nave and tower of the church (All Saints’) were rebuilt in 1914; the chancel dates from 1867. Its average attendance is now about 7, less than half the number recorded in 1986. The most popular service each year is the Harvest Festival. The parish is part of the combined benefice (established in 2003) of Hawkshead with Low Wray and Sawrey and Rusland and Satterthwaite. There is one service on each of the first four Sundays in every month, with a ‘Service for All Ages’ (introduced in 2008) held on the third Sunday. The church and its organ are in good repair. In the last five years there have been 5 funerals, with burials taking place in the village burial ground, but there were no weddings or baptisms during that period.&lt;br />&lt;br />Satterthwaite Parish Room opened in 1883, constructed on the site of the former Satterthwaite School. A reading room was added in 1903, which now acts as a kitchen. The building is a venue for quiz nights, suppers and business meetings, and is in reasonable repair. A group of local volunteers clean the church and the parish room.&lt;br />&lt;br />Satterthwaite Parish has its own community website and Twitter account which help it keep in touch with the modern world.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>