<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-26.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449707</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2012-11-06T16:20:29.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:54.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26Vegetable Survey of Timsbury</title>
<content>

Out of 34 interviews only three of them had allotments. Eleven people grew their own veg in their garden so nineteen people didn't and that's quite a lot, It's cheaper to grow their own so I don't know why they didn't... Six people grew carrots and only one person grew peas. Four people planted potatoes and two people earthed herbs. There's a lot more to go! Tomatoes was quite popular, seven people grew them! Strawberries are tasty and there are only three people making them grow! One person grew parsnips, one person grew gooseberries, one person grew rhubarb and one person grew courgette. I Like gooseberries but I suppose some people don't; only one gardener grew them! Two people planted cucumbers and five of them grew beans. Mmmmmmm... Lettuce, three people grew them. Leeks... One person grew them! Peppers, three gardeners like them on their dinner plate. &lt;br />&lt;br />One lot of beetroots sits in one person's garden, pink and purple varieties are not very popular! Crunchy apples grown by two people, and their similar shaped relative the pear, also grown by two people (Just shows their related!). Radishes and raspberries got only one grower. I don't like radishes but raspberries, they're tasty! Mmmmmmmmmm!!    &lt;br />
Lucien</content>
</page></content></entry>