<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-14/GB-304000-141000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-30-14 GB-304000-141000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-14/GB-304000-141000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-30-14/GB-304000-141000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-304000-141000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412503</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-13T15:31:57.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:31:57.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-304000-141000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Watchet Festival</title>
<content>

Watchet LIVE returns for its fifth year as West Somerset's largest outdoor 3 day music event. Watchet LIVE is a family friendly festival with amazing views of the stunning West Somerset coast line and beyond. Complete with on site camping, 2 Stages including the famous Croissant Neuf venue, Over 50 live acts, bringing a wide range of high calibre musical acts not normally found performing in West Somerset at a affordable entrance price. Along with Open Mic Tent, The Something Else Tea Tent, Food Court, Workshops, Festival Market, Real Ale and Cider Bar, Kids corner, Headphone Disco and free Car Parking.&lt;br />&lt;br />Watchet Music Festival is run by Watchet LIVE Community Interest Company (C.I.C) who organise events in and around the town of Watchet West Somerset. By staging such events the aim is to help make the town of Watchet a vibrant, diverse and lively place to live and visit for both residents and visitors alike. Staging events such as Watchet LIVE Music Festival and Watchet Carnival over numerous years it has helped generate income into the local economy and community. Any profit made by Watchet LIVE is used to fund and provide free admission community events and is also donated to local groups or charities within the local area that that C.I.C recognises need help.Over the past years money has been donated to Children's Hospice South West, 1st Watchet Sea Scout Group, paid for a visiting artist to hold a flag design workshop at the local primary school. Funded Watchet Phoenix home alone Christmas dinners for the elderly of the town to name a few.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
R Gunns</content>
</page></content></entry>