<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-40/GB-380000-408000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-38-40 GB-380000-408000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-40/GB-380000-408000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-40/GB-380000-408000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-380000-408000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412547</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-13T16:10:09.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T16:10:09.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-380000-408000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21No Change there then</title>
<content>

A road used as a rat-run by lorry drivers has collapsed.&lt;br />&lt;br />A 6ft deep and 5ft wide hole appeared in tree-lined Hollins Brow, Bury.&lt;br />&lt;br />Council workmen repaired the crater over the weekend but the road was closed for more than 24 hours.&lt;br />&lt;br />The incident comes just a month after a police operation to capture truck drivers flouting a new law banning them from using the road and adjoining Croft Lane.&lt;br />&lt;br />In February, residents of Hollins Village, won a seven year fight to stop vehicles over 7.5 tonnes travelling on the roads.&lt;br />&lt;br />The route is used by heavy goods vehicles heading to and from the M66 at Pilsworth.&lt;br />&lt;br />Andrew Taylor of the Hollins Village Community Association, said: "I was alerted at about 2.30pm on Friday. The road collapsed near the top of the hill outside the stables, near the mini roundabout.&lt;br />&lt;br />"It could be down to a combination of wear and tear on the road, the recent rain damaging the drains, and lorries which are heavier than 7.5 tonnes still using the road.&lt;br />&lt;br />"There have been a couple of recent police operations which have targeted lorries. I have reported some companies.&lt;br />&lt;br />"I had a positive e-mail from a firm in Somerset in which they apologised after one of their drivers used the road in lorry that is banned due to its weight " but that may be because I told them I had also informed the police and Traffic Commissioner."&lt;br />&lt;br />Two years ago Croft Lane was closed for several months as major repairs were carried to the road surface. Residents had complained vibrations from passing trucks was rattling windows and shaking the foundations of their homes.&lt;br />&lt;br />After the weight restriction was imposed in February there were several weeks of calm but then residents complained to police that HGV drivers were still cut  ting through to the M66.&lt;br />&lt;br />Police staged a three-day operation in April and stopped 32 lorries. Nine were allowed in the area as they were delivering goods rather than passing through.&lt;br />&lt;br /&gt;But 23 breached the regulations and were each fined £30 for driving in the area.&lt;br />&lt;br />Eight were fined £170 for driving for too a long a period without a rest; and seven £60 each for using a mobile phone at the wheel.&lt;br />&lt;br />Four lorries had mechanical faults " three relating to brakes.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Yollom</content>
</page></content></entry>