<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-25.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420021</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:41:33.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:39:51.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25People and Jobs</title>
<content>

A few local residents work in the valley, either in the tourism and forestry trades, or work from home using the internet, but others travel to the bigger towns such as Ulverston, Kendal and Barrow. There is a reverse flow of workers coming into the valley from these towns, because those in lower paid jobs cannot afford to live here.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Forestry Commission is still the main employer, but its focus has changed from timber production to wildlife conservation and recreational activities. The Grizedale Visitor Centre was rebuilt in 2006 and at the same time an education centre, ‘The Yan’, was added, to encourage town-bred children to discover the countryside.&lt;br />&lt;br />Apart from a few remaining foresters, educational staff, wildlife rangers and tourism staff employed by the Forestry Commission and its franchises, self-employed residents run the Grizedale Lodge Hotel (formerly Ormandy Hotel), the Eagle’s Head Inn, a nd Pepper House B&amp;B. Other self-employed locals include a forestry business person, a landscape consultant, an executive researcher, a cartographer, a carpet cleaner, a mobile motor mechanic, an artist, a handyman, two people working as holiday cottage booking agents, and a logistics expert.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>