<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-34.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-34</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-34.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-34.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-34</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420045</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:49:55.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:49:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>34Recreation Ground</title>
<content>

The recreation ground, built by local volunteers, was opened on 9th July 1983 with funds provided by the Parish Council, the Silver Jubilee Fund and the Rawdon-Smith Trust. It consists of a children’s playground, a tennis court, a cricket/rounders field, and a large wooden storage hut.&lt;br />&lt;br />In the playground, there are two large swings for older children and two low swings for infants, a slide, a rope walkway, and a series of logs and poles set into the ground for balancing feats. The two crawl tunnels have been removed because Health and Safety inspectors say they are a danger to modern children, who might bang their heads on the lining whilst using them. Rubber mats have been placed under and around all the play equipment in case a child falls off or trips over, again due to Health and Safety concerns.&lt;br />&lt;br />The playground committee, whose members maintain the site, is struggling to find enough people to join it, now that there are so few children in the village. Recently, a second-hand sit-on lawnmower costing about Â£700 has replaced the ancient version that had become too costly to maintain. Selling keys each year for the tennis courts, which raises most of the maintenance income, is getting more difficult as the number of permanent residents declines. The summer barbeque still takes place but again with diminishing numbers of attendees.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>