<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-36.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-36</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-36.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-36.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-36</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449725</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>36Interview with The Rev.Hare</title>
<content>

Rev. Hare enjoys meeting people and talking to them. He enjoys special times of years like Christmas because it a very special part of the year and also a magical time. Rev. Hare started his job as Reverend in 2001. He was solicitor for 25 years before joining the church. He's lived in Timsbury since January 2001 and the Church has provided a modern house for him to live in.   He was the first Rev to live in it by choice because he did not want to live in a big Rectory house which the church had traditionally provided. Lots of children come to his church and the children love the extra clubs such as "snap  group" which is on Sunday nights.&lt;br />&lt;br />The best about his work is Timsbury it's a real village- not a picturesque  image but real activities shops people of all ages and sizes  a real community all mixed together helping each other . He loves that people talk together a lot a friendly village and all together we make a good village.&lt;br />&lt;br />We asked "Is it hard running the church?" &lt;br />&lt;br />He replied, "It's busy! There are no set hours but I can be working very late into evenings and weekends (50-60 hours a week). I can be asked to do lots of weddings in the summer, especially between June and September."   &lt;br />
Paige and friends</content>
</page></content></entry>