<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-27.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-27</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-27.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-27.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-27</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449709</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2012-11-06T16:20:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>27Kitchen appliances in Timsbury</title>
<content>

Out of the thirty four Timsbury surveys we sent out all thirty four people had an oven and only for people had a hob. Twenty four people had a dishwasher. This is a marvellous invention because it means people don't have to wash their dirty dishes by hand. They simply put the grubby items in dishwasher, add a washing tablet, close the door and switch it on. This leaves owners free to enjoy their spare time. I am surprised that not every house has one!&lt;br />&lt;br />Having a microwave is great but only twenty six people had one. Instead of taking ages making food and putting it in the oven, get a readymade meal from the freezer and pop it in the microwave for a few minutes. I think everyone should get one because they are very useful.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Only one person has a sandwich toaster. I know it's pretty weird to toast sandwiches but it saves time! And one late counted survey even has a candyfloss maker!  Fourteen people had a handy toaster for toasting bread. Yummy! We counted that four people a mixer or a blender. Kettles are for making cuppas which sixteen people owned. This object is very handy at stressed and hectic times. Just plug it in, boil the water, add a tea bag pour the water and voila! You've got yourself a cuppa! Large machines were highly popular as thirty two people had a fridge-freezer.  Everybody had a washing machine. Two people had slow cookers, five people had a health grill and four people had fryers. Six people had a tumble dryer and only one person had scales.   &lt;br />
Hattie and Elsa</content>
</page></content></entry>