<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-25/GB-364000-252000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-25 GB-364000-252000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-25/GB-364000-252000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-25/GB-364000-252000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-252000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412637</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-15T11:43:12.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-15T11:43:12.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-252000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Bromyard &amp; District Local History Society</title>
<content>

The Society, founded in 1966, exists to foster interest, enjoyment, research and publication in the field of our local history.  It offers all members a varied programme of events, at least monthly, throughout the year. These are mainly illustrated lectures in the winter and guided outings in the summer. It stages an exhibition every year at the Local and Family History Centre 5 Sherford Street Bromyard and Bromyard Gala and the Society publishes an annual Journal containing items of local history and accounts of its activities.&lt;br />&lt;br />At the new Local History Centre there are excellent facilities for research and we are endeavouring to make our now considerable archive more available to the public. Many photographs &amp; documents relating to family, trade and property etc have been donated over the years and these are stored in our purpose built archive.  Other records that include the local newspapers, parish registers and censuses are stor ed on film and fiche. Changing displays of local interest are staged in the Exhibition Room.  If you would like to be involved, we are always looking for volunteers to help and to take part in our activities.  Do call in.&lt;br />&lt;br />Open Thursdays and Fridays 10.0am - 12.30pm &amp; 2.00pm - 4.30pm and Saturdays 10.0am - 12.30 pm.  Other times by appointment.  Our website has further information. The Society also publishes an annual Journal and some back copies are available from in the shop.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>