<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-32.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-32</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-32.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-32.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-32</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449715</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>32THE CONNIE'S TEAROOM</title>
<content>

We went to interview Sarah and Alex Fan, the owners of the tearooms. We found out lots of key information about the place. They are open Monday to Saturday, 9am-5pm. The most popular food is the pannini &amp; the most popular drink served is filter coffee. Carrot cake is the best selling cake in the tearooms. This would count as a full meal which would usually cost about five pounds.&lt;br />&lt;br />We found out that the tearoom have their fresh, daily bread delivered around 5am every weekday morning including Saturday. The bread is bought from a bakery   in Midsummer Norton. When we asked if they have ever run out of food they replied that they had run out of little things like bread and coleslaw. Saturdays are the busiest days for the Connie's, we think this is because a lot of people don't work Saturdays, so have free time to meet friends for a coffee. Many people give tips to show how much they have enjoyed their visit to the tea rooms. These tips are shared out between all nine members of staff.&lt;br />&lt;br />But it's not all good, once when they were doing it up they found that the roof was rotten and they had to replace it!&lt;br />&lt;br />The staff have a shift rota so they all work at different times. We asked Mrs Fan if they sell anything else apart from food and drink in the tearooms, "We sell jewellery, cards, bunting, and other crafts" she replied. They sell many types of food such as hot breakfast, sandwiches, Panini's, homemade cakes, quiche, ice cream, tea &amp; coffee. The couple enjoy their job a lot and intend to carry on a long time. The Connie's tea room got its name from the owner of the building and chip shop next door some years ago. &lt;br />&lt;br />With a five star rating for food hygiene and delicious food we would definitely go! &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>