<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-20.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-20</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-20.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-20.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-20</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448041</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>20Ennerdale Farming Update 2011</title>
<content>

Archaeological evidence suggests that the Ennerdale valley has been subject to low intensity farming since the Bronze Age. In comparison to other Lakeland valleys, more recent farming has been (for the most part) on a limited scale and thus evidence of historic activity remains extremely well preserved. &lt;br />&lt;br />Today farming remains one of the major influences upon the landscape in Ennerdale; sheep grazing predominates on the fells (very few intakes). All the farmland within the Wild Ennerdale boundary is owned by the three partners and is tenanted by a number of farmers, some of whom farm from over the Ennerdale watershed. In addition there are some privately owned parcels of land which fall outside the Wild Ennerdale boundary but lie within the Ennerdale valley. The partners are committed to working with neighbouring land owners and to take opportunities to manage all the land within the watershed in a holistic manner. Historic grazing levels have reduced species composition on the fells and surpressed upland heath communities. More recently there has been a move towards a reduction in sheep numbers from some areas, and a total exclusion of sheep from others (e.g. Red Beck Close on the south-west side of the valley). Large areas of land designated as SSSI area moving from "unfavourable condition" to unfavourable improving following reduction in sheep grazing and repairs to the ridge wall reducing encroachment from neighbouring Common sheep.&lt;br />&lt;br />In the last 5 years extensive grazing Galloway cattle have been introduced into the valley and three herds now have freedom to roam around 1000ha. The cattle are out all year round and have to seek out their forage daily. They give birth unaided often taking themselves away from the herd for a number of days. The cattle have been reintroduced as they are seen as a missing natural process. Their dunging, patchy grazing and ground disturbance providing opportunities for vegetation change.   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>