<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-13/GB-328000-135000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-32-13 GB-328000-135000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-13/GB-328000-135000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-13/GB-328000-135000-19.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-328000-135000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412519</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-13T15:49:20.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-13T15:44:12.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-328000-135000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Bridgwater-Now</title>
<content>Bridgwater has changed dramatically since the original article back in the day. The Cellophane factory has been torn down because they moved production elsewhere because of the cost rises. The precinct is now built and business is booming. We used to have a swimming pool called Splash but because it cost to much to run so the council tore it down and they are supposed to be building a Tesco's soon but they are still undecided whether they build that or something else. They are now building the new swimming pool near Chilton secondary school which is being remodeling due to the schools of the future project someone was running. Blake secondary school and Elmwood school are also getting remodeled due to this project. The YMCA has been remodeled and there are lots of activities available. My school (East Bridgwater Community School - Sydneham) will be changing in September 2012 and will then be called Bridgwater Academy and will be joining with Sedgemoor M anor Juniors and the Sedgemoor Manor Nursery to make one big academy from ages 3-16. Unfortunately our fair little town is turning into the town of shops and I swear if they build one more in years to come we will be known not as Bridgwater but The Shopping Town Of England. Hopefully the next time someone writes an article about this town it will have changed dramatically (for the good).   &lt;br />
Rachel</content>
</page></content></entry>