<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-39/GB-380000-393000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-38-39 GB-380000-393000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-39/GB-380000-393000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-39/GB-380000-393000-21.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-380000-393000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411965</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2012-07-13T16:50:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:00:42.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-380000-393000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Today was more interesting than usual</title>
<content>I'm woken up at 6.25am by our little boy, who is 14 months, and get his morning milk. Back to bed for a cuddle for half an hour before making his breakfast of porridge and banana and back upstairs to play with him in his bedroom while my wife gets up. His mum is taking him off to her parents in Lancaster today because she has a meeting all morning at the University, where she is going on secondment from her work. They'll be staying overnight. They head off at 8.45am. I have breakfast of toast with marmite and peanut butter, orange juice and my third cup of tea of the morning listening to the Today programme, where I hear about the Domesday Reloaded project. Just after 9am I go upstairs and check my emails. At 10.30am I have a quick wash and walk to the office of the organisation in Hulme where I work part time. I arrive at 11am. I'm planning on going to a talk at 2.30pm at the Future Everything conference but get diverted into a meeting that makes me late to leave, at 2pm. I've left my conference pass at home so walk back quickly and then to Cornbrook tram stop. A tram arrives as I'm buying my ticket and the tram door closes on me just as I'm trying to get on. The next tram arrives quickly. I get off at Piccadilly Gardens - five minutes to the conference. After the second talk, at 4.20pm, I go and look at the art exhibition on the ground floor. My favourite thing is Nicolas Felton's 'Feltron Annual Reports' which collate all sorts of measurements about Felton's daily life (coffees drunk, songs listened to) and present them in graphs and maps reflecting the year's activities. I make one of the digital exhibits go wrong by pressing something and walk off hoping no one notices. Later I see someone looking at it bemused until a member of staff comes along and fixes it. At 5pm I walk to Piccadilly Gardens and go into the Manchester Visitor Centre which I've not noticed before. I consider buying a mug for my wife which has the slogan 'We do things differently here' from Tony Wilson on it, but it's a bit overpriced. It makes me think of St Ann's Church, where his funeral was held and where I used to go and sit sometimes during the day just after my brother died.  I buy a 'Dine in for 10 pounds' deal from M&amp;S and get the tram from Mosley Street to Cornbrook, walk ten minutes home, arriving around 6pm. I put the food in the oven and go online, then start writing this until 7pm, when I eat tea watching Channel 4 news. At  7.30pm I write more of this.  I'm supposed to be working but go online at 8pm and never do. Edit this to size. 9.55pm have a glass of wine. Watch the BBC News. Bed at 10.30pm. Brief read. Sleep. &lt;br />
Contribution by: Dan Welch
</content>
</page></content></entry>