<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-328000-387000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-32-38 GB-328000-387000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-328000-387000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-32-38/GB-328000-387000-22.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-328000-387000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411947</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T13:52:22.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T15:31:31.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-328000-387000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Bidston Observatory &amp; Proudman Oceanographic Laboratory</title>
<content>Proudman Oceanographic Laboratory moved to a purpose built building next to the Liverpool University campus in 2004. &lt;br />&lt;br />Bidston Observatory, Proudman Oceanographic Laboratory and the former site of Braehead Cottages are up for sale.&lt;br />&lt;br />Since 2004 most buildings here have been left vacant and the area has attracted graffiti and flytipping. The access road has also been used to abandon stolen (and burnt out) cars on Bidston Hill.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Bidston Preservation Trust does want to buy the buildings and run it as a museum. Who knows what will happen? The Observatory had been in use since 1866, although the POL building is more modern with a thirty year lease from Wirral Council.&lt;br />&lt;br />Although some students are living in one of the buildings, the loss of local employment and effect on the local economy of POL's move to Liverpool was one that caused much concern to local residents. These days instead of academics this area of the hill is most frequented by people walking their dogs.&lt;br />&lt;br />Clearly any decisions are made many miles away with no thought for the local community.&lt;br />&lt;br />Bidston Windmill (after a lot of money was spent on it) is now open to the public on certain days and Tam O'Shanter Urban Farm continues to attract large numbers of visitors.
&lt;br />
Contribution by: Mr John Brace
</content>
</page></content></entry>