<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-31.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-31</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-31.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-31.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-31</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449713</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2012-11-06T16:20:29.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>31Interviews of people running businesses and working in Timsbury.</title>
<content>

Answers from Mr Bill Pearce owner of allotments&lt;br />&lt;br /> Mr Bill Pearce moved in to Timsbury in 1965, so he has been living here for 38 years in which time he has purchased 2 allotments of his own. Over all in Timsbury there are 68 allotments, WOW! &lt;br />&lt;br />Mr Bill Pearce loves living in Timsbury because the are lots of exciting things such as good and friendly shops, nice people and lots of interesting clubs and sports.&lt;br />&lt;br />Mr Bill Pearce says "I grow every vegetable that you can think of, even red cabbage". He remembers that in the seventies there was such bad weather that it killed lots of the plants because it was very cold and lots of high snow. The area around the allotments has changed alot because of housing estates.&lt;br />&lt;br />&#xd; 
  Mr. Pearce came to our school and taught some of the children about the allotments.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Even though the vegetables are great you are not allowed to sell them. The allotments are all 15 meters by 5 meters large! &lt;br />&lt;br />He's seen pictures of purple carrots but he doesn't actually grow them. He does grow spinach but doesn't like it. He likes sprouts and therefore grows them. He grows a lot of things now that he did not grow back in 1965 such as garlic... (A lot more than that!). He grows lots of amazing vegetables like purple cabbage and purple broccoli!   &lt;br />&lt;br />Sadly he does not grow anything blue.  He said: "I find about 20 pests a day!" Most people grow mushrooms in a log, but he has tried...and failed...  &lt;br />&lt;br /> He grows summer broccoli, and winter broccoli, and also seasoned broccoli. He has grown Jerusalem artichokes, but not any other type of artichoke. His favourite type of vegetable is beans, whilst in season and sprouts!    &lt;br />
Elsa, Connor, Charlie and Holly</content>
</page></content></entry>