<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-25/GB-384000-252000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-38-25 GB-384000-252000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-25/GB-384000-252000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-38-25/GB-384000-252000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-384000-252000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436007</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T10:40:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T10:40:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-384000-252000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Changes and corrections</title>
<content>

The 'Worcester-Droitwich canal' alluded to in the original article, is in fact called the 'Birmingham-Worcester Canal', and like all canals, was the principle highway for the movement of goods and raw materials between the midlands and Worcester, in Victorian England.   Where the canal ends, at what is known as Diglis Basin, there used to be a variety of small storage units and warehouses, where goods brought up the River Severn from the docks at Gloucester and Bristol would be off-loaded and stored, before being loaded onto the smaller narrow boats (barges), which were used to transport the goods through the narrower canal.   The last two pairs of lock gates, before the canal meets the river at Diglis, to the south of Worcester City, are much wider than the others along the length of the canal, specifically to accommodate the larger vessels used on the river.   Some of the original warehouses have been converted to offices and, more recently, housing, whilst others have been demolished entirely, to make room for modern apartments.   A small, local pub called 'The Anchor' has survived the redevelopment so far, but one of the redeveloped warehouses, which appears to have been designed with a restaurant in mind, has stood empty and unused for three years or more.   Perhaps this might change when the additional development of houses and apartments between the Diglis Basin and the river are completed in the next year.&lt;br />&lt;br />The world-renowned Royal Worcester Porcelain Works, was once spread over a large site between the west bank of the canal and the east bank of the river, with its main administrative buildings and museum situated in Severn Street.  Sadly, in the region of 80% of its buildings have been cleared or converted for residential development, resulting in very attractive, modern places to live for those able to afford them, but the loss of several hundred jobs.   The Porcelain museum remains open today, but the few pieces still sold are manufactured in the far east.&lt;br />&lt;br />Much of the housing in the southern region of Worcester actually varies in age between new and 150 years old, although there are numerous well preserved examples of housing a good deal older.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Will Richards</content>
</page></content></entry>