<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-39/GB-332000-390000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-39 GB-332000-390000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-39/GB-332000-390000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-39/GB-332000-390000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-390000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411963</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-06T16:24:38.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T16:24:38.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-390000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Tourism in Liverpool</title>
<content>In the 1980's few people considered Liverpool as a place worth visiting whereas tourism is now one of the main industries in the city. Today, there are many hotels in the city in contrast to the four present in the 1980's. Also in 1980's saw the beginning of tours around the city, which has now developed into an industry of its own with four companies operating tours all day and every day. The cruise liner terminal has introduced a new means for people to visit the city with local tour guides providing personal tours. On average twelve cruise liners visit the city every year bringing around three thousand passengers every time. Foreign students also bring their own tourism with friends and family visiting the city. Since the 1980's the Beatle tourism industry has gone from strength to strength and has seen the recruitment of specifically trained Beatle tour guides. Liverpool won European capital of culture 2008 which drew the attention of the rest of the world and put liverpool back on the map attracting more and more tourism from across the globe.&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>