<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-51 GB-312000-513000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-51/GB-312000-513000-22.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-312000-513000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448043</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:11.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-312000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Ennerdale History Update 2011</title>
<content>

Ennerdale has provided for people's needs for many centuries. The range of monuments and features within the valley demonstrates how the landscape has been influenced and altered by man for over 3500 years. Over five hundred individual archaeological sites have been recorded through recent survey work, many of which are of regional and national importance.  &lt;br />&lt;br />Looking as far back as the Mesolithic and early Neolithic periods, the landscape in the region was almost entirely tree covered. In Ennerdale this woodland was predominantly oak, alder and birch. Evidence suggests an episode of forest clearance between 3200BC and 2700BC with more extensive clearance episodes continuing during the Bronze Age (2000BC-800BC). At the same time, low intensity pastoral farming was introduced to the fells. This restricted the re-growth of trees and resulted in slow (but more long lasting) woodland clearance. &lt;br />&lt;br />By the Iron Age (800BC-AD43) there was an enclosed settlement in the valley implying widespread clearance and drainage on the valley floor. There is uncertainty as to whether there was a break in the settlement of the valley during the later Roman/Early Medieval period but if this had been the case, there is a likelihood of some recovery of the natural forest. &lt;br />&lt;br />During the early medieval period (AD410-AD1066), a settlement developed from a clearing within the forest at Gillerthwaite. At this same time, there is evidence of a second site of activity at the head of Ennerdale Water. Both settlements were slow to develop and it was not until the later medieval or post medieval period that the valley floor was enclosed and improved. The higher ground was subject to transhumance (seasonal) farming and much of the land on the southern side of the valley was enclosed for deer farming. &lt;br />&lt;br />During the medieval period the mineral potential of the valley was realised and resulted in the increasingly intensive extraction (iron ore) and localised despoiling of the fell sides. The Smithy Beck settlement remains remarkably intact, complete with evidence of medieval iron production. &lt;br />&lt;br />The post-medieval period saw (in common with other upland areas) the increasingly intensive pastoral exploitation of the valley sides. The numbers of stock shelters and bields are testament to rising numbers of sheep on the fell which inevitably had an impact on vegetation. This system of exploitation was rationalised in the later nineteenth century with the parliamentary enclosure of much of the fellside. The impacts of post-war intensive agriculture were restricted by the acquisition of a large proportion of the valley for forestry.  &lt;br />&lt;br />Historical evidence shows us how  the landscape and ecology of Ennerdale has been shaped by the cultural and economic values of the day. Archaeology and features in the landscape provide us with an understanding of those changes. In the context of present day changes in public policy, social and economic needs, we have the opportunity to influence the next phase of Ennerdale's evolution with the needs of present and future generations in mind.   &lt;br />
Gareth Browning</content>
</page></content></entry>