<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-33.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449717</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:55.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>17</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33Interview P.C. Boulton</title>
<content>

P. C. Boulton was asked to be interviewed and happily gave a lot of information about policing in the local area. &lt;br />&lt;br />He works 10 to 24 hours a day and personally arrests 1 person per week on average; he has been trained to use a taser gun but has not seen the need to use it in Timsbury. He has used the baton and taser numerous times but only when he happened to not be in Timsbury, and only when he needed to gain control over struggling criminals. &lt;br />&lt;br />P.C. Boulton has been in the police force for a couple of years, but because he likes the department he's in, he has not wanted to do the exams so he can move up from Constable to Sergeant. He also earns money in amounts that are similar to teachers, so there is no real need to move up anyway. He works in the operation department, where he and 7-8 other officers take turn to drive a van to where ever they're needed.  The constable likes his job.&lt;br />&lt;br />P.C. Boulton also brought in the list and figures of crimes in Timsbury from January- July 2011. &lt;br />&lt;br />The figures are as follows:&lt;br />&lt;br />January:  2 burglaries, 3 anti-social behaviours, 5 violent crimes and 1 other crime.&lt;br />&lt;br />February: 1 burglary, 9 anti-social behaviours and 11 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />March: 6 anti-social behaviours, 2 vehicle crimes, 1 violent crime and 7 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />April: 7 anti-social behaviours, 3 vehicle crimes, 6 violent crimes and 4 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />May: 10 anti-social behaviours, 3 vehicle crimes, 5 violent crimes and 2 other crimes. &lt;br />&lt;br />June: 9 anti-social behaviours, 1 vehicle crime, 2 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />July: 1 burglary, 7 anti-social behaviours, 1 violent crime and 4 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />Total: 4 burglaries, 9 vehicle crimes, 51 anti-social crimes, 18 violent crimes and 31 other crimes.&lt;br />&lt;br />(Please note each 1 is a report o  f a crime, not necessarily 1 different crime.)&lt;br />&lt;br />There have been no major crimes in Timsbury, though he has been to major crimes, like the riot in Bristol. &lt;br />&lt;br />He's used the sniffer dogs once in Timsbury (a drug search, a couple of years ago) but because sniffer dogs are changed quite often, he has not got a favourite. &lt;br />&lt;br />He works 2 out of 3 weekends so this police officer is a very busy man. He works 6 days, doesn't work for 4 days, works for 7, and doesn't work for 4 (his 3 week rota). He has been hit, but not in Timsbury, and has had a few false alarms (don't let 4 year old kids get hold of the phone!). He messes up sometimes, but rarely, as he's been put through lots of tough training, testing his physical fitness, calmness, honesty, and to ensure he's sensible enough. &lt;br />&lt;br />He said his favourite part of his job was the variety and the surprise of what needs doing. Overall, Timsbury is a  safe village, only needing to be patrolled by 2 officers and 1 beat officer.   &lt;br />
Georgia, Ethan, Ben, Rhiannon</content>
</page></content></entry>