<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-34.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-34</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-34.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-34.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-34</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449723</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>17</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>34CROSSING PATROL OFFICER</title>
<content>

We talked to Colin Jackson about his job as the crossing patrol officer for our primary school.&lt;br />&lt;br />We asked Colin if he likes his job and he told us he did, because he likes working with children.  We then asked him how long he has been working as a crossing patrol officer and found out he has been doing this for 2 and half years. He started his job on the 6th of October 2008. He doesn't work at weekends because the school is closed. &lt;br />&lt;br />We then asked him more about his job. He told us that he had never dropped the lollypop stick on a car. He also said that everyone is really polite - they say please and thank-you after he has helped them across the busy main road.&lt;br />&lt;br />He works for 1 and half hours per day,  split into 2 sessions a day, one in t  he morning and one in the afternoon.&lt;br />&lt;br />Colin helps on average 40 children per day to cross the road safely. &lt;br />&lt;br />All the children at St. Mary's Primary really love having Colin as our Crossing Patrol Officer because he has a wonderful personality, great sense of humour and his really kind to everyone. Thank you Colin for your help.  &lt;br />
Jordan, Luke, Zack and Connor O - Y5 pupils from St. Mary's, Timsbury.</content>
</page></content></entry>