<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-36.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-49 GB-332000-492000-36</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-36.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-49/GB-332000-492000-36.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-492000-36</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420047</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-07-25T15:49:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-25T15:49:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-492000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>36People and Hobbies</title>
<content>

In order to help with this section, 50 questionnaires were sent out houses within the Satterthwaite D-block.&lt;br />&lt;br />The most popular hobby by far was gardening, with competition prizes awarded for the best flowers and produce exhibited at the Rusland Show every August. As might be expected in such a beautiful area, outdoor pursuits were well represented, these including cycling, fishing, shooting, walking, dog walking, horse riding, beekeeping, and photography.&lt;br />&lt;br />Indoor pastimes include reading, watching television and playing computer games. A Scottish country dancing group meet on Monday evenings in the parish room during the winter months, and there is a local rock band called ‘Cragg Atak’ that plays about five times a year in the village inn. Other musical events are held occasionally in the church, in the parish room, and around the village Christmas tree. There are a number of enthusiastic choral singers, and m usicians play such diverse instruments as church organ, piano, flute, cello, mandolin, drums, electric and classical guitars, electric keyboards, penny whistle, gourd, tambourine, triangle, chimes, maracas, cazoo and jug.   &lt;br />
Kevin Baverstock and Suzanne Tiplady</content>
</page></content></entry>