<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-17/GB-396000-171000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-39-17 GB-396000-171000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-17/GB-396000-171000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-39-17/GB-396000-171000-22.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-396000-171000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439761</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:54:59.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:54:59.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-396000-171000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Fynamore Primary School</title>
<content>

Fynamore primary school was opened in 2001 and now we have just been celebrating our 10th anniversary. &lt;br />&lt;br />At Fynamore there are about 400 children. We all have to wear Cadburys purple and golden yellow uniform. Our head mistress is called Mrs. Maddox and she has been at Fynamore ever since it was open! She is kind as well as being very good at organising exciting events like pop-corn night, the summer fate, fund raisers for the castle project and lots more.&lt;br />&lt;br />In 2009 we had our school extended. The builders knocked down all the old mobiles and replaced them with an amazing 7 classroom building. Ever since that happened we have had lots of things added to our school including our outdoor classroom, the year 5 and 6 peaceful place and a new area we haven’t named haven’t named. we got all the money from the CASTLE project which is from all the fund raisers we’ve done. The CASTLE project stands for Creating A St imulating Teaching Learning Environment. &lt;br />&lt;br />A couple of weeks ago the whole school celebrated our 10th anniversary by letting balloons of. Someone emailed the school and told them they had found a balloon in Surrey.   &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Maddy Goode</content>
</page></content></entry>