<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-35.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449721</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35Interview with Dr Mitchell</title>
<content>

We went to interview DR Mitchell and we found out that she worked Monday, Tuesday, Thursday and Friday in the Doctors which is a small place of work and sometimes she works some other days.  We were really surprised that she lives in Bristol and works in Timsbury. Before she came here she was training at the RUH and then got offered a job here. She's been working in Timsbury for 2 and a half years. Her patients are 0- 0ver 100 yea  rs old and she does surgery in the morning and in the afternoon, also she goes out to people's houses. Then we found out the best thing about her job was making people feeling better and happier. After that we found out the worst thing about her job was the worry and the thought of missing something. She lives by herself so she has no children and she's not married. She gets home late but gets a lot of company at the Doctors. When you see the Doctor all your medic record are on the computer. If a G P. sends a patient to the hospital doctors they write a letter to the Doctor. The doctor has to send an email or a letter to the doctor at the hospital to have a blood test and an x ray. &lt;br />
Imogen, Connor, Sami and Amber</content>
</page></content></entry>