<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-36-15 GB-364000-156000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-36-15/GB-364000-156000-25.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-364000-156000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449703</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2012-11-06T16:20:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:54.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-364000-156000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25Gardens</title>
<content>

We have 9 people that have small gardens, with lots of pretty flowers and benches and other things like that! Then 13 people had medium gardens, because you don't need much in your gardens to make it pretty. 2 people have large gardens to fit more stuff in it and make the houses look better.   Read on to find out what vegetables people grow in their gardens in the piece of writing by Lucien Wolf.&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />Equipment in the Garden.&lt;br />&lt;br />5 people had a washing line in their garden. 2 Gardens had green-houses to grow yummy tomatoes, and I'm guessing that the 2 gardens are the small gardens, but I could be wrong. 25 Gardens had sheds to keep all children's toys or the grass equipment. 1 garden has a workshop to build wood sculptures. 6 people have ponds which are good for fishes and to make gardens look very beautiful. 20 people have play equipment to bounce on a trampoline, climb on a climbing frame, swing on swing and enjoy the sunshine (or the rain!) 4 gardens have furniture so they could relax and watch children play on different toys and have a sleep ZZZZ! &lt;br />&lt;br />One Garden has a water feature to watch the water go into... maybe the pond? Sadly not many people have BBQ now to have nice food, pity! 1 person had a swimming pool! Awesome! Last but not least 1 person had a bird bath, so even the birdies can have a bath or swim.   &lt;br />
Amy</content>
</page></content></entry>