<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-31.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-31</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-31.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-31.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-31</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447097</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>31ATTITUDES OF LOCAL PEOPLE</title>
<content>

Spratton has a mix of ages and social groups. There are families with young children who have the facility of a pre- school play group and a primary school. The teenagers travel to a high school in a neighbouring village but they have little provision for their social needs as there is no longer a youth club. Many of them leave the village to seek employment in local towns. Working age villagers commute to towns including Daventry, Milton Keynes and London whilst enjoying the tranquillity of living a village life. Retired villagers who are still mobile have more time to enjoy the Country houses, historical sites and Gardens in and around our area. However villagers, who do not drive, have to rely on the local bus service, and this may be under threat from council cut backs.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a village general store, an excellent butcher's shop which attracts customers from far and near, a hairdresser and a new business offering beauty treatments as well as a pub in the village. This gives Spratton a great advantage over many other villages which only have a church.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a football team and sports club although they do not appeal to all groups. The pub should be the focal point for the whole area but many villagers do not use it and prefer to travel elsewhere. Generally, the residents of the 20th century housing do not get so much involved with the church or village societies but many support the sports/social club. Although many of the more affluent villagers from the traditional housing do get involved in many aspects of village life there are some villagers who are not involved at all.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many people in the area no longer enjoy shopping in the county town, Northampton, for a variety of reasons. They use the outlying retail parks but many prefer to travel to places such as Milton Keynes or Market Harborough for more specialised and luxury shopping and increasingly people buy onlin  e.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>