<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-28.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-28</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-28.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-28.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-28</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436841</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:07.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>28Development in Ravensthorpe since 1986</title>
<content>

There has not been the scale of development, which was seen in the late 1960s, 1970s and the early 1980s. The closure of the village school in 1962; its subsequent demolition; and the demolition of the former Baptist Chapel in the High Street paved the way for the construction of Church Gardens and Scott Close. There was also much development, or re-development, during this period along the Guilsborough Road, Church Hill, Teeton Road and the High Street. Paddock Close was built on land formerly belonging to The Old Vicarage. At the time of the 1961 census there were 315 people living in the parish of Ravensthorpe and Coton. By 1981 this figure had jumped to 546 people.&lt;br />&lt;br />However, the period since 1986 has still seen a steady drip of planning applications and developments.&lt;br />&lt;br />There appear to have been a number of applications in the late 1980s. This was probably not unconnected to the over-heated nature of the UK property market at the time, when housing seemed more like a cash accumulator than somewhere to live. The Secretary of State for the Environment from 1987-1989 was Nicholas Ridley, who was in favour of fewer planning controls and more development.&lt;br />&lt;br />New developments in Ravensthorpe at that period include the four houses in The Orchards (formerly the orchard at Manor Farmhouse) and the four houses built by Clayson Country Houses along the Guilsborough Road. These houses were all larger than average.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many villagers were concerned that the housing stock was becoming over dominated by 'executive' homes. Eventually, after a lot of patient hard work by members of the Parish Council, a development of 'affordable' housing was created at Diary Field, off the High Street. Six semi-detached homes were built in the mid-1990s and a further six were added in 2008.&lt;br />&lt;br />Other new houses which have appeared in the village in this period include the two semi-detached houses, built behind the Post Office, at the bottom of Little Lane (circa 1988). This site was formerly a builder's yard. &lt;br />&lt;br />Some of the new houses are linked in many villagers' minds with the magazine, 'The Raven', which came out four times a year from 1983 until 1994. Its editor, the late Robert Wornum, was wont to comment on planning matters quite forcefully. So, 'Two Hoots' (circa 1991) allegedly got its name as its owner's riposte to what he gave to other people's view on his house (in Church Hill, built on garden from the New Vicarage); and a new house in the High Street (circa 1988) remains known by many as 'The Blott'.&lt;br />&lt;br />Thorpe House Farm was built, behind the bus shelter in the High Street, in the mid 1990s; the surroundings of Halls Farm on the Guilsborough Road were re-development with two new houses and residential conversions of outbuildings; Lorna Jones had a new home built for herself in the garden of her former home on Teeton Road; and a thoughtfully-designed house was squeezed into a key spot opposite the Church in 2007.&lt;br />&lt;br />It should not be supposed that the Editor of 'The Raven' was purely anti-development. When news that The Chequers pub car park had been given the green light, he wrote that 'this development, when completed, should be welcomed by all in Chequers Lane and Paddock Close, as the growing popularity of The Chequers makes a car park even more essential than it was (Issue no. 33, Spring 1991). Only a few years previously, other pub landlords had applied (unsuccessfully) for permission to build a house on the land which became the pub car park.&lt;br />&lt;br />Another major new development at the end of the 1980s was the news that the village engineering business, Torquemeters, has outgrown its home in an old stone building in the High Street and was seeking to move to a new factory in the West Haddon Road. This caused much anxiety in the village, as many feared it would be the start of a number of industrial units. However, the new factory was built, emphatically described by the planners as a special case, and the business has gone from strength to strength.&lt;br />&lt;br />In recent years, with the national and international economy in some difficulty, the UK housing market has become less buoyant and it is noticeable that many villagers are now choosing to stay put and build extensions to their existing homes. Of course, this does mean that many of those 'large' houses built in the later decades of the twentieth century are now even bigger and their gardens that bit smaller. Perhaps it is not surprising that there is now a long waiting list for a village allotment.&lt;br />&lt;br />The 1990s also saw major efforts by certain villagers to secure some open spaces for long-term public enjoyment. The Pocket Park (Crabtree Pit) and Top Ardles Wood were respectively opened in 1999 and 2000. The villagers' debt of gratitude to the individuals who pushed these projects to fruition is an enormous one. &lt;br />&lt;br />Ravensthorpe is constantly evolving. For many of us who so value living here, we hope that change continues to be small-scale and in keeping with the beautiful surrounding landscape. But the planning system is constantly changing too and the messages coming from our current Coalition Government appear to be somewhat mixed with regard to development and control. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>