<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-29/GB-404000-291000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-29 GB-404000-291000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-29/GB-404000-291000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-29/GB-404000-291000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-404000-291000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449013</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:16.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:16.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-404000-291000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Diversity in Handsworth, Handworth Wood &amp; Perry Barr</title>
<content>

School pupils from Handsworth Wood Girls School took part in BBC School Report 2011. They looked at how the diversity of their area has changed over the last 25 years. &lt;br />&lt;br />Aashna one of the students involved summarises their findings:&lt;br />&lt;br />In order to find out how the diversity of Handsworth, Handsworth Wood and Perry Barr has changed over the last 25 years, students from Handsworth Wood Girls’ School met and interviewed several people from the community.&lt;br />&lt;br />One interviewee, Mr. Ashraf, has been a Governor at our school for 25 years. He says he has noticed a change in the overall ethnic population from predominantly African/Caribbean to Asian and he has seen the establishment of temples for Sikhs and Hindus.&lt;br />&lt;br />He explained how the area had become more multi-cultural in the last 25 years. &lt;br />&lt;br />Worshippers in churches have also changed. Interviewing Reverend Eve Pitts, she told us she had noticed a change from a mainly white congregation to a mixed congregation in her church. &lt;br />&lt;br />And at St. John’s Evangelist Church, Reverend Father Crispian noted that the closure of many factories, and changes to jobs in the area, had caused a change in the diversity of the local population and his congregation.&lt;br />&lt;br />From the interviews it showed how over time the areas population has became more diverse and multicultural. We feel this has had a positive effect with far more racial harmony and tolerance of other people’s beliefs and cultures. &lt;br />&lt;br />Some people did not like all the changes, but they liked the fact that today’s society in our area is multicultural. &lt;br />&lt;br />That diversity of the culture and the changes over the last 25 years is reflected in our school as well. There are many students who come from many different parts of the world. &lt;br />&lt;br />The changes of the last 25  years have made our area what it is today.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
School pupils from Handsworth Wood Girls School</content>
</page></content></entry>