<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-30.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-30</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-30.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-30.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-30</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447095</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>30ECOLOGY AND CONSERVATION</title>
<content>

The ecology of the area which contains Holdenby, Spratton and Teeton is typical of the Northamptonshire uplands with its fairly intense use of mixed arable and dairy land interspersed with spinnies long established for the Pytchley Hunt.  It does not provide a great variety of flora and fauna but some judicious observing and a little knowledge produces rewards in many areas.  In recent years there has been an increase in badgers and rabbits as evidenced by road kill and the continued expansion of the Buzzard population in the country is well in evidence in this part of the countryside with many breeding pairs and regular gatherings of high circling groups.  There are a number of areas which produce field voles and small mammals suitable for sustaining Kestrels and Barn Owls in reasonable numbers.  Barn Owls vary in their success rates and as with Kestrels they are not in strong numbers perhaps owing to the lack of suitable habitat for prey species.&lt;br />&lt;br />Rabbits continue to be a pest to many landowners although often when they reach large numbers they will be attacked with miximatosis and populations plummet.  Muntjac deer have been on the increase and become bolder though owing to the intense cultivation of much of the land they are perhaps not as numerous as some other parts of the country.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are a number of good bird recorders for the area and the BTO Bird Atlas is completing the latest survey countrywide from 2007 to 2011, the previous atlas being 1988 to 1991.   It is hoped that the results will show whether the steep decline in farmland birds in the area is continuing or whether the agri-environment measures such as the former Set-Aside and now the Entry Level and Higher Level Stewardship Schemes, have helped top halt the downward spiral.&lt;br />&lt;br />Farming practices cannot be blamed for the reduction in trees caused by disease.  For example the leaf minor causing damage to the Horse Chestnut  being the larvae of a moth, Cameraria ohridella from Europe, is rife throughout this transect as elsewhere and whilst to date it does not appear to kill the trees it will inevitably cause continuing weakness.  However the less common Phytophthora ramorum known as “sudden oak death” with liquid oozing from cracks in bark, does kill Horse Chestnuts and several other varieties of tree though happily it is not as common in this transect and rarely kills our native oaks.&lt;br />&lt;br />Opportunities to appreciate the ecology of the countryside in this transect is quite good, if patchy.  There are some very good footpaths, particularly around Holdenby and East Haddon but around Spratton there are none save for short local ones in and around the village.  However in 2011, owing to the generosity of one landowner, the first long footpath is to be created which runs from Spratton to Teeton.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>