<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-20 GB-452000-201000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-25.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-201000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435143</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:52:57.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:52:57.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>15</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25Games &amp; computers, 2011</title>
<content>

Games, 2011. We still play some of the games on the last Domesday like conkers, hop-scotch and off ground tig.&lt;br />&lt;br />For battle ships; you have a grid on paper a-f and 1-6. The other person has to do a grid and add crosses for a submarine, warship and then you have to guess where the other person's ships are and hit them.&lt;br />&lt;br />Freeze tag; there's an Itter and they have to try and hit everyone then you have to freeze and then the other people who aren't frozen can release you. The Itter has to hit another member of the game and that makes them become It and the other person not and it keep going like that until you've had enough.&lt;br />&lt;br />For rounders there are 2 teams. 1 team stands on the field, the other bats. You get 3 goes at batting. You have to get all the way round the bases. You are only allowed to run when the ball is in the air.&lt;br />&lt;br />Computers, 2011.  We thought of lots and lots of things which use computers. Lots of them wouldn't have been there in 1986. There are lots of computer parts in televisions, cameras and photo display boxes. Cameras mean you can take pictures of something exciting or brilliant. Wii games, DS games and X-boxes are all for games. Lots of everyday things have computers too; cars, clocks, mobile phones, MP3 players, DVDs, computers and lap-tops. Computers help with information and some have games. Lights which come on when it is dark without having to use a switch help us so we can see. Ovens have computers so you can cook your food properly when you are hungry.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Cowly Brownies, (URC), Oxford. July 2011.   </content>
</page></content></entry>