<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-30.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-30</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-30.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-30.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-30</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436839</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:48.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>30Industry in Ravensthorpe</title>
<content>

Torquemeters Ltd was founded in Ravensthorpe in 1951 by RD van Millingen, in a barn adjacent to the Post Office. Today the family owned Company employ 42 people in a purpose built factory on the outskirts of the village. The company's core products are torquemeters which accurately measure the power of rotating machines, sometimes at speeds up to 150,000rpm and up to powers of 100,000 HP. These can be used for R&amp;D of new machines, particularly components of jet engines, where improving efficiency is paramount, and also for monitoring the health of big turbines used in the oil, gas and petrochemical industries. &lt;br />&lt;br />More recently, they also design and make complete complex test systems, which embrace both mechanical, electrical and automation technologies for testing high speed machines. The company's workforce is all highly skilled, with over 10 graduate engineers engaged in design, and many skilled craftsmen in the manufacturing and testing area. &lt;br />&lt;br />The company's global reputation means that over 80% of the company's products are exported around the world, to countries such as USA, Europe, Russia, Japan and China and the Middle East.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>