<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-34.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-34</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-34.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-34.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-34</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449119</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>34MARGROVE PARK AND SLAPEWATH</title>
<content>

Margrove Park is one of the five residential areas in the block.  The terraced houses were built in the 19th century to house the ironstone miners working at the Stanghow Mine.  That area is now the caravan and camping site.  The above ground portions of the mine shafts can still be seen on the site.  The village green is well maintained, with flowerbeds, seats and trees.  There is a children’s play area in on the opposite side of the road from the Community Centre.  A woodland walk has been created through the belt of woodland on the west and north sides.&lt;br />&lt;br />The disused school became a heritage centre that was run by the Cleveland Community Forest, an organisation that no longer exists.  The buildings are still marked as a heritage centre on Ordnance Survey maps but are now used as the headquarters of the Tees Valley Wildlife Trust. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Trust has an area of land called Woodhill Meadows with a variety of habitats including a pond that is used for environmental education for visiting school children.&lt;br />&lt;br />The 1986 description of Slapewath is still accurate.  The inn is the Fox and Hounds.  It is especially busy serving food on Sunday lunchtimes.  It is often used for wedding receptions.  Slapewath is on the route of the Cleveland Way so it is also frequented by walkers.  The sites of the Spa Wood Mine and the Spa Mine are at Slapewath.  Drift mine entrances and the remains of the powder house can be seen in woodland.  The mine manager’s house has been renovated and is occupied again after being empty for a few years.  Guisborough and District Motorcycle club uses an area in the woods partially covered with shale from the ironstone mines for trials biking.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Stephen Larkin</content>
</page></content></entry>