<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-33.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447101</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:19.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>7</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33POPULATION OF THE AREA</title>
<content>

The Spratton Parish Electoral Roll has almost 1000 people listed; its population is estimated at around 1200 in approximately 460 houses, about 2.5 per household. Holdenby and Teeton are the only other conurbations within the area, having about 20 houses each (few smaller houses, so probably with a higher level of occupation), and then there are the outlying farms. So a population of around 1400 is speculated.&lt;br />&lt;br />The area encompasses a broad cross-section of socio-economic groups. In higher and middle management there are business owners medium and small, people based on the NHS hospitals, particularly Northampton General, and local surgeries; those based on the Agricultural College at Moulton; others based on the two schools in the village; those based on either local industry or professions; and those retired from positions within these two groups. It is not easy to identify, but there are almost certainly many in supervisory, sales and junior management roles. There are many skilled manual workers, some of these running their own business from their home address, as evidenced by the vans with their business name, particularly in Spratton. Farming now employs very few people, probably no more than twenty within the area, the main farms being based at Holdenby Mill, Brampton Hill, Holdenby North Lodge, Holdenby South Lodge, Holdenby House, Vicarage Farm and Tithe Farm (East Haddon) and Teeton Grange. In the largely arable nature (prevailing in 2011) of this business, which is now highly skilled, one man can farm up to 1000 acres with casual labour at harvest time. There are probably only relatively few semi-skilled and unskilled manual workers. In today’s tough economic climate there may be many unemployed and pensioners living on basic benefits, but this is difficult to ascertain.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>