<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-20 GB-452000-201000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-201000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435141</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:52:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:52:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Favourite games &amp; computers, 2011</title>
<content>

Games, 2011. Our favourite game at the moment is Jenga. Jenga has lots of small bricks we build in a tower. You have to try and pull them out one at a time and try not to knock the tower down.&lt;br />&lt;br />Other games we play are Twister, where you have to try and put your hands and feet on a colour and try not to fall down yourself. You get very tangled up.&lt;br />&lt;br />We still like to play games like Ludo and Monopoly. We don't play any of the other games that were mentioned in 1986 apart from skipping, off ground tip and bull-dog.&lt;br />&lt;br />Computers. We kept talking and talking about things we use which have computers in them.  Some are games and some are things we use all the time in our houses or outside. We made very long lists!&lt;br />&lt;br />We thought of i-phones, computers and laptops, ovens, microwaves, cameras and alarm clocks. We use TVs, X-boxes, Wii gmaes, DS, DVD players, MP3 players, CD players, radios playstations and mobile phones. Lots of these are for games. Satnavs tell use where to go when we are in the car. Motor bikes and cars (like the Mini which is made in Oxford) have lots of computers in them. Musical things like guitars and keyboards and even drums. We decided that everything which is electic at home probably has a computer in it.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Cowley Brownies (URC), Oxford. July 2011.   </content>
</page></content></entry>