<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-31.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-31</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-31.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-31.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-31</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439781</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:05.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:05.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>31Farming 2 at North Farm 2011</title>
<content>

The farm now has a contract with four neighbouring farms/ farmers to sow and harvest the crops. Oil seed rape is a more modern crop and widely sown in this area together with more traditional seeds eg wheat.All is totally arable now since 2005.&lt;br />&lt;br />The accompanying photograph is of stooks of wheat grown especially, with longer stems, for local thatching and nearby is someone who owns an old binder and threshing machine used to prepare these stooks.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is much heavy machinery but far fewer workers are required to maintain the business.&lt;br />&lt;br />The wooded area is still used and a hurdle maker manages it and cuts every seven years or so. This is a different man from the one mentioned in a previous entry for 2011 so hurdle makers are still vey much part of the country scene&lt;br />&lt;br />The entrance to the farm off the road has been re-aligned and widened to make it a safer access but the adjoining footpath still follows the old route.This was c ompleted about 15years ago.Dorset is very proud of its footpaths and many were reviewed to celebrate the Millennium in 2000.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is some caravan storage on site and someone lives there for security reasons.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are no children living at the farmhouse to use the local First and Middle Schools.&lt;br />&lt;br />In the mid 1980s the original Farmhouse had been sold and was about to open as a small hotel.The couple with their adult children made this into a very popular and luxurious hotel and it was very successful.&lt;br />&lt;br />The couple have now retired and yet again the property was sold privately.It now seems very rundown even derelict after a fire.Apparently, the family who own it may have children who attend the Upper School in the nearby market town.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett and Gillian Martin</content>
</page></content></entry>