<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-43/GB-428000-432000-16.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-42-43 GB-428000-432000-16</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-43/GB-428000-432000-16.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-43/GB-428000-432000-16.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-428000-432000-16</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>438685</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-30T13:48:05.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-30T13:48:05.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-428000-432000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>16A new description of Central Leeds</title>
<content>

The great thoroughfares of the Leeds town - Briggate, Kirkgate, are now closed during the day to vehicles, who are restricted to slipping in and out early in the day. The fleet of four wheel mountain ready vehicles are diverted aroud "The Loop", rarely disturbing the busy crowds of shoppers. Shopping Centres - covered 'malls' -  rise up every year or so surrounded by paved piazzas and bars for the daytime shoppers and panini and espresso hunting city office workers. By the river the industry - even the riverside Tetleys brewery - are bulldozed for prestige flats to house the young lawyers and finance executives that now live here, where a centrury ago workers dwelt. The great Leeds Kirkgate market continues its slow decline with the multi ethnic public wandering past stalls of yet another failed business, steel shuttered and empty. Around its perimeter a new Cash Converter (high risk loans, pawnbrokers) nestles in between gambling dens (called Amusement Arcades), pubs for serious drinkers, another tattoo parlour, and fast food outlets - Cantonese, Iranian, fish and chip. And, mysteriously, barbers shops. What I like most though is what I found here 36 years ago - strangers still talk kindly to each other when circumstance allows. I'll stay a while yet.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Mike Throssell</content>
</page></content></entry>