<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-363000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-44-36 GB-448000-363000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-363000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-363000-21.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-448000-363000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>414013</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-06-27T09:46:01.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-27T09:40:22.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-448000-363000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Pleasley, Religion - Churches</title>
<content>There are three churches in Pleasley. St Augustine's, St Barnabus and St Michael's. They are all Church of England. Generally people consider themselves to be Church of England and turn to the Church for marriage, baptism and funerals. There are around 72 people in Pleasley who have an active commitment to the churches. There are fundraising events, summer and autumn fayres, concerts, quizzes and harvest festivals. In St Augustine's Church, the Beavers, Cubs, Scouts, Rainbows and Brownies regularly meet.  The Methodist church was closed around 15 years ago. 45 parishioners regularly attend Church Services.&#xd;
&#xd;
HOMELIFE&#xd;
&#xd;
The original families spoken to in 1986 have not been located but in trying to find them it has been interesting to speak to some residents who have lived in Pleasley since that time.  Home life for the Mrs Smith that was interviewed consists of childminding for her two grand-children.  Taking them to play-school, feeding and entertaining them.  She mainly socialises with her family and small circle of friends, who meet for coffee and perhaps a drink in the local.  She likes watching TV and feels a strong sense of community with her neighbours.&#xd;
&#xd;
LEISURE AND ENTERTAINMENT&#xd;
&#xd;
The Woburn Centre that was reported on originally no longer exists.  There is a new Community Centre known as Landmark and this has been the cause of some controversy since being built, as it was sold a few years ago to a private concern in Mansfield Woodhouse who now runs it as a commercial business.  There is a coffee shop and regular keep fit (bums and tums) classes.  There is also a day nursery for children.  &#xd;
&#xd;
People still meet in the local public houses, the Swan and  Elm Tree for dominoes and darts and regular barbecues during the summer months.  The Plough Inn has been turned into a Chinese Restaurant.  There is also a Lakeside Fitness Club on the village square.&#xd;
&#xd;
SUPERNATURAL&#xd;
&#xd;
There was no-one who could comment on the ghostly apparitions which were reported in the original Station Cottage but since the closure of Pleasley Vale Cotton Mills by Coates Viyella in 1987, the building, originally built by William Hollins in 1785 has been included in the Most Haunted places to visit.  The site, although built in the most picturesque Derbyshire countryside, became derelict, but Bolsover District Council rescued it, and there are now historical tours and several thriving businesses in the area.&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
HOUSING&#xd;
&#xd;
The terraced houses built by William Hollins in 1889 to house over 500 workers on Pleasley Hill will be demolished imminently.  There is a lot of ill feeling regarding this turn of events, because the council owned properties have been used to house people with little regard for their upkeep and have been allowed to fall into the sorry state they are in now.  New housing will be put in their place, but locals worry that the same people will be allowed to live there and the same thing will happen again.  There are rows of terraces all around Pleasley and filming took place on Clarence Street and Hillmore Street in 2002 for an adaptation of  D H Lawrence's Sons and Lovers.  Housing is generally cheaper in this part of the country and a terraced house can be bought for around £70,000 - £40,000 less than the average.  Nevertheless, it is increasingly difficult for young people to get on the property ladder.  There is new up-market housing between Pleasley and New Houghton called the Willows.  New affordable housing will be built on Pleasley Hill together with commercial and council owned properties.  Farm land at the back of the houses has been sold to allow for a larger estate.&#xd;
&#xd;
FAMILY LIFE&#xd;
&#xd;
Family life in Pleasley is no different to anywhere else in the country, although many are unemployed - not finding employment after the mills and mines closed.&#xd;
&#xd;
Farmillo Primary School and Nursery takes children from 3 to 11 years.&#xd;
&#xd;
GAMES CHILDREN PLAY&#xd;
&#xd;
Children of primary school age play football and a game called 'Longstretch' which is a form of 'tig' one child is 'on' and has to tig as many as they can.  Girls still like skipping.  Outside school, cycling is still popular and boys reported they like to build dens.  Visiting the local shops for buying sweets is another favourite pastime.&#xd;
&#xd;
PRINCIPLE FEATURES &#xd;
&#xd;
The principle features of the area haven't changed much.  There is a new MARR road, Mansfield and Ashfield Regeneration Route which connects to Nottin  gham Road, and Sutton in Ashfield, taking traffic away from Mansfield Town Centre.  There is a new nursing home on the site of the old New England Public House.  The Meden Trail is still well used, and the Pleasley Colliery chimney which was mentioned in 1986 is still visible at Longhedge Lane and is currently being turned into a Mining Heritage Site.&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;
&#xd;

</content>
</page></content></entry>