<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-23.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447083</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:16.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:16.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23HISTORIC HOUSES</title>
<content>

Holdenby House was built in 1583 by Sir Christopher Hatton for Queen Elizabeth I.  Much of it has been pulled down and now it is approximately one eighth of its original size.  The present owners are James and Karen Lowther.  The House is open to the public regularly during the summer months, as is the 20 acre Grade One Listed garden.  Half of the estate of 2,000 acres is used for growing crops and much emphasis is placed on the preservation of the natural environment and conservation.  There is a flourishing Falconry Centre with a resident Falconer.  Some of the birds that can be seen are the Black Eagle, Lanner Falcon, European Eagle Owl and the Harris Hawk.&lt;br />&lt;br />The education department has grown in popularity over the last 30 years and now presents living history projects with costumed staff and visiting school pupils behaving as characters from, for example, the Victorian house or the Elizabethan period. The House is licensed for civil wedding ceremonies and both House and Garden can be booked for special occasions.  Concerts, parties, exhibitions, charity auctions, corporate meetings and small conferences are held.  It is also used occasionally by film and TV companies.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>