<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-19.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420615</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Leisure centers in Bestwood</title>
<content>

&lt;br />&lt;br />In Bestwood there are lots of Leisure activities like: Swimming, gyms, libraries, parks, and more to keep you occupied for the day.&lt;br />&lt;br />Swimming costs £2 normally however; if you have a city card it will only cost £1! There are diving boards, toys (like swimming floats and others) a little pool (for children if they don't want to go in the big pool although adults can go in too) and a big pool for all ages.&lt;br />&lt;br />A city card is a card that gets things cheaper for you. Like: bus fairs, for the swimming pool, to buy books, to give you a discount on your shopping and loads more!&lt;br />&lt;br />At the library you can sit and read a book or you can take books out of the library to borrow and then bring back when you have read it.&lt;br />&lt;br />Also if you don't have a computer at home you can go on the computers there.&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />If you want you can go to the gym and it will cost £26 a month. It keeps you fit and healthy. But remember to take a drink because you might get hot and thirsty.&lt;br />&lt;br />Not everybody spends their leisure time in Bestwood. We are really close to the city so it's only a short bus ride to do things like ice skating. When you go ice skating (in Nottingham city) it will cost about £6- £8. And if adults don't want to go on the ice they can sit at the side and watch or enjoy a delicious meal or cup of tea at the side of the ice rink.&lt;br />&lt;br />Some of the parks in Bestwood are:&lt;br />&lt;br />Queens Bower park (also known Bullifield), Chedisten, The ridge, Southglade park and Moswood. &lt;br />&lt;br />  &lt;br />&lt;br />So if you don't know what to do one day&lt;br />&lt;br />Then why don't you visit one of these Leisure activities?&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />By Nieeve&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Class 6 Glade Hill Primary</content>
</page></content></entry>