<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-33.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449121</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33CHARLTONS VILLAGE</title>
<content>

The village is usually known as Charltons.  This name is used on maps, road signs and by the district council and Post Office, but the name Charlton is sometimes used by local people such as the author of the 1986 description.  The Slapewath Mine (closer to what is now Charltons rather than to Slapewath with shafts on private land at Hollin Hill farm) was established by Thomas Charlton in 1864.  The houses built by his company from 1872 onwards were variously known as Charltons Cottages, Charltons Houses or Charltons Terrace, hence the name today.  After his death and the sale of the mine and houses his son, William Charlton, was the mine manager for the new owners, B. Samuelson &amp; Co.  &lt;br />&lt;br />There have been significant changes since 1986.  The Methodist Chapel has been closed and converted into a house as have many others in this area and elsewhere.  Many Post Offices were closed in 2009 including the one at Charltons, so the shop closed with it.  There are still grassed areas between the front row and the main road, but there is no longer a play area there.  Instead one was created in part of the grassed area behind the second row of houses.  In 2011 the play equipment was replaced by Redcar and Cleveland Council with modern equipment suitable for children of various ages and designed to encourage more of a sense of adventure than what went before.  The new play area was opened officially on 21st August 2011.  Part of the grassed area near the Community centre has been recently planted with fruit trees as a community orchard.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Stephen Larkin</content>
</page></content></entry>