<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-32.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-32</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-32.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-32.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-32</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436843</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:48.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:08.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>32Ravensthorpe Village Hall</title>
<content>Ravensthorpe village hall was built in 1912 on land given to the village by Louisa and Isabella Langton and Stephen Chillizzi. The deeds were handed to the Reverend C Brook who was to raise a committee to deal with the building of the hall. It was originally called the Parish Room and was used mainly by the men of the parish as a social club where they would meet in the evenings to chat and read the paper.&lt;br />&lt;br />The hall is a valuable village asset and will be 100 years old on 30th March 2012 and is shortly to be refurbished at a cost of approximately 75,000 pounds. The money has been raised by the village through many fund raising events and also by donation. This work has taken place after the village voted for the hall to be updated rather than rebuilt in another area of the village. The porch and hall will be replaced and the outside of the majority of the hall rendered, the stage taken out to make the hall longer and the kitchen extended. The inside of the hall is to be redecorated and the new lights and blinds fitted. Work is due to start on 9th May 2011. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>