<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-24.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436835</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24Transport in and around Ravensthorpe</title>
<content>

Many people in Ravensthorpe travel for business and pleasure by car as local employment centres such as Northampton, Rugby, Harborough and Daventry are over 9 miles away.&lt;br />&lt;br />Fuel prices have risen continuously over the past number of years. The cheapest local prices currently stand as follows in April:&lt;br />&lt;br />Diesel between 138.9 to 142.9 pence per litre&lt;br />&lt;br />Unleaded between 130.9 to 136.9 pence per litre&lt;br />&lt;br />LPG 75.9 pence per litre (available from 2 garages within 10 miles radius)&lt;br />&lt;br />There are two local fuel stations in West Haddon and Long Buckby, the next nearest stations are in Kislingbury and Duston on the edge of Northampton. Most supermarkets in the local towns have associated fuel stations.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />The rural roads around the village are in a bad condition with many pot holes, bumps, hollows and deteriorating edges.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many years ago families would cycle around the village for leisure but the speed at which cars can go and people will drive is a major off putting factor.&lt;br />&lt;br />There has been a bus service stopping in the village for many decades. The current service is a regular direct bus to the Drapery in Northampton taking approx. 30 minutes. The stagecoach bus 96 collects from Ravensthorpe High Street at 0754, 1004, 1204 and 1403. There are a few more buses going to Northampton but these require a change at Long Buckby and take approx 1 hour 16 minutes.&lt;br />&lt;br />To get to Daventry from Ravensthorpe there is a change at St. James End Square and the journey takes approx. 1 hour 20 minutes.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are recent concerns over the future of the bus service. The current service is subsidised by the local authority but with recent austerity measures taking place in the public sector following the recession, this is one of many public services that is likely to change in the future. Other bus routes in the County have or will soon be withdrawn or are being revised and altered. It appears from the County Council website that nothing is planned to change for our service. Responsibility for administrating the Concessionary Bus Pass recently passed to the County Council from Daventry District Council, there is also less money being received centrally for providing this service resulting in reduction in permitted travelling times.&lt;br />&lt;br />One or two villagers commute by bicycle but it's hard to get a precise number.&lt;br />&lt;br />The village is also served by the Daventry Area Community Transport (DACT). DACT is a registered charity established in 1993 to provide community transport services within Daventry District area. They provide a variety of transport and mobility services such as a car scheme and minibus scheme. There are 115 volunteer car drivers that assist anyone who has difficulty using public transport to get to any medical appointments. There are over 40  volunteer minibus drivers and 7 coach built minibuses to take community groups on a wide variety of trips.&lt;br />&lt;br />The nearest train stations are at Long Buckby (4 miles), Northampton (9 miles) and Market Harborough (14 miles). The nearest is Long Buckby station which is on the London Euston to Birmingham New Street line, also stopping at Northampton. The station is a field length away from the edge of the village. Car parking is free but is well used as it is hard to find a place after 7.30am. Bollards have placed onto the Highway verge to stop station users parking on the roadside. There is a small ticket hut which is mostly manned in the mornings only and a couple of outside ticket machines. Tickets can also be purchased online in advance, then posted or collected from these machines. There are no other facilities such as toilets, waiting rooms or cafe. &lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>