<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-40.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-40</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-40.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-40.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-40</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447467</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-28T18:00:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-26T14:41:30.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>40RURAL ARTS AND CRAFTS</title>
<content>

Whilst rural arts and crafts are not practised to the extent they were previously, there has been a revival of interest in such activities in Spratton, as elsewhere.  There is a working thatcher in the village, who also lectures on his subject at a local thatching school, which is the only one left in the country.  A very few ladies continue the village tradition of bobbin lacemaking, purely as a hobby.  Knitting, patchwork and quilting, soft toy making and bead jewellery making are also pursued by individuals and introduced at the village primary school during special activity events.  Local ladies continue to decorate the parish church with flower arrangements for the regular services and festivals and many of the flowers and greenery are provided from their own gardens.&lt;br />&lt;br />The W.I. has always encouraged baking, bread making and preserving and these categories are well represented at the annual produce and craft show in the village hall. There is a thriving allotment association, which organises the show, and there is healthy competition for the prizes in the produce section.  Several people keep chickens on their allotment or in their back gardens.  There are also categories in the annual show for art, needlecraft and photography.  Indeed, there is now a thriving and very well-supported photography club in the village.&lt;br />&lt;br />Understandably many of the above activities are pursued mainly by the older and retired residents in the village, who have more time and opportunity to pursue traditional crafts.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>