<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-36/GB-496000-369000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-49-36 GB-496000-369000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-36/GB-496000-369000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-36/GB-496000-369000-21.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-496000-369000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412205</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:09.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T11:47:02.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-496000-369000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21A River Journey</title>
<content>

Heading  east  along  the  River  Witham from Brayford Pool, the journey takes  you  through  the centre of the city. The  Brayford  narrows into  the Witham  outside  the Odeon Cinema at the end of a long row of restaurants, hotels and pubs. You then pass  under  Wigford  Way which links vehicular and pedestrian traffic to the roads exiting West out of the city and east through the City Centre.  Travelling through the Glory  Hole, you reach High  Bridge which supports a coffee house and several shops such as a Clarks shoe shop and a mobile phone store.&lt;br />&lt;br />You then emerge between the Waterside Shopping Centre on the northern bank and the Wilkinson's homewares store on the southern bank.  The Waterside Shopping Centre contains 3 floors of stores such as The Perfume Shop, New Look, The Early Learning Centre and Primark.  The Wilkinson's store faces onto City Square, where regular seasonal events such as a Winter Ice Rink, regular fa irground rides and a fortnightly Farmer's Market.  On the Northern side of the bank, the Waterside Shopping Centre ends and then you have the Witch and The Wardrobe pub, a modern restaurant building which has housed several asian and italian restaurants and then The Green Dragon public house, behind which the new Thorgate House apartment complex sits.&lt;br />&lt;br />You then pass under Thorn Bridge over which runs Broadgate, one the main arterial routes leading north and south through the city.  This brings you into the industrial centre with Siemens Engineering dominating the majority of the length of the southern bank and the Environment Agency building and Stamp End tower block dominating the northern bank.&lt;br />&lt;br />The final buildings you come to are the old Titanic works on the southern bank, which now house Anglian Water, Lincolnshire County Council offices and Lincs FM.  Within a few hundred yards, you return to countryside.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Mr Adam Clarke
</content>
</page></content></entry>