<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-460000-267000-1.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-460000-267000-1</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-460000-267000-1.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-460000-267000-1.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-460000-267000-1</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435113</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T16:38:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T16:38:50.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-460000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>01Shops and Businesses</title>
<content>

When I moved to Long Buckby in 1994 The Market Square looked much the same as it did the photo from 1986. The Market Square was redeveloped some years ago with the old toilet being demolished to make way for more parking and a new one being built on the main road. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Pizza Shop next to the Pharmacy was a small craft shop. The Jewellery Shop has been a Nearly New and Second Hand children's clothing shop and then Wilton Fabrics. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Stove Shop next to the Post Office was a Haberdashery and then became the Pet Shop. The Pet Shop used to be on Church St. next to the Vets. The unit that housed the Pet Shop became a Bargain Shop for a while and was then bought buy the Voujon (Indian Restaurant) and incorporated as part of the restaurant. The Voujon was called the India Village back in 1994. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Village Garden on the corner of the Market Square used to be The Nags Head. It then became a restaurant and bar called The Cobblers for a few years before becoming the Village Garden (Indian Restaurant). The entry door to the Village Garden on Station Rd. used to be the door to the Countryside Estate Agents. That unit was bought by the Village Garden and incorporated into the restaurant.&lt;br />&lt;br />Jackson Grundy Estate Agents used to be the Village Estate Agents.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Goa on the High St. used to be a Recruitment Agency.&lt;br />&lt;br />Baileys (the ironmongers) on the High St. closed at the start of the year. It supplied the DIY, TV and kitchen needs of the village for many years. Along with the newsagents (before it changed hands a few years ago) it was one of very few shops that did not use a conventional till, but just a wooden drawer for storing cash taken for purchases.&lt;br />&lt;br />Cuisine 15 has been a food establishment for many years. It was a restaurant before that and before that it was known as the Antique Coffee Pot and was a cafe. &lt;br />&lt;br />Verdi's Sandwich shop was a  hairdresser's before becoming Verdi?s.&lt;br />&lt;br />New Housing Developments&lt;br />&lt;br />There has been some new housing development in Long Buckby since 1986. Floyers Farm behind Princes Park and next to the Junior School and sports field has been built. The main road through there is called Wright Rd. There are about 50 houses on 5 acres.&lt;br />&lt;br />Clover Rise off East St. is a small cul-de-sac of about 10 houses. &lt;br />&lt;br />The site of the old belt factory next to the recreation ground was developed as Cooks Way. The building on Station Road has the same roof line as the old belt factory.&lt;br />&lt;br />Rockhill Road has been properly tarmacced.&lt;br />&lt;br />The disused factory site behind the Co-Op car park has one new house on it. One of the planning conditions was that the little access road was tarmacced when the build was completed. It has been and the pavement has been improved as well.&lt;br />&lt;br />The waste ground between the back of The Poplars and Long Buckby Castl  e was developed a few years ago. About half a dozen executive style homes were built.&lt;br />&lt;br />There have been other pockets of in-fill development throughout Long Buckby.&lt;br />&lt;br />Schools and Pre-schools in Long Buckby&lt;br />&lt;br />Long Buckby has an Infant School housed in the Victorian school building on the High St.. The Junior School is housed in a more modern purpose built school building on South Close. The children of secondary school age are bused to Guilsborough Secondary School.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is community pre-school that runs in the upstairs room of the Baptist Church on the Market Square.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a private nursery that runs in premises on the High St.&lt;br />&lt;br />Mums and Tots runs on a Monday in the Community Centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />Leisure Facilities and Activities in Long Buckby&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a Community Centre that has a wide variety of activities running. From Bowling and Blood Donor sessions to Weight Watchers and Yoga for Pregnancy.&lt;br />There are Brownie, Guide, Cub and Scout groups running in the village. &lt;br />&lt;br />A Youth Club that runs in a building on the edge of the Sports Field.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Sports Field is home to the Football, Rugby and Cricket Clubs. Part of the sports field has been set aside for the use of the Junior School, so they have access to a large area for athletics and games.&lt;br />&lt;br />The swimming pool at the Junior School is no longer is use, because it became too expensive to maintain and run. &lt;br />&lt;br />The United Reformed Church has a large hall available for hire with a badminton court marked out and ceiling high enough to play.&lt;br />&lt;br />St. Lawrence?s School Rooms are also available for hire and fairly large venue.&lt;br />&lt;br />Religion in Long Buckby&lt;br />&lt;br />The main parish church on Church St. is St Lawrence?s. There is currently a vicar.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Baptist Church on the Market Square is currently between Pastors.&lt;br />&lt;br />The United Reformed Church in Br  ington Rd. has a Rector.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Catholic Church on the edge of the village is operated as a satellite church from the Catholic Church in Daventry.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is currently no Mosque, Synagogue, Gurdwara or Temple.&lt;br />&lt;br />Long Buckby Castle&lt;br />&lt;br />Long Buckby Castle is a grassy castle mound situated behind the Poplars and the new houses. From the top of it you can see into the back garden of the Old Vicarage and down to the back of Jubilee Close. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>