<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436833</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>7</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Ravensthorpe Allotments</title>
<content>

The allotments are owned by the Parish Council and rented out to plot holders. They in Ravensthorpe are situated next to graveyard. The land is L shaped and has a public footpath running though it from Church Gardens to The Hollows. &lt;br />&lt;br />Up until 2000 only 7 plots where available for rent and not all of them where fully cultivated. The rest of the land had become very overgrown with perennial weeds and Ash tree saplings. The area was really a bit of eye sore. At the request of a keen gardener three additional plots where made available 2000. &lt;br />&lt;br />The interest in Grow Your Own has really expanded in the last few years helped by the BBC gardening programs and as people become concerned about health and their carbon foot print. In 2008/9 the rest of the land was cleared so that we now have 13 plots. In addition, running water has been made available for the allotment holders through a Green Infrastructure Grant Scheme administered by River Nene Regional Park, making life easier for the allotment holders.&lt;br />&lt;br />Today the allotments are used by enthusiastic group of amateur gardeners who are passionate about growing and eating all sorts of fresh vegetables and fruit. Even grapes are grown on some of the plots to make Ravensthorpe Wine. &lt;br />&lt;br />The allotment holders who look after and fully utilised the land, have ensured by this action that the allotments are now seen by villagers as a valued green resource within the village. The footpath is regularly used and this adds to the social side as walkers come and talk to you when youre working on the allotment. There is now a waiting list as new garden enthusiasts want the chance to join in the fun of growing your own food.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>