<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-43-34/GB-436000-348000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-43-34 GB-436000-348000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-43-34/GB-436000-348000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-43-34/GB-436000-348000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-436000-348000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449731</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-03T17:32:56.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-436000-348000</dblock_id>
<original_item>15</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Ripley Morris Men.</title>
<content>

Ripley Morris Men were founded in 1924 as part of the Ripley branch of the English Folk Dance and Song Society. The Ripley branch flourished in the pre-war years and often hosted Derbyshire wide events, and performed at the Albert Hall in London. In 1952 the Morris side danced at the meeting of the Morris Ring in Tideswell. In the mid 1950's the morris side folded, but it was revised by Brian Rose and Keith Giddens in 1981. One of the original men from the 1950's side, Sam Taylor, danced again with Ripley, and Herbert Hunt from the old side gave advice. Since then Ripley Morris have performed continuously around the area,  often accompanied by their Fool ,Unicorn, Hobbyhorse, Green Man and Molly ,dancing every Thursday night in the summer, as well as at other times such as Easter, Boxing Day, and  New Years Day. They have danced in most parts of England and Wales, and in France, Germany and Denmark. They have hosted national meetings of the Morris Ring at Ripley  and twice at Ashover, and have attended such meetings annually .They regularly perform at such prestigious events  as Derby Beer Festival, have appeared on television in various programmes ( e g  The Michael Ball Show, The Rainbow) and at the Sidmouth International Folk Festival, and at the Whitby Folk Festival (twice). They have danced in front of the Queen and Prince Phillip, and 20,000 others, at Pride Park Derby for the Queen’s Jubilee. They perform Cotswold style morris dances, and perform a number of dances that they have written themselve; in a style they call Lower Baldby. Every Christmas they perform a Guisers play, ( a traditional play taught to them by Percy Cook of  Hammersmith in Ripley when he was 90), around the Ripley and Selston areas , about 40 performances each year, collecting for Ripley Hospital League of Friends, and have donated well over £20,000 to the Friends over the years, thanks to the generosity of local pub and club landlords and their customers.   &lt;br />
Graham Clarke 2011</content>
</page></content></entry>