<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-26.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449109</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:24.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26COMMUNITY</title>
<content>

The 1986 description of community life is still true for many residents, although others are less involved with the affairs of their neighbours.  The community working together was very evident at Charltons in the winter of 2010-11 when there was snow on the ground for many weeks and neighbours helped each other to clear snow, grit the roads and pavements and get cars out.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Post Office and shop closed in 2009.&lt;br />&lt;br />One aspect of community life did not exist in 1986.  Margrove Park and Charltons are included in East Cleveland Online, a digital villages project.  Margrove Park has an extensive website with information about the village today, its history and news of events.  Charltons has a less active Community Centre website, but has a Facebook page to promote events and to share photographs afterwards.  Charltons Heritage Hunt has a website for results of research on the history of the village and for reminiscences. Under the UK Online scheme there are opportunities for residents to learn to use computers and the Internet in the community centre. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>