<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-25.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447081</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:15.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25COMMUNICATIONS - GENERAL</title>
<content>

Within easy reach of Northampton, both Holdenby and Spratton have good road communications and have a bus service operating daily. Although neither are served by a Post Office, that at Creaton is nearby. The local authority provides a coach service for the elderly.&lt;br />&lt;br />Local and national radio and TV services are accessible throughout. A few residents subscribe to satellite channels.&lt;br />&lt;br />National and local newspapers are available at Spratton Village Stores. Spratton has an active Parish Newsletter usually published quarterly. These, together with flyers placed in the Stores, Local Radio announcements and road-side notices offer advance notice of local events as well as promotional opportunities s for neighbourhood businesses.&lt;br />&lt;br />The telephone service through land-lines is available on demand while coverage for most mobile networks is of average quality with varying strength of reception. For Broadband the whole area is supplied by copper cable laid considerable distances from the exchanges, that for Holdenby being at  East Haddon and Spratton at Chapel Brampton This results in extremely poor access speeds (from 0.5 to 2.0 Mbps) and considerable disadvantage. British Telecom has indicated that the Chapel Brampton exchange will be up-graded with fibre to the cabinet in 2012.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>