<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-25.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436831</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25A sporty family</title>
<content>

We are a sporty family living in Ravensthorpe. Mum and Dad do lots of mountain biking and road biking. Daddy often bikes to work instead of driving his car. &lt;br />&lt;br />Mum and Dad also sail at Pitsford Reservoir which is in a village called Brixworth.&lt;br />&lt;br />Mum sometimes runs around the Ravensthorpe Reservoir. She has a very read face when she gets back. I take part in lots of sports including swimming, gymnastics, rugby and riding my bike.I go gymnastics and swimming at Market Harborough Leisure Centre. I am currently working towards Badge 4 in gymnastic and can swim 5 metres by myself. I play rugby on a Sunday morning for Long Buckby Lions. Next year I will be able to play in matches both in Long Buckby and other villages.&lt;br />&lt;br />My sister also swims at Market Harborough Leisure Centre. She also does ballet on a Tuesday afternoon in Ravensthorpe village hall.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are lots of opportunities to take part in sport at my school. We can do basketball, football, golf and cross country running.&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />Jack aged 9:&lt;br />&lt;br />I go to Harlestone Golf Club. I do lessons with a man called Nick Soto. I play football and basketball at school with my friends. &lt;br />&lt;br />At school each year group key stage 1 and key stage 2 have a box with equipment; our Head Teacher calls it huff and puff. I like playing in the tennis court with my elder brother Harry. At the park I like to play football with Harry's friends. We don't have any football or rugby teams in the village.&lt;br />&lt;br />Harry aged 11:&lt;br />&lt;br />I go to Guilsborough Secondary School and in PE we do lots of different sports like rugby, hockey, football, badminton and tennis. At my school we have lots of opportunities to do sport like rugby on a Thursday lunch time. At the weekend me and my family go down to our nearby tennis court and we go down to the park and play football and basketball. In my village we have no football or rugby teams. &lt;br />&lt;br />Emily aged 12:&lt;br />&lt;br />My name's Emily; I'm 12 and I go to Guilsborough Secondary. I used to take part in the hockey and netball clubs but as horses take up most of my time, I had to quit. However, there are many other sports at my school, including gymnastics, trampolining, dance, HRE (health related exercises) badminton, rugby, tennis, basketball and football. I've lived in Ravensthorpe all my life and living in the countryside is great. There's a tennis court in my village that my friends and I can play in if we have permission. There's also a playing field; I don't think people hold football there anymore but the younger kids usually go there for a kick about with their mates. My nanny and grandpa live on a farm so I have grown up around horses and animals. I have two horses and my mum also has a horse so I can ride after school and at weekends and I love to.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>