<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-29.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-29</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-29.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-29.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-29</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436937</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:48.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-19T11:04:18.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>29Ravensthorpe Nursery</title>
<content>We started Ravensthorpe Nursery in 1986 with just over three acres of land, part of which was planted with strawberries and raspberries. There was also a polytunnel and we brought some young plants with us.&lt;br />&lt;br />For the first few years whilst the business and our children grew it did not earn us a living and Richard had to retain a full time and then a part time job. &lt;br />&lt;br />Gradually as the plant stock grew we were able to build a glasshouse and more tunnels, adding bedding plants, vegetables and cut flowers to our produce. Escalating fuel costs and increased competition from large bedding growers led us to turn increasingly to hardy stock, to the point where now we grow between two and three thousand different varieties. &lt;br />&lt;br />Visitors can see what our plants look like in a garden setting in our large display garden and we love sharing its delights, as well as raising funds for the National Gardens Scheme and village amenities.&lt;br />&lt;br />During our 25 years we have seen the industry change and many smaller, family run nurseries disappear. If we want a particular plant to sell, we have to grow it ourselves, as there is often no wholesaler to buy it from.&lt;br />&lt;br />We have no staff, but in recent years more mechanisation has helped, particularly our compost mixer and Manitou, which is a cross between a tractor and a fork lift truck, and these are invaluable in saving a great deal of hard, physical work. We have a computerised watering system, so though we still have to use hoses for hand watering, the irrigation system saves hours of work and means we can get away from the nursery for the odd day. At last we now have a ride-on mower which is a great time and leg saver. Richard must have walked miles over the years! &lt;br />&lt;br />What a difference power-tools have made too, from cordless screwdrivers and drills to power saws, trimmers and lawn edgers. The internet has made a huge difference to the way people use us and has led to increased business, including mail order. &lt;br />&lt;br />We could not manage without using pesticides and weed killers, but these are very strictly regulated and are too costly to use thoughtlessly. Our other great enemy is the wind on our exposed site. Our first tunnel was squashed flat in ten minutes when it was only a week old. We were glad when we could replace the tunnels with a large, second-hand greenhouse, which we moved from a redundant nursery. As well as being more wind-resistant, it provides a much better growing environment, avoiding the rapid temperatures changes and lack of ventilation in polytunnels.&lt;br />&lt;br />Ravensthorpe is a beautiful place to live and we are so lucky to be able to spend our working lives here too.   &lt;br />&lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>