<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-10/GB-468000-105000-28.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-10 GB-468000-105000-28</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-10/GB-468000-105000-28.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-10/GB-468000-105000-28.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-105000-28</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420795</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-12T14:47:46.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-12T14:47:46.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-105000</dblock_id>
<original_item>6</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>28The Spring Heritage Centre</title>
<content>

Since 1986 the Arts Centre has been through a number of changes. It is now called The Spring Heritage Centre, it houses the museum, plays are performed there and lots of clubs are available. The museum itself  was opened in 1979. Approx 230 people visit the museum each week, they tend to stay between 5 and 30 minutes. We found evidence of people visiting from Sussex, Portsmouth, Emsworth and West Leigh.&lt;br />&lt;br />People tend to visit in the holidays especially during the Christmas break.&lt;br />&lt;br />The most popular exhibits are The Leigh Park kitchen although the staff liked the clock from St Faith's Church. The special exhibitions change every 2-3 months and this is done via the museum services in Winchester.&lt;br />&lt;br />Plays are performed in the theatre. The theatre has 134 seats, often shows are sold out. The average price to see a play is £7 - £10. The most popular show this year was I Elizabeth. There are on average 86 different shows a year.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are 13 staff working in the Heritage centre, some of these work in the popular café. In 1986 the café was vegetarian, now it serves home cooked food.&lt;br />&lt;br />The centre is home to 7 weekly children's clubs, The most popular of these is Rock School. Children from 5-19 can attend these clubs, There are also lots of adult clubs.&lt;br />&lt;br />The longest running activity is the drama group Act One. &lt;br />&lt;br />In addition to all this the Centre has about 6 open days a year which are always hugely popular. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
5B Bosmere Junior School</content>
</page></content></entry>