<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-22.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436019</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T10:40:27.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T10:40:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Stanbridge Mill</title>
<content>

Stanbridge Mill is an historic building which has changed in the twenty five years since 1986, with different owners. It was bought in 1990 and not occupied until 1993. The glass floor was removed by the present owner who mainly lives in Australia but stays here for 4 -5 months each year. Note the weather vane showing a kangaroo. The water wheel still works but cannot be seen from the house above.&lt;br />&lt;br />A male Head Gardener has been employed to manage the gardens which occupy three acres of the fifty acre property. At this time it was decided to open the garden once a year, in early June, for the National Garden Scheme. Also, private visits could be arranged, all proceeds going to charities. He had some help from other staff. On his retirement an female under - gardener was promoted and is fully responsible with one other young woman.The area is devoted to wildlife now with a hide beside the River Allen.There are only Dorset Horn sheep, used to keep down the grass and looked after by a non - resident shepherd. The fleeces go to local spinners or the Wool Board.&lt;br />&lt;br />Cottages on the property are occupied by the gardener, the house-keeper and a chef who take on additional tasks while the owner is abroad.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett and Gillian Martin</content>
</page></content></entry>