<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-28.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-28</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-28.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-28.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-28</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439769</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:02.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:02.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>28Tourism and Historic Inn</title>
<content>

The current managers, young and of only two weeks into their posts, read the original entry in 1986 and were surprised that much written then is still true in 2011.&lt;br />&lt;br />The big change is that there is no link to the Shaftesbury Estates and that Marstons the Brewers from Burton on Trent, who bought out Ringwood Brewery, now own the Horton Inn.This means it is a managed house and part of a large chain of public houses and inns.&lt;br />&lt;br />Horton Inn now has seven ensuite bedrooms and WiFi is available.There are two bars and restaurants.There are meal promotions as in curry and steak nights with a carvery on Sundays.&lt;br />&lt;br />The managers agree that there is still difficulty with recruiting staff due to the isolated situation of the inn. Although on a cross roads, the nearest villages are still some distance away and own transport is still essential.Trade is local, including combine harvester drivers after hours, and passing holiday trade.&lt;br />&lt;br />The go od news is that the post box on the wall is still very much in use today and regularly emptied.&lt;br />&lt;br />The cottages opposite are still lived in, possibly by different families and the owners probably work away from the immediate area.&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett and Gillian Martin</content>
</page></content></entry>