<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449095</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-09T18:20:08.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">

<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>

<original_item>17</original_item>

<year>2011</year>

<title>21GOVERNMENT OF THE AREA</title>

<content>



Since 1999 elections to the European Parliament have used a proportional representation system, so the area is now part of a much larger constituency. Three MEPs were elected for the North-East of England in 2009, one from each of the three largest parties.  These are Stephen Hughes (Labour), Martin Callanan (Conservative) and Fiona Hall (Liberal Democrats).&lt;br />&lt;br />In the UK Parliamentary election of 2010 Tom Blenkinsop (Labour) was elected for the Middlesbrough and South East Cleveland constituency, following the death of the previous Labour MP, Ashok Kumar, shortly before the election.  Tom has often visited Charltons for events in the Community Centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />Cleveland County Council was created in 1974 and abolished in 1996, with its boroughs becoming unitary authorities.&lt;br />&lt;br />The District Council in 1986 was Langbaurgh Borough Council, named after the ancient wapentake (a group of parishes) of North Yorkshire of the same name.  It became a unitary authority when Cleveland County Council was abolished in 1996 and was renamed Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council.  The council is responsible for most of the services affecting the everyday lives of residents such as schools, roads, supporting public transport, waste collection and recycling.  The 2011 election gave the Labour party 32 of the 59 councillors.&lt;br />&lt;br />Most of the area is in the Westworth Ward where the current councillors, re-elected in 2011 are Dave Williams (Labour) and Carole Jeffery (Conservative).  Dave had been elected for the ward as a member of the East Cleveland Independents but transferred to Labour in 2010.  Carole is one of only 6 Conservatives on the Council. Both are regularly seen at Charltons events.  Stanghow is in the Lockwood ward and the councillor is Steve Kay (East Cleveland Independent).&lt;br />&lt;br />The lowest level of government is the parish council, in this case Lockwood Parish C  ouncil.  As with most of the parish councils in Redcar and Cleveland there was no election in 2011 because the number of nominations was not more than the number of seats available, 12.  There are two councillors for the area of Margrove Park and Charltons.  Five councillors cover Lingdale (to the north of this block) and Stanghow.&lt;br />&lt;br />The area south of the A171 is also in the North York Moors National Park.  The National Park Authority is responsible for planning and some other aspects of governance of the area.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />

Stephen Larkin</content>

</page></content></entry>