<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-19 GB-452000-195000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-19.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-195000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412677</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-15T14:47:46.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-15T14:47:46.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-195000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Joint European Torus - JET</title>
<content>

Although originally planned to run for only twelve years, JET is still operating twenty eight years later. When the JET Joint Undertaking eventually came to an end in 1999 the project evolved into a European user facility, EFDA-JET, the flagship fusion facility of the European Fusion Development Agreement. JET’s scientific programme is co-ordinated by EFDA and the facilities are maintained and operated by CCFE (Culham Centre for Fusion Energy as the Culham Laboratory is now known) on behalf of the European fusion research community.&lt;br />&lt;br />JET remains the world’s largest fusion device and not only achieved the world’s first controlled release of fusion power in 1991, but also still holds the world record for the amount of fusion power produced: 16 megawatts.  Having achieved, and indeed surpassed, its original goals, JET has moved into an era of dedicated experiments in support of ITER, an international fusion project currently being built in the south of France. Building on JET’s success, this project aims to prove the scientific and technical feasibility of a fusion-powered power plant.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>