<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-18.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-18</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-18.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-18.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-18</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420617</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>18Films in 2011</title>
<content>

By Chrystal Smiley&lt;br />&lt;br />Over the years the cinema has been popular and still is but now the tickets  prices have been raised. The tickets for adults are for £8.10 children’s tickets cost £5.50 and senior citizen tickets cost £5.50 as well. If you are watching a 3D film 1 adult costs £2.10 extra and 1 child cost £1.50 on top of ticket price and 80p for glasses.&lt;br />&lt;br /> I did a survey in my class with Rachel to see what movie children liked the choices were out of Kung fu panda 2, Pirates of the Caribbean stranger tides, Wild child, Paul, Diary of a wimpy kid, Are we there yet?, Rio, Avatar and Tangled. The one that was the most popular was Paul and Miss Gibson chose Avatar.&lt;br />&lt;br />The movies in the cinema today are called Senna, Bad teacher, Bridesmaids, Diary of a wimpy kid Rodrick rules, Green lantern, Hangover part 2, Kung fu panda 2, X-men first class, &lt;br />&lt;br />Pirates of the Caribbean stranger tides and The merry wives of Windsor. The top 5 uk box office were green lantern witch was 1st,Kung fu panda 2 was 2nd,Bad teacher was 3rd,Hangover part 2 was 4th and X-men first class is 5th.&lt;br />&lt;br />If you go to the cinema you can choose to watch a 2D film or a 3D film. The 2D film is just normal but if you want to watch a 3D film you would have to buy special glasses that you get to keep. If you are watching a 3D film that shows you shooting stars or something when you got on the glasses its looks like the shooting stars are coming straight at you. &lt;br />&lt;br />In the future we hope we wont be able to wear those horrible glasses but the things will still come at you like shooting stars.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
class 6 from Glade Hill</content>
</page></content></entry>