<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-20 GB-452000-201000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-23.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-201000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435145</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:52:57.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:52:57.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>17</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Our school day, 2011</title>
<content>

We wake up about 7am and at  8.25 we set off for school. We all walk to school. Some people go by car.&lt;br />&lt;br />9 o-clock is registration. We have lunch at 12.15pm. We like roast dinners, fish, chips and baked beans.&lt;br />&lt;br />Our favourite subjects are art, music, ICT (Information and Communication Technology,) literacy and PE (Physical Education.) Topics include history and PHSE (Physical, Health &amp; Social Education.) We are all in year 3 or 4 which means we are 8 years old. Our classes are called 4y, 3g and the names of the teachers.&lt;br />&lt;br />Computers.  We thought of lots of things which use computers in 2011. Computers we write on, i-pods, MP3 players (we listen to music on them), alarm clocks, radios, phones, DVD players (to watch films on), laptops, camcorders, SatNavs (to find places when we are in the car), cameras, TVs, DS, X-box, Playstation and Wii. A lot of these are for playing games. Smart boards (we use at school), hairdryers (we think), CD players, motor bikes, ovens, microwaves, electric pianos and electric guitars all have computers in them, too.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Cowley Brownies (URC), Oxford. July 2011.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>