<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-28.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-28</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-28.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-28.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-28</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449105</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:24.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>28TRANSPORT</title>
<content>

Bus services are much reduced compared with 1986, with some cuts implemented at the end of September 2011.  &lt;br />&lt;br />The Arriva 28 runs from Middlesbrough to Saltburn-by-the-Sea passing through Slapewath, Charltons and Margrove Park with an hourly daytime service.&lt;br />&lt;br />The 93 Middlesbrough to Scarborough service stops at Slapewath, Birk Brow Top and Stanghow Lane End on the A171.  Buses are every two hours on weekdays and every three hours on Sundays.  In the summer the service runs for longer into the evenings.&lt;br />&lt;br />Services to Stanghow are now much reduced.  The 758 is now run by Redcar and Cleveland Council on Tuesdays, Thursdays and Saturdays only, running from Guisborough to Loftus and Easington and back with four buses in each direction.&lt;br />&lt;br />To replace evening buses that were run by commercial operators and subsidised by the council there is a new hourly Monday to Saturday circular service from Redcar through Guisborough, Slapewath, Charltons, Margove Park, Skelton, Loftus and Saltburn.&lt;br />&lt;br />A significant change is that pensioners now have bus passes giving free use of buses as part of a national scheme.   Many make good use of the local buses for shopping and trips to Whitby or Scarborough.&lt;br />&lt;br />As elsewhere in the country car ownership has increased.  For example the 2001 census results for the area covering Charltons shows only 27% of households had no car or van.  It is still true to say that few of the cars are new.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Stephen Larkin</content>
</page></content></entry>