<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-18.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-19 GB-452000-195000-18</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-18.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-19/GB-452000-195000-18.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-195000-18</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412675</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-15T14:47:46.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-15T14:47:46.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-195000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>18Culham Science Centre</title>
<content>

Culham Laboratory is now Culham Science Centre. First established in the 1960s, owned and operated by the United Kingdom Atomic Energy Authority, it is home to the UK's national laboratory for fusion research CCFE (Culham Centre for Fusion Energy) &lt;br />&lt;br />Culham has made many major contributions to international fusion research and development. Today the UK fusion programme is centred on the innovative MAST (Mega Amp Spherical Tokamak) experiment and employs around 150 people. The programme is funded by the Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council and the European Union under the EURATOM treaty.&lt;br />&lt;br />Culham Science Centre hosts the world's largest magnetic fusion experiment, JET (Joint European Torus), on behalf of its European partners in the European Fusion Development Agreement set up in 1999. Around 500 people are employed at the JET facilities, with around 350 mainland European scientists visiting each year to conduct research , and many others from outside Europe.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Culham Science Centre site is also an attractive location for hi-tech businesses. It houses accommodation for a diverse range of science and technology tenants, including an Innovation Centre for start-up companies.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>