<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-31/GB-452000-318000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-31 GB-452000-318000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-31/GB-452000-318000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-31/GB-452000-318000-21.xml/4" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-318000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412009</as:updateIndex><as:revision>3</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:07.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T18:00:32.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-318000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21This area of Loughborough transformed</title>
<content>This area of Loughborough has been transformed in the intervening years. The knitwear has gone, the engineering has shrunk to a shadow of its former self and although 3M still exist in the area, to the north, pharmaceuticals giant AstraZeneca is just in the process of pulling out of the town. &lt;br />&lt;br />The land around the railway station is finally being developed from its past as a goods yard and a scrap metal company, with a new road, housing, car park and an amenity park for the area. The park has been a focal point for local community action for years. The campaign started with local community arts organisation, Charnwood Arts coming together with local residents to challenge development plans for the area. Now Sidings Park is a green space for the communities sandwiched in between major roads, the railway and the canal. It is one of the most ethnically diverse areas of the town. &lt;br />&lt;br />This area is steadily improving, albeit slowly. The farmlands are still there and Prestwold Hall is now a venue for many activities and events. Between Loughborough and Prestwold there is also now a natural burial ground.&lt;br />&lt;br />  &lt;br />&lt;br />     &lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />
Contribution by: Kev Ryan
</content>
</page></content></entry>