<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-20 GB-452000-201000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-26.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-201000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435151</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:52:59.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:52:59.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26Marbles, phones &amp; computers, 2011</title>
<content>

Marbles.  I don't think many people play marbles in 2011. When it's a sunny day I go to my uncles for a barbeque. Me, my aunties and my cousins play marbles. We have 4 marbles and we put 3 in the middle and we check the first marble in and then we get the 3 marbles before the 1st one comes back down. We have to get the 3 marbles to win.&lt;br />&lt;br />Phones. I'm going to get an i-pad. I want to be able to play games on it. I like talking on the phone but it's expensive so I can't talk to my friends too much. My big sister has a mobile phone; sometimes Grandpa helps her pay for that because you have to pay every time you use it. I hope I'll get a mobile when I'm bigger - about 10 year old.&lt;br />&lt;br />Computers. We have lots of things that people didn't used to have that use electricity and computers. There are lots and lots of the things we thought of which we use now. It would be boring if we didn't have all of these things because there wouldn't be anything to do.  We thought of i-pods, alarm clocks, TVs, Xbox, microwave cdookers, cars, overns, cameras, MP3 players, DS, Satnavs, playstations, Wii games and radios.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Cowley Brownies (URC), Oxford. July 2011.   </content>
</page></content></entry>