<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-35.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439835</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T17:51:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T17:50:09.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35Life in Rural East Dorset 2011</title>
<content>

Twenty five years on life is much the same here. Generations grow up, homes change hands and many still belong to land-owners. As fewer staff are required to run farms, some homes, traditionally, tied - cottages, have been sold or let to Housing Associations. Anyone living in this area needs to have a love of the countryside and a willingness to be happy in rather remote homes. &lt;br />&lt;br />Many more wives work and may need more cars to get to employment out of villages.Children continue to attend local, mainly Church, First Schools and Cranborne Middle School. School buses are provided and pupils aged 5 to 13 often share the same transport.The school system here is very successful and parents are happy with it.&lt;br />&lt;br />The doctors' surgeries are still in the same villages as in 1986 although access to hospitals may have changed with the greater mobility of the public. Village Halls have been up-graded in some cases and now they are used for Art classes and keep fit as well as bingo.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Women's Institute is active in nearby Cranborne, Sixpenny Handley and Witchampton but no longer in "our square". In 2015 the Women's Institute will be 100 years old and still going strong in Dorset.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett and Gillian Martin</content>
</page></content></entry>