<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-22.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449097</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:23.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:23.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22COMMUNICATIONS</title>
<content>

There is now only one postal collection, in the afternoon from several post boxes in the area.  The delivery is at about 1.00 pm (in Charltons).  With increasing ownership of mobile phones there has been nationally a decline in the use of public telephones and many have gone from rural areas.  The one at Charltons was removed by BT in December 2008.  There is still a public telephone at Margrove Park.  Mobile phone reception is not very good at Charltons.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Teesside Gazette can be delivered in the area.  The free newspapers that existed in 1986 are no longer published, but Coastal View and Moors News is a monthly free paper published in Moorsholm, covering Redcar, East Cleveland and the northern part of the North York Moors.&lt;br />&lt;br />The analogue television signal will be switched off in the region in 2012, then only digital television will be available.  Although the five terrestrial stations can be received in the area the signal is not strong and the majority of houses in Charltons have satellite receiver dishes.  The local radio stations have changed their names and are now BBC Tees and TFM Radio.  &lt;br />&lt;br />Many households have access to the Internet with broadband connections.  Wireless broadband is available in Margove Park village hall and Charltons community centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Stephen Larkin</content>
</page></content></entry>