<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-44-36 GB-448000-360000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-21.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-448000-360000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412005</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:51:33.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-448000-360000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21A LOCAL FARMER</title>
<content>Twenty-five years on from my original article in 1986, my dad still works in farming and has now been a farmer for forty-seven years. My dad's farm business is called Porter Brothers, which originally started in the 1940s as a partnership between my late grandad and his three brothers. &lt;br />&lt;br />Nowadays, the partnership is between my dad and his cousin, who also works on the farm.&lt;br />&lt;br />Although I don't work on the farm, I've seen a lot of changes whilst growing up on one and I help my dad with some of the paperwork that's now required. &lt;br />&lt;br />Since 1998, every bovine animal on my dad's farm has to be registered with a government agency called the British Cattle Movement Service (BCMS). When an animal is born it's given a unique number carried on a tag in its ear. It also has a passport, which details its mum (dam), dad (sire) and tracks all of its movements throughout its life.  &lt;br />&lt;br />My dad still receives agricultural subsidies from the European Union under the Common Agricultural Policy (CAP). The current subsidy scheme is called the Single Payment Scheme (SPS). My dad is no longer paid different amounts according to the crop he produces, but a set amount per hectare of agricultural land that he maintains in a cultivatable condition. To comply with the rules of this scheme, my dad has to keep lots of records about the crops he grows and the pesticides and fertilisers he uses.&lt;br />&lt;br />A farmer's life in the 21st century involves a lot of paperwork and a computer is just as important as a tractor.&lt;br />&lt;br />My dad's farm has grown in land area and cattle numbers over the years, but has reduced from three working farms - Hill Farm, Manor Farm and Teversal Farm to just one, Hill Farm.&lt;br />&lt;br />My dad is a beef and arable farmer and gets up at seven o'clock, seven days a week to feed his two hundred and thirteen head of cattle. He has three breeding bulls - one Limousin bull and two British Blue bulls, one hundred breeding cows, seventy-five yearlings and thirty-five beef heifers and bull calves.&lt;br />&lt;br />My dad farms two hundred and ten hectares of land, of which forty-one hectares is rented. One hundred and forty-six hectares is used to grow barley, oats, oilseed rape and wheat. The rest is grass land, which is grazed by the cattle in summer and used to make silage.&lt;br />&lt;br />No farm is complete without a tractor. My dad owns five tractors, a combined harvester, a J.C.B, a reversible plough, two telescopic fork trucks, a large square baler, four hydraulic tipping trailers, a seed drill, a fertiliser spreader, a total mixed ration feeder and a straw spreader.&lt;br />&lt;br />Farm machinery is expensive, so my dad hires some equipment, such as manure spreaders and uses contractors for chemical spraying and silaging.&lt;br />&lt;br />Neither my brother nor I work on the farm, but it is hoped that my dad's cousin's son will become a farmer and continue the Porter Brothers farming business when my dad retires...  &lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />
Contribution by: ANGELA PORTER - original author of entry when a child
</content>
</page></content></entry>