<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-55/GB-428000-555000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-42-55 GB-428000-555000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-55/GB-428000-555000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-55/GB-428000-555000-19.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-428000-555000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435135</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:11:41.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:11:41.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-428000-555000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19A Brief Historical Appraisal</title>
<content>

The previous entry ("Battle - Washington") is from 'Local Tales of Fact, Fiction, and Folklore' by local schoolmaster and historian Frederick Hill, published for children in 1944.&lt;br />&lt;br />None of the occurrences mentioned appear in any sources for the year 1068. However, the following records do exist. &lt;br />&lt;br />1069: Scots raid the Wear valley, reaching Wearmouth in 1070.&lt;br />&lt;br />1070: Storms cause a Danish fleet to scatter and some ships seek refuge at Wearmouth and Tynemouth.&lt;br />&lt;br />1069: A regional rebellion breaks out. Durham and York are captured by Northumbrians. King William leads his forces northwards as far as the south bank of the Tyne, raiding Jarrow and spending Christmas of 1069 at Hexham. &lt;br />&lt;br />William's 'Harrying of the North' results in that part of Northumbria south of the Tyne becoming totally desolate and devoid of human life for many years to follow.&lt;br />&lt;br />If any battle actually took place, why did Frederick Hill say it occurred in 1068?&lt;br />&lt;br />He was probably using The Anglo-Saxon Chronicles as a source. Some entries for 1068 actually occurred in 1069. &lt;br />&lt;br />If such a battle did occur, why is there no written record of it?&lt;br />&lt;br />Not every event was recorded and some records are lost.&lt;br />&lt;br />Why would a battle take place here?&lt;br />&lt;br />Northumbria's forces were retreating and needed to escape over the Tyne.&lt;br />&lt;br />Commanding views of the Wear Valley, Great North Road, and controls approach to the Tyne Crossing at Gateshead.&lt;br />&lt;br />Near Harlow Green a muster place for the local militiamen.&lt;br />&lt;br />Whilst an oral history does exist it is my personal feeling that without any credible evidence other than circumstance,  the alleged event must be placed firmly under the heading of 'fiction or folklore'until proven otherwise.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Ian S Chadwick</content>
</page></content></entry>