<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-35.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447105</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:20.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:20.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35FARMING – A DETAILED LOOK</title>
<content>

Following the abolition of compulsory set aside, arable fields are now seldom left fallow, except where a problem of cultivation may occur. There has been a recent development in the way in which some arable farmers now manage their crops. Instead of the traditional and very labour intensive approach of ploughing the field after harvest, the next crop is drilled direct into the stubble of the previous crop, thus disturbing the land less. Specialist equipment has been recently developed for this purpose and it creates the perfect “plant pot” in the soil for the seed to grow in, ensuring that the seed does not become flooded, causing it to rot. With exceptionally dry conditions in the spring of 2011, it appears to be the case that the new crop was less affected than if the field had been traditionally ploughed, with the difficulty and high cost of subsequently creating a new tilth. Particularly with escalating fuel prices, farming is driven to find new economies of production. Both the farms mentioned still use crop rotation with oil seed rape between wheat crops in one case and oil seed rape and beans alternatively in the other. The choice of crop could well be influenced by the ‘futures’ prices of these crops. Good quality wheat might well end up being sold to the local Weetabix factory, and beans would be sold for animal food or for the human food market in Egypt if the crop was of sufficient quality. Cank Farm was all arable, but Holdenby Mill Farm maintained some 80 cattle on 100 acres, part of which is still ridge-and-furrow and probably unploughed since the Middle Ages.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>