<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-29.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-29</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-29.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-29.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-29</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447089</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:17.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:17.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>29LEISURE ACTIVITIES AND CLUBS</title>
<content>

Membership of clubs in the village seems to be dwindling.  There is so much choice of activity nowadays and many people play golf, go walking or sit at the computer "tweeting" and "blogging".  Nevertheless, the Women's Institute continues to be popular as does the Garden Club.  Spratton Local History Society was founded 12 years ago and attracts about 30 history lovers to each meeting.  All these societies have speakers and meet throughout the year.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a pre-school play group and a mothers and toddlers group, while the beaver scouts, cubs, scouts, guides and brownies are extremely popular. The Football Club meets on the Recreation Field and has its own sports and social club premises.  A Photography Club has recently started and is attracting an enthusiastic following.  The Women's Institute have generously gifted their hall to the village and this is now Spratton's Village Hall, looked after by a committee of volunteers.  Allotment holders have an annual Produce Show and the history society gives guided walks to visitors round the historic centre of the village.&lt;br />&lt;br />St Andrew's Church is the venue for concerts and exhibitions and the PCC is keen to encourage more activities centred on the Church.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>