<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-99/GB-464000-99000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-99 GB-464000-99000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-99/GB-464000-99000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-99/GB-464000-99000-22.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-99000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436087</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T12:09:59.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T12:09:59.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-99000</dblock_id>
<original_item>7</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Tricorn - Life &amp; Death</title>
<content>

Many people will be glad to hear the Tricorn has since been demolished! It was in fact during the 1980s, the centre became increasingly seedy and the nightclub there was developed into a casino. The shops slowly left, with the last ones closing in March 2002. The centre's car park was also the scene of many suicide attempts, being amongst the tallest publicly accessible buildings on the south coast. For this reason, a plaque offering support from The Samaritans was positioned at this infamous point.&lt;br />&lt;br />Numerous attempts to get the building listed as amongst the best examples of Brutalist architecture failed throughout the 1990s, and neglect, in addition to Portsmouth's wet coastal climate, caused the building to fall beyond the scope of easy repair. Structural steel within the concrete began to rust causing expansion of the concrete, and in some sections, small stalactites began to grow off ledges.&lt;br />&lt;br />Portsmouth City Council deliberated the demolition of the centre for many years; however, the uniquely designed car-parking block, which provided 400 parking spaces, was too useful for the city to destroy it until 2004. The site is now occupied by a ground-level open-air car park.&lt;br />&lt;br />Car parking area of the Tricorn Centre.&lt;br />&lt;br />Opponents of demolition argued that the structure, while sadly undermaintained, was still salvageable with the work of ingenious designers and a long-term city plan. However, government and public opinion was that the building had decayed too far and had attracted such a bad reputation that the only option was to replace it.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Tricorn was the subject of such strength and diversity of public feeling that opinion boards were placed around its boarding for the public to write on.&lt;br />&lt;br />Shame there was not much variation in the source of submittals though. If the BBC were to reinvite people to do a similar thing now  , thanks to the internet the response would be incredible.   &lt;br />
George Hafiz</content>
</page></content></entry>