<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-25.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439777</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:04.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:04.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25Homelife and Dairy Farming 2011</title>
<content>

There have been changes to the Shaftesbury Estates in recent years since the sad death of the 10th.Earl in 2004. Sadly, the 11th.Earl died aged 27 and his brother Lord Nicholas has become the 12th. Earl. He seems very committed to the estate and has already made many changes - not least the renovation of one wing of St.Giles' House to live in.&lt;br />&lt;br />Also, New Barn Farm has returned to Estate ownership.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a dairy herd of 1000 animals and woodland management continues.&lt;br />&lt;br />The 12th.Earl, a keen sportsman, has plans to use the Estate as in the Great Shaftesbury Run in June 2011.&lt;br />&lt;br />The cottages nearby are now privately owned. &lt;br />&lt;br />Matterley Drove Cottages, four in all, are now privately owned, and the gardens, once open, reach the road B 3078 and are hidden by tall trees. Any children in these homes are too young to go to school or go elsewhere from when they had started school before the parents moved to their present homes.&lt;br />&lt;br />One owner felt they were too remote, although on a main road,and were looking to sell, possibly not true country-lovers they feel.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett and Gillian Martin</content>
</page></content></entry>