<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-52/GB-420000-528000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-42-52 GB-420000-528000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-52/GB-420000-528000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-42-52/GB-420000-528000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-420000-528000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>445209</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:12.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-21T11:38:22.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-420000-528000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Growing up in Bishop Auckland</title>
<content>

I moved with my family to Bp A from Crook in January 1945, aged 12. The school playing fields were adjacent to those of the Boys' Grammar School next door, very convenient for friendships developing as one grew older. One of the Masters ran an after school Dancing class, where we all learned to quickstep, foxtrot and waltz sedately for the School Dance and less sedately at the Youth Club run by the Methodist church... the main aource of evening socialising, apart from the cinema, for us teenagers. The daytime rendezvous was Rossi's cafe, which I think is still there.  There was no swimming pool then so occasional trips to the Darlington Baths were considered a real outing!  I was very interested in the history of the town and enjoyed the school visit to the Roman hypocaust at the Vinovium a mile or so away. Recently, watching Time Team on television it has been fascinating to see how much more there was to discover....the row of Temples and now a whole Roman Town is appearing. The war did not touch us so much as children in the north of England. I remember the day it ended and that we had the next day as a holiday. i went for a bike ride with my friend to Witton-le-Wear. I was in the sixth form when the King died and happened to be on the school drive when the postman arrived "the King's dead" he said. I thought I had better tell the Head Mistress and she called an assembly to announce it to the school.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>