<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-25.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436057</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T11:29:47.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T11:29:47.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25Lifein 2011</title>
<content>

Hi my name is Maddison. Life in 2011 is very different than in the 1986 some of the things are the same such as schools  Children still go to school but they have to do S.A.Ts but in 1986 they didn't have to.&lt;br />&lt;br />Clothes&lt;br />&lt;br />Nowadays people wear more trendy stuff, everyone has there own style also clothes cost a lot more money. I go to Next for my clothes it is very expensive but they have great styles. Me and my mum like most things the same I brought a jacket the other month it cost (£30) but my mum does not mind because we don't go often! &lt;br />&lt;br />Consoles&lt;br />&lt;br />Also children have games consoles such as wii, Xbox 360, I pads, I pods, mobile phones, Ds, Ds I, TV’s (in colour) and computers. Me and Taylor (a girl in my class) did a survey of the gadgets children in class 6 own : phone 15 , I pod 12, computer 15,ds 15 , ds I 11, TV 22  and I pad 1  but lots of children are getting an I pod soon.&lt;br />&lt;br />Girls football in 2011&lt;br />&lt;br />Girl’s football is really popular and most schools have a girls team as well as a boys team. This year the girl’s football team has played in some tournaments. The team are Maddison (me) Nicole, Megan, Taylor, Stephanie, Shelby, Olivia, Chrystal. We came 4th.&lt;br />&lt;br />Mr Connolly was our manager and some of the parents came to watch us we play against South Glade primary, Seely primary and Warren primary.&lt;br />&lt;br />My achievements this year&lt;br />&lt;br />I play football for a team (Arnold town ) we won in the cup final we got a medal and a shield also we have a sports day which is took place on our school field every year I took part in the girls short race and came 2nd then in the relay race me and my team came 3rd .&lt;br />&lt;br />By Maddison   &lt;br />
Gladehillprimaryschool</content>
</page></content></entry>