<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-18/GB-476000-189000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-47-18 GB-476000-189000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-18/GB-476000-189000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-18/GB-476000-189000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-476000-189000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449139</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:27.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-476000-189000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Public Services in the early 21st Century</title>
<content>

TRANSPORT.Public transport in the area is non existent.The Post Bus and the last of the subsidised public bus services were discontinued some years ago.Members of the public are not allowed to travel on the school contract buses.Residents have to use their own cars , pay for taxis or rely on lifts from friends and neighbours.It is unlikely that this situation will change in the future. However, many of the households in the area own 2 or more cars.&lt;br />&lt;br />POSTAL SERVICES. There is one collection and delivery a day on Mondays through Saturday.This is mainly a letter and small packet service. Parcels are usually handled by private carriers.&lt;br />&lt;br />TELECOMMUNICATIONS.The public telephone kiosk in Turville has been closed. Mobile phone reception and access to Broadband is variable throughout the area.&lt;br />&lt;br />MEDICAL SERVICES.GP services are provided by the Marlow Medical Group who have a purpose built surgery in Hambleden. Some residents prefer to use surgeries in Marlow or Henley along with dental practices in those towns.&lt;br />&lt;br />The provision of library services, public utilities and secondary education remain as described in 1986.   &lt;br />
Ray Jones</content>
</page></content></entry>