<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-33.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436847</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:08.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:08.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33The Chequers Public House</title>
<content>

The Chequer is a traditional English pub with the current building dating from around 1870.&lt;br />&lt;br />It located in the heart of the village on Chequers lane between the High Street and the church. The inside of the pub has an L shape bar and a restaurant area at the back which was added about eighteen years ago. As well as the main bar area across the yard there a games room for playing darts or the traditional game of skittles, there is a also new outdoor smoking area in the yard and beer garden for summer drinks.&lt;br />&lt;br />Gordon and Gill moved to the village twenty one years ago to take over the running of the pub. In that time they have seen a change in consumer tastes and with the strict drink driving laws the pub has had to change from  being a place to get a drink into some where you go for the evening.  In meeting these new demands the bar offer a number of different real ales as well as the full range of other beverages.  Good  home made food has also become very important part of want the pub has to offer.  As well as the regular menu they offer a range of specials often using seasonal ingredients.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>