<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-20.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-38 GB-468000-387000-20</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-20.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-20.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-387000-20</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447117</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-11-10T11:47:14.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:22.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">

<dblock_id>GB-468000-387000</dblock_id>

<original_item>9</original_item>

<year>2011</year>

<title>20Conversion of Mattersey chapel to a dwelling</title>

<content>



The Ruff family purchased both Chapel House and the Old Chapel in 1984, both listed buildings, from the previous owner, a developer.  The chapel was initially only allowed to be used unaltered for business purposes, so storage for a plumbing business mainly.  It was built as a Methodist Chapel in 1792, holding about 50 people, and in its time had been a very lively community, with regular well-attended services and coach outings recorded locally before its merger with Everton Methodist church and sale to the Pentecostal church (1960s?).  The only trustee known of on purchasing was Mr Walker of Brewery Lane, Everton, and the chapel had been unused for some years, especially since the opening of Mattersey Hall Bible College around 1981 (previously a private school).  Before purchasing, the chapel included long dark-wood benches raised in gentle tiers – these were claimed by the Bible College - and the village war memorial plaque on the north wall, which was removed by a parish councillor for storage.  A simple wooden dias had an unadorned wooden bookstand on the east side and the eastern corners of the room were partitioned with half-wood, half-glassed screens for storage.  Eventually, planning application to convert to a house was applied for the chapel, as it was felt this would better ensure its preservation in the longer term, and plans were drawn up by Jack Bell, architect, of Harwell, Everton.  The work was carried out by John (Jeremy) Ruff and completed in 1996, when the Ruff family moved in on selling Chapel House next door.  The southern part of the garden of Chapel House, fronting Job Lane, was separated by deed to provide a garden/driveway for the Old Chapel, as it became known, as it only occupied the corner it was originally built on.  An extension to provide an adjoining garage and bedroom above was added at the back, the north side.  The original cladding was left in place, as it was unusual for small chape  ls locally, and it was felt removal would comprise the original soft (and probably damaged) clay brickwork (as is common around Mattersey and Everton).  The south frontage of the chapel on to Job Lane and the gable ends were preserved in their original state, as per the requirements of the planners.  The false ceiling of the chapel was removed, to reveal the original beams, which were left visible in the full-height living room, alongside which a stair and gallery was constructed accessing two bedrooms.  The original plain glass windows on the south and east walls were replaced or restored. On working on the one-time Methodist Manse on Lime Tree Avenue, Retford, Mr Ruff came across an original Bible belonging to the chapel and was allowed to retain it to keep at the Old Chapel.  This was passed on to the new owner when the Ruff family moved on in 2000.   &lt;br />

Mrs M Ruff</content>

</page></content></entry>