<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-44-36 GB-448000-360000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-22.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-448000-360000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411999</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:05.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:51:32.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-448000-360000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Employment changes in Mansfield</title>
<content>Mansfield has lost a great majority of its industry&lt;br />&lt;br />All pits have closed&lt;br />&lt;br />Mansfield shoe Co closed in 2004 and the building was knocked down in 2006 - presently the land is under development for building flats&lt;br />&lt;br />Mansfield brewery has closed and has been demolished, the site is where the new bus station is planned&lt;br />&lt;br />Metal Box factory has closed and has been partially demolished&lt;br />&lt;br />The leisure centre on Chesterfield Road has been demolished and a large Tesco store built (some jobs recouped here)&lt;br />&lt;br />It is easy to see why we have such a large percentage of unemployment in the area now with the loss of all theses industries.&lt;br />&lt;br />Various Industrial Unit sites have sprung up in and around the town - especially along the MARR route but all of these have failed to attract businesses as predicted.&lt;br />&lt;br />We do now have a Railway Station, built in 1995 and a 4th lane on the M1 opened in 2010 after 2 and a half years of disruption and a cost of £350 million - and both of these serve to transport people out of Mansfield looking for work.&lt;br />&lt;br />My daily journey on the M1 from J27 to J25 for Long Eaton gives evidence of the traffic flow away from Mansfield towards Nottingham in the morning and then the ensuing traffic jams back again in the evening. &lt;br />&lt;br />As the 4th lane was built specifically to cope with the extra traffic flow between J29 and J24, this would support what I would experience on my journey&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />
Contribution by: Mrs Elizabeth Parker
</content>
</page></content></entry>