<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-28/GB-400000-282000-20.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-28 GB-400000-282000-20</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-28/GB-400000-282000-20.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-28/GB-400000-282000-20.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-282000-20</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411981</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-06T17:31:24.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:31:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-282000</dblock_id>
<original_item>6</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>20Stonehouse Gang - Still going strong</title>
<content>The Stonehouse Gang Youth Club is still going strong today (after nearly 75 years), but is now situated halfway up Burnel Road in it's own dedicated clubhouse. The motto "It's better to light a candle, than to curse the darkness" still sits in the heart of all the Stonehouse Gang does, and they use the Ankh as its logo - the Egyptian symbol for life.&lt;br />&lt;br />I volunteer at the Stonehouse after having grown up going to the club as a kid. The Gang opens 6 nights a week for activities for all ages (6-25 year olds) and during the school holidays it offers a successful playscheme.&lt;br />&lt;br />They still have their residential in the Brecon Beacons which I love to visit several times a year on adventure trips. A snapshot of this years activities include a camping trip to Germany, a week away in Cornwall, trips to the Ty Carreg residential centre and trips to Thorp Park. Also trips ice skating and bowling feature within the programme. The volunteers and Leaders regularly organise activities and leagues within the club too. They have a media club who make movies, music and webpages. The Gang's Friday night football club play come or shine on the Powerleague pitches in Aston, and the club also run a popular Duke of Edinburgh award scheme.&lt;br />&lt;br />As a charity, the Gang currently faces tough times due to Government funding cuts to youth services across the board. The club encourages its youngsters and volunteers to help with fund-raising within the local community.&lt;br />&lt;br />I enjoy working as a volunteer for the Stonehouse Gang. It's offered me many great memories and experiences both as a youngster at the club as a member, and as a volunteer. It's a great community hub, brings people together of all ages, races and backgrounds. Despite its history, it isn't afraid to move with the times.&lt;br />&lt;br />There's a great team spirit amongst the team of staff  and volunteers, as well as the young people at the Gang. It's an 'all come together' type of place, with an 'anything's possible' attitude. Long live the Gang!
&lt;br /&gt;
</content>
</page></content></entry>