<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-31.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-31</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-31.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-31.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-31</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436071</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T11:29:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T11:29:49.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>31Schools in the bestwood area</title>
<content>Schools in the Bestwood area!&lt;br />&lt;br />There are lots of schools in Bestwood: Glade hill, Southglade, Arnbrook, Robin Hood, St Margret Clitheroe and Westglade. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Teachers at Glade hill are:&lt;br />&lt;br />Teachers at Glade Hill are :&lt;br />&lt;br />Class 1: Mrs Rowe&lt;br />&lt;br />Class 2: Mrs Bailey and Mrs Selby&lt;br />&lt;br />Class J: Mrs Joubert&lt;br />&lt;br />Class L: Miss Lee &lt;br />&lt;br />Class 5: Miss Clayton&lt;br />&lt;br />Class 6: Miss Gibson &lt;br />&lt;br />Glade Hill is a fairly small school with only 235 pupils. So, compared to other schools it is quite small because at Southglade there are 350 pupils and at Robin Hood there are 444 pupils. &lt;br />&lt;br />I go to Glade Hill and I am in year 6, my teacher is Miss Gibson. I don't do any after school clubs but some children decide too there are lots of afterschool clubs such as: Football, Music, French, Activate, Big band and Nature Bugs. Some clubs are in school times like: Choir, Ict, Campus Rangers, Pupil voice and Green team. &lt;br />&lt;br />Every year we go on school trips for example: Museums, Theatres and Adventure parks. At the end of year the year 6s go on an end of year treat. This year we are going to Drayton Manor on the 12th of July, It will cost £22.50 per child.&lt;br />&lt;br />A Typical day at school &lt;br />&lt;br />A Normal day at school starts at 8:45 first we do Literacy then at 10:00 we go into assembly then everybody goes to maths focus groups for 15 minutes. After that we go outside for 20 minutes break then we have maths. At 12:00 we have lunch for 1 hour. Then after lunch we do PE, topic work or French.&lt;br />&lt;br />At Glade Hill we have solar panels which take light from the sun to generate electricity for our school to use.&lt;br />   &lt;br /> Class 6 Glade Hill Primary</content>
</page></content></entry>