<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-16.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-16</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-16.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-16.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-16</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420611</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-10T14:27:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-10T14:27:49.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>16Schools in Bestwood</title>
<content>

There are many schools in Bestwood such as: Glade Hill, Southglade, Arnbrook, Robin Hood, St. Margaret Clitheroe and Westglade. But the school I go to is Glade Hill and it has 235 children in it but compared to other schools it is quiet a small school because there are 350 children in Southglade and 444 children in Robin Hood!&lt;br />&lt;br />The teachers at my school are:&lt;br />Foundation 1: Mrs Beet and Mrs Michel. Foundation 1 has 48 children. &lt;br />Foundation 2: Mrs Man and Mrs Tilston. Foundation 2 has 28 children. &lt;br />Class 1: Mrs Rowe. Class 1 has 27 children&lt;br />Class 2: Mrs Selby and Mrs Bailey. Class 2 has 30 children&lt;br />Class J: Mrs Joubert. Class 3 has 25 children&lt;br />Class L: Miss Lee. Class 4 has 22 children&lt;br />Class 5: Miss Clayton. Class 5 has 27 children and&lt;br />Class 6: Miss Gibson who is my class teacher. Class 6 has 28 children.&lt;br />&lt;br />Glade Hill has been on many fantastic trips like Oaklands manor, Ice skating, Trampolining at Bigwood, Basketball tournaments, Cinemas and lots more. Also, children decide to do after school clubs such as: Football, Music, French, Big band, which is like music, Nature Bugs, Basketball. During the day we also do Choir, ICT, Campus Rangers, Pupil Council and Green Team.&lt;br />&lt;br />When you get into year 6 every year you have to do S.A.T.S they are very important because the levels go up into your secondary school. &lt;br />&lt;br /> By Stephanie &lt;br />   &lt;br />
Class 6 from Glade Hill</content>
</page></content></entry>