<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-26.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447087</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:17.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:17.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>15</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26TRANSPORT - RURAL</title>
<content>

The most widely used mode of transport is the family car, with a large influx of these into the village twice a day during term-time from parents outside the village who have their children at Spratton Hall School.  The village roads are unsuited for this influx, but an alternative solution has yet to be found.  Also during term-time, there is a collection and delivery service by bus for pupils attending Guilsborough School.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is a local ‘Centre Bus’ service which runs between Welford and Northampton, picking up from up to nine villages.  There are seven buses each way on Monday to Friday, and six on Saturdays, the first bus is at around 0700 and the last at around 1700.  A small number of residents use this service, which is free to residents entitled to a bus pass.&lt;br />&lt;br />Tesco sponsor a bus which comes to the village every Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday at 1030, and takes people to the Weston Favell Shopping Centre, returning approximately 2 hours later.&lt;br />&lt;br />Daventry Area Community Transport (DACT) is a charity based in Daventry, which uses volunteer drivers (three or four live in Spratton) to take people without their own transport to medical appointments.  There is a small fee to cover costs, which are supported by an annual grant from Spratton and other Parish Councils.  The DACT bus, which has a capacity of 16 people, can also be hired by local organisations wishing to visit places of interest.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>