<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-35.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436853</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:10.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35Ravensthorpe Church</title>
<content>

Building:&lt;br />&lt;br />The Church of Saint Denys has stood here for 800 years, but the present building of brown ironstone dates from the 13th and 14th centuries. It is in good condition but the weathering of the soft Northamptonshire stone needs regular restoration on which over 150,000 pounds has been spent in recent years. There is evidence of a religious building of 10th century here.&lt;br />&lt;br />Internally it has a plain appearance with rows of pews and a small side alter which was brought from the neighbouring hamlet of Teeton when the chapel closed years ago. The only stained glass window is to the east over the alter and was installed in 1937. The other windows are old and give clear, magical light.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is an absence of elaborate memorials but two hatchments from Teeton hall hang over the North door. There is a massive iron bound chest over 400 years old with 6 locks, a wall cabinet displays armour from the 15th and 16th century. &lt;br />&lt;br />At the back is a small organ, also a recess under the tower where the bells can be wrung. A sound system has been installed for the hard of hearing. The clock has been automated this year thanks to a gift from a member of the congregation; thus eliminating someone having to climb the vertical ladder into the tower once a week. Colourful kneelers have been worked for many of the pews. Volunteers clean and put flowers in the Church by rota.&lt;br />&lt;br />Churchyard:&lt;br />&lt;br />Around the church is an extensive churchyard which is the parish burial ground with a corner set aside for ashes. These grounds are kept in good order by voluntary effort, which has recently involved tidying up several of the large trees and renewing lengths of boundary wall. The steps to the churchyard were also repaired. In order to get mowers into the churchyard without damaging the steps, a new entrance was created through the hedge at the far end, adjacent to the church allotments. It also has provided a popular short cut for parishioners. Regular mowing is paid for by the parish council and the grass has never looked better. The headstones have been checked for safety and repaired as necessary. The paths are gravel and new surfaces are being considered to provide better access for prams and the disabled.&lt;br />&lt;br />Newsletter:&lt;br />&lt;br />For 10 years a member of the PCC has written and edited a newsletter that is delivered free of charge to every household in Ravensthorpe. Church service times as well as village news are published. This is a much valued community service dependant on the editor and the generosity of the printers. &lt;br />&lt;br />Organisation:&lt;br />&lt;br />At present Saint Denys is one of the eight churches that constitute the Uplands Benefice consisting of the parishes of Cold Ashby, Cottesbrooke, Creaton, Guilsborough, Hollowell, Ravensthorpe, Spratton and Thornby. We are currently served by a committed and enthusiastic Priest, the Revd. Mark Battison together with some lay readers. The vicarage for the Benefice is in Guilsborough (The vicarage in Ravensthorpe was sold many years ago). Since March 2011 a clerk has been employed by the parishes on a part time basis and is based in Guilsborough Church.&lt;br />&lt;br />St Denys and the village of Ravensthorpe have been disadvantaged over two decades by frequent diocesan changes to parish arrangements in the area which has included 6 different Parish Priests.  &lt;br />&lt;br />Services:&lt;br />&lt;br />1st Sunday 	8.30am 	Communion&lt;br />&lt;br />2nd Sunday 	10am 	Benefice Service at one of the 8 Parishes.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Sunday 	9.45am 	Sung Communion&lt;br />&lt;br />4th Sunday 	11am 	non Eucharistic Service&lt;br />&lt;br />The trend is to have more interaction between the Parishes.&lt;br />&lt;br />The attendance at a Ravensthorpe Service is approximately 10 at a Communion Service and 35 to the non Eucharistic Service increasing to 60 for the major festivals of the Church. Once a month the morning service is conducted by a lay reader and coffee is served afterwards by volunteers. The Church is full at the annual Christmas Eve service.&lt;br />&lt;br />St Denys relies on visiting bell ringing teams for weddings. There is an organist at most of our services and the choir is going from strength to strength and is a joyous part of Church life.&lt;br />&lt;br />Fund Raising:&lt;br />&lt;br />We contribute about £6,500 per year as our Parish Share to diocesan funds. An annual Church Fete was restarted 4 years ago by an enthusiastic Ravensthorpe resident is our main fund raiser. Other events are the annual cycle ride and the well supported Harvest supper. Gift Aid envelopes bring in an extra 28p to every pound.&lt;br />&lt;br />Future:&lt;br />&lt;br />The Church is well supported by villagers in many different ways from maintenance to fund-raising. Ho wever the average age of the congregation is elderly and service attendance is decreasing, factors used by the diocese in the provision of pastoral care. Attempts are being made to introduce younger members to the congregation.  To remain unchanged makes St Denys's future uncertain.&lt;br />&lt;br />For the Church only to be used for special occasions, weddings, funerals, baptisms, and an annual carol service would be sad, reducing the church to a care and maintenance basis. The message must be use it or risk losing it.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>