<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-27.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-27</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-27.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-27.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-27</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447093</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:18.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:18.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>27HOUSING AND RESIDENTIAL</title>
<content>

Holdenby remains a relatively exclusive village with median to high property prices. Most of the houses have been modernised. One small in-fill development has been permitted with six mid-range houses constructed in a style consistent with the surrounding residences.&lt;br />&lt;br />Few major developments have occurred in Spratton in the last fifteen years. Nearly all residential construction has been confined to in-filling and, occasionally, the exploitation of larger gardens. Most frequently developments have been speculative in nature with the result that there remains a severe shortage of affordable housing in the village. Their style ranges from the utilitarian, to 'Town house', to the vernacular. Property prices hover around mid-range levels depending on location and size. A Village Design Statement to serve as a framework for the future infrastructure and building environment of the village is to be submitted to Daventry District Council to provide planning guidelines. The possibility of a Conservation Area is being discussed.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>