<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-41-29/GB-412000-294000-14.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-41-29 GB-412000-294000-14</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-41-29/GB-412000-294000-14.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-41-29/GB-412000-294000-14.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-412000-294000-14</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449021</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:16.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:16.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-412000-294000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>14Day in the life of a sixth former</title>
<content>

Hannah is 17 and a sixth form pupil. Back in 1985 sixth formers didn’t have mobile phones, cable TV, computers and iPods. Now they’re part of every day life: &lt;br />&lt;br />Hannah’s typical day:&lt;br />&lt;br />My school day begins at 8.40am. I get woken up by the alarm on my mobile phone at 7am. I usually watch TV in my room while I’m getting ready (we’ve got Virgin cable). &lt;br />&lt;br />I don’t often have breakfast and I walk to school with a group of friends.&lt;br />&lt;br />I’m studying Maths, Physics, I.C.T and Economics. I’m undecided about what I want to do after school, so I’m researching options of both university and apprenticeships.  I’m exploring whether to go into business and finance or teaching. &lt;br />&lt;br />Obviously what’s happening with tuition and university fees at the moment is something that will probably affect me and my friends in the next couple of years.&lt;br />&lt;br />On a typical day at school I usually stay in for lunch, though I don’t usually take any food with me. I sometimes buy food from the sixth form vending machine or go to the local shopping centre. At the end of the school day I walk back home with my friends.&lt;br />&lt;br />Once home I go on my laptop and go on facebook for around half an hour. I then either have a driving lesson or do homework/revision. &lt;br />&lt;br />Once I’ve finished my school work I have my dinner. As I am a vegetarian and my parents aren’t, I tend to cook for myself. My dad tends to cook dinner for him and my mum. I have a takeaway about once a month with friends. &lt;br />&lt;br />I go jogging twice a week and listen to my ipod while joggnig.&lt;br />&lt;br />From around 7pm I watch TV or a DVD in my room and I’m constantly texting my friends until I go to bed.&lt;br />&lt;br />At the weekend I tend to go shopping usually for clothes and in the evening I either go to a party, see my boyfriend or see my friends.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Hannah</content>
</page></content></entry>