<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-36.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-26 GB-468000-267000-36</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-36.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-26/GB-468000-267000-36.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-267000-36</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447107</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-09T18:20:08.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:20.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">

<dblock_id>GB-468000-267000</dblock_id>

<original_item>4</original_item>

<year>2011</year>

<title>36FARMING AN OVERVIEW</title>

<content>



There are a number of farms in the area, the majority leased from the Holdenby and Althorp Estates. The earlier survey was based on Cank Farm, part of the latter and now farmed by a different tenant and covering just over 200 acres. Another farm at Holdenby Mill encompasses 580 acres, part owned and part leased but not from these Estates. There are just two farms which had sheep in the square, with Holdenby North Lodge keeping some 200 animals bought in as ewe lambs to sell later on as young breeding sheep, and Tithe Farm with the grazing under the control of a local butcher having some 350 animals. The latter were ‘easy-care’ sheep with self-shedding fleeces, avoiding the need for uneconomic shearing. There has been little money in sheep in recent years with even the value of fleeces now more or less being the same as the cost of shearing, but there are better signs in 2011, and clearly the butcher (who has a flock of 1000 sheep) finds it worthwhile. One farmer, who has given up keeping sheep, described them as very labour intensive and for the younger farmer. So the entire square is now dominated by arable, with a few cattle, and horses for recreational purposes. It is difficult to be precise on the usage of the 4700 acres or so in the square, but dwellings and Holdenby House possibly 350 acres, sheep 350 acres, cattle 250 acres, horses 300 acres, other 350 acres, so arable could be around 3100 acres, around two-thirds. Certainly a visual overview of the area would support this.   &lt;br />

</content>

</page></content></entry>