<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-33.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-40-10 GB-400000-108000-33</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-33.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-40-10/GB-400000-108000-33.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-400000-108000-33</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439785</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-400000-108000</dblock_id>
<original_item>17</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>33Farming and Cottage Industry 2011</title>
<content>

Although little seems different in this very rural area, in the twenty five years since 1986, this particular settlement has seen some changes. The old farmhouse and holiday complex originally owned by the couple who decided to breed Jacob sheep has now been sold and the cottages are individually owned. A local GP now lives in the farmhouse and it has been changed to allow separate access to the house and garden, no longer shared with the cottages. &lt;br /> &lt;br />In 1988 a new Scandia Hus (Swedish) house and farm buildings were built on adjoining land further down the road to accommodate the increasing flock of sheep. This business grew until it was necessary to send the fleeces away to be machine - spun, as there were too many to hand spin, and to be woven or knitted. At the beginning all wool was knitted up locally which provided local - cottage industry - employment. &lt;br /> &lt;br />The husband has a suit made from home - grown wool. Meat was also available to buy for a time from the farm. &lt;br /> &lt;br />The business grew and the ewes and rams were taken to local Agricultural Shows to enter competitions and won many prizes. &lt;br /> &lt;br />The couple have now retired and only keep a small flock for their own interest &lt;br /> &lt;br />Since a famous supermarket came to the local market town shopping habits have changed but it is still about eight miles away and cars are essential.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Heather Bartlett</content>
</page></content></entry>