<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-39/GB-476000-393000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-47-39 GB-476000-393000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-39/GB-476000-393000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-39/GB-476000-393000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-476000-393000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447469</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-28T18:00:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-26T14:41:30.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-476000-393000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Fire Station</title>
<content>

Misterton Fire Station still provides fire cover for the village and surrounding area and on average receives 140 calls a year. During 2009, the station under went a major refurbishment which provided staff with extra office space, changing facilities and a gym as well as upgrading the training facilities and IT.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Andy Horton is now the Officer in Charge and there are still 16 personnel providing "On call" cover day and night. As most of the local employers have now gone, the 16 all work away from the village and to provide 24/7 cover we are reliant on the shift workers - these include Power workers, full time and Airport firefighters, Security workers and a miner.The personnel are now trained in a wide range of skills above and beyond fire fighting - Working at Height, water rescue, Road traffic Incidents, Chemical incidents and first aid. And they carry equipment on the appliance to support these skills - Dry suits, harnesses for working at height, radiation detectors, defibrilators, hydraulic rescue equipment.In 2005 Misterton became one of the first fire stations in Notts to respond to medical emergencies on behalf of the Ambulance Service. They still carry out this role and have now been provided with a response car, allowing them to respond to medical incidents and fires or rescues at the same time. The Fire Crew from Misterton also promote fire safety and visit local schools and youth groups as well as attending many local events throughout the year.   &lt;br />
Andy Horton</content>
</page></content></entry>