<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-36.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-36</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-36.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-36.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-36</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436851</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:10.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>36Ravensthorpe Women's Institute</title>
<content>

Ravensthorpe WI was formed in 1919 and today we have a successful branch with 39 members. In 2009 we celebrated 90 years with a birthday tea party and an outing to Teeton Hall to recreate the first meeting. It was an occasion to dress up, wear our hats and celebrate many achievements over the years.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Head office is in London and the regional office is in Moulton, Northampton. Membership costs £30 per annum. We meet monthly in the Village Hall for a programme of talks, discussion of any campaigns that the W.I is involved in and to meet friends and chat. &lt;br />&lt;br />In 2011 our programme includes talks on -&lt;br />&lt;br />Working with Police Dogs; Beetle Drive with cheese and wine evening; Sewing and Craft; Old Soldiers; Resolutions discussion and vote; Crazy Hats; Reflexology for Better Health; My Work in Crime; Metal Detecting.&lt;br />&lt;br />There is also an outing in August and a Christmas Party with members own entertainment. The party is always good fun - we all contribute to a shared festive meal which is followed by the entertainment either a pantomime sketch, readings, tales to tell or songs.  &lt;br />&lt;br />We have supported campaigns to save local Post Offices from closure and to raise concerns over the decline of the bee population. This year's  AGM will discuss the resolutions to oppose the practice of mega farms and to ask the Government to support libraries some of which are currently facing closure.&lt;br />&lt;br />The members take an active part in their community. We have a display in the Post Office window this currently shows some of the craft work that has been done and photographs of members taking part in a "sport for all"  exercise.&lt;br />&lt;br />Several members are involved in a project of "crazy quilting". Odd shapes of material with varied colours and textures are sewn together by hand, embroidered and embellished and then fitted together to make a small quilt. This will be sold to raise funds for a charity. &lt;br />&lt;br />Next year when the village hall has been refurbished we hope to put on another Food and Produce Show. Whatever the event the W.I will be there making tea and selling their home-made cakes! &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>