<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-17.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-34 GB-452000-345000-17</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-17.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-34/GB-452000-345000-17.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-345000-17</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420613</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-10T14:27:50.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-345000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>17Football in 2011</title>
<content>

&lt;br />&lt;br />Football is one of the most popular sports in the world.&lt;br />&lt;br />In 2011 Manchester United won the Premier League it was their 19th title which puts them one above Liverpool.&lt;br />&lt;br />This year Manchester United has bought Ashley Young, Phil Jones and David de Gea.&lt;br />&lt;br />Barcelona won the Champions League and Manchester united came second.&lt;br />&lt;br />Barcelona won La Liga and Real Madrid came second and Valencia came 3rd.    &lt;br />&lt;br />Ronaldo, who plays for Real Madrid, is worth £80 million!!!&lt;br />&lt;br />Ronaldinho was the most skilful player in the world.&lt;br />&lt;br />Manchester city won the .F.A and Birmingham won the carling cup. &lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />In the Championship Queens Park Rangers came first and Norwich came second. Swansea city won the play offs so they have got promotion to the Premier League. &lt;br />&lt;br />If you want to go and play for a football team you could go and play for Arnold Town or Bestwood Park Rangers.&lt;br />&lt;br />My favourite football team is Nottingham Forest and my favourite player is Robbie Findley. &lt;br />&lt;br />GLADE HILL SCHOOL FOOTBALL TEAM&lt;br />&lt;br />The school football team train on Mondays we play our matchers at south glade we play all different teams such as &lt;br />&lt;br />Southglade , Hayden and Seely.&lt;br />&lt;br />The football team players are Thomas W, Thomas U, Chrystal, Oliver, Kadyn, Louis, Morgan and Ryan.   &lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />              By Ryan. &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Class 6 Gladehill</content>
</page></content></entry>