<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-11/GB-440000-114000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-44-11 GB-440000-114000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-11/GB-440000-114000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-11/GB-440000-114000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-440000-114000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412631</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-15T11:36:26.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-15T11:36:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-440000-114000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Shirley</title>
<content>

Shirley consists of a residential built up area. It is split up into two parts, Upper Shirley and Lower Shirley: in Lower Shirley you can find the main road Shirley High Street which has many chain shops such as Poundland and boots as well as fast food restaurants like subway and mcdonalds. Also there are specialist shops such as 'Holt and Haskell' which is a cricket shop and a local butchers. There is also a Police station.&lt;br />&lt;br />Lower Shirley also contains a high rise tower block called 'Shirley Towers', surrounding this is lots of council flats which were built in the 1950s. At the edge of Lower Shirley there is a very popular park called St James Park which is currently being rebuilt with help from the lottery fund. Completion is due to be mid-June 2011 and it will contain new tennis courts, a cafe, bew play equipment and beautiful gardens.&lt;br />&lt;br />Upper Shirley consists of higher class Edwardian housing which h ave higher ceilings and larger rooms. It contains some convenience shops such as 'Dhillons' on Wilton Crescent and 'St James Convenience'. There is also a bakery and a fish and chip shop on St.James Road. Upper Shirley contains a primary school called Shirley Junior School, a secondary state school called Upper Shirley High, and an independent secondary school called King Edward VI school.&lt;br />&lt;br />The Common is a major park in Upper Shirley which separates Shirley from Highfield. It contains a paddling pool, play equipment, a boating lake, a fishing lake and also a cemetery. The Common is a large park and also contains a wildlife centre, The Hawthorns. &lt;br />&lt;br />There is also a church called St.James Church and further away from Shirley towards Bassett there is a sports centre that contains an athletics track and a dry ski slope.   &lt;br />
Tom Stroud</content>
</page></content></entry>