<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-516000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-516000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-516000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-516000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-516000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412017</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-06T18:00:33.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T18:00:33.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-516000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Our Schools</title>
<content>25 years passes very quickly. On 1st July 1986 I was 16 years old and had just left De Brus Senior School. It no longer exists having been demolished in 2010, 30 years after it was built. The photograph of Skelton Church shows all that remains of the school premises, the Sports Hall which is now a community centre. Skelton has seen tremendous improvements over the last 25 years, more new homes and an increase in the Population. It remains a beautiful set of Skelton Villages separated from Saltburn by the lovely Skelton / Saltburn woods. Cleveland County was split into 4 unitary authorities in the 1990s, Skelton now belongs to the much smaller Redcar &amp; East Cleveland Council. The Co-op has modernised and is unrecognisable, it now concentrates on food. 25 years ago  it provided a Bank Cashier Service, a fresh butchers and haberdashery, all long gone. The Fish Shop, Chinese Takeaway and Harrisons Toy Shop have gone to be replaced by Pizza and Tanning Shops and an internet cafe.  Kath Chapman's DIY shop is now a home. There are no more telephone boxes in Skelton due, no doubt, to the meteoric appearance of mobile phones.  The Tattie field I used to cross to run to school is now occupied by the Church Hill estate, where I now live. The Old youth Club on the High Street has gone too, its land operates as a temporary car park for the High Street Shops.  Skelton remains 'God's little secret' a northern village with great character close to the North Yorkshire Moors and the Northern Beaches of Saltburn and Redcar. Many of the pupils that left school in 1985 still live here. Andrew Scott 12/05/2011
&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>