<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-44-36 GB-448000-360000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-44-36/GB-448000-360000-23.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-448000-360000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412001</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T17:51:32.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-448000-360000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23LANGUAGE IN MANSFIELD</title>
<content>Language constantly evolves and dictionaries are updated as "popular" words become part of everyday language. Unfortunately many swear words and vulgar terms have embedded themselves into the local language.  Adopted by youbng adults and passed down into the school children's vocabulary are words which we would have been punished for uttering in our childhood. F**k is now heard as integral parts of every conversation and more or less every sentence which is very uncomfortable to listen to - especially for the older generation.&lt;br />&lt;br />Children, teenagers and most young adults spend most of their time using mobile phones while walking around so are in their own world and oblivious to their surroundings. This heavy use of mobile phones has led to a new language called text speak: LOL=lots of laughs, gr8 = great, 2=to, 4=for, ?4u= I have a question for you. This all serves to diminish the English language and I wonder if we will be in danger of losing our local identities because of this new language.  Overall, the art of conversation is being lost for the most part and people seem reticent to speak to others in the street, particularly the younger generation, not even passing the time of day as they pass by each other.&lt;br />
Contribution by: Mrs Elizabeth Parker
</content>
</page></content></entry>