<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-20 GB-452000-201000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-20/GB-452000-201000-24.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-201000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>435149</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-05T17:52:59.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-05T17:52:58.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24A school day, 2011</title>
<content>

At 7.30am we get up and dressed and one of us chooses her prayers for the morning.&lt;br />&lt;br />Our schools start at 8.30 for some of us and 9am for others. We all have 15 minutes for our break. Sometimes we get extra play for lining up sensibly. Sometimes we get free time when we can draw or read a book or tracing.&lt;br />&lt;br />School subjects  include literacy, maths, ICT, science, PE and art. Some of us do Drama. Some of us have Golden Show and Tell, which is when people can bring things in to show others and talk about them. Sometimes it is something we have got for our birthday or something we found at the weekend. &lt;br />&lt;br />Sometimes we go on school trips with a picnic eg to Roald Dahl museum or Sulgrave Manor, a Tudor manor house near Banbury. We all have school dinners - they're good. On Friday we get fish and chips. On Wednesdays it's roast dinner.&lt;br />&lt;br />We all finish at 3pm. One of use is going to a new school soon where she will finish at 4pm. That seem late but we hope she will still be able to come to Brownies.&lt;br />&lt;br />Computers, 2011. We thought of lots and lots of things we use everyday which use computers. These were i-pods, i-phones, computers, ovens, microwaves, alarm clocks, TVs, Wii games, DS and playstations, X-boxes, mobile phones, cars, motorbikes, school buses, cameras, keyboards, MP3 players, Satnavs in cars and lorries, Smartboards at school, electric musical instruments and keyboards.&lt;br />&lt;br />3rd Cowley Brownies (URC), Oxford. July 2011.   </content>
</page></content></entry>