<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-27.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-27</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-27.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-27.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-27</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436837</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-10-13T17:16:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>27Village Industry</title>
<content>

There has been an increase in the number of businesses that are run from residents' homes in Ravensthorpe. This is due in part to the village being connected to broadband internet, a service which was finally introduced in 2006. Internet access is still slow however and there is currently a campaign to try and get the speed increased.&lt;br />&lt;br />The businesses come under 3 main types. &lt;br />&lt;br />Firstly, there are practical skills and services offered which include a small engineering firm, double glazed windows made and fitted, a sign maker, painter and decorator, chiropodist, curtain and dressmaker, beauty therapist, hairdresser, gardener, fencing contractor, builder and sales of garage supplies.&lt;br />&lt;br />Secondly, there are also individuals based at home who use the internet for sales and marketing, financial advisor, accountant, author, health and safety advisor. &lt;br />&lt;br />The third group are those who have a  work place elsewhere but can work from home for part of the week.&lt;br />&lt;br />This is in addition to the business premises industry of MB Motorsales, Torquemeters, Batten's Bootmakers, The Post Office, Ravensthorpe Nursery (plants), Hydraulic Component Services, a working farm, Town and Country Windows and The Chequers public house.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>