<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-40/GB-464000-408000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-40 GB-464000-408000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-40/GB-464000-408000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-40/GB-464000-408000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-408000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439787</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-408000</dblock_id>
<original_item>18</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Memories of Abbey Middle School</title>
<content>

I attended Abbey Middle School from approx 1979 to 1983. This is where I spent the best school years of my life. The Teachers I remember are Mr Tabarah, Mr Middleton, Mr Raper, Mr Wilson, Mr Barker, Mr Wall, Mrs Monks, Miss Allan, Mrs Fothergill and Mr Benniston the school caretaker. There was a old boarded up toilet block that was used untill they built indoor facilities.&lt;br />&lt;br /> I remember there were built in cuboards in each classroom and one of these had a hidden door inside, I was always led to believe that this led to a long corridor which was an escape route to the air raid shelters during the war which were situated beneath a hill to the right of the field behind the school, which was covered in trees.&lt;br />&lt;br /> The school itself had a lovely paraquet floor that was always varnished and kept clean. The corridor was in the shape of a square that went round the interior of the school and I remember that the central part of this square was not covered to be used as a indoor room, instead it had a aviery which housed a variety of birds such as parrots. Each year the school took us on various outings and trips to France. My father attended this school along with his siblings as did my sister before me. I believe that Abbey Middle school was closed down in 1995 and stood derelict for the next few years. It was finally demolished much to the sadness of many residents of Dunscroft village. The school was the heart of Dunscroft which can never be replaced. There now stands a new estate of houses built on the old school site and all that is left are distant memories.   &lt;br />&lt;br />
Contribution by: D.Dickman</content>
</page></content></entry>