<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-26.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-26</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-26.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-26.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-26</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436857</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:32:26.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:32:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>26Crabtree Pit Pocket Park</title>
<content>

Crabtree Pit is a small field (under 1 acre is size) on the edge of the village. It is reached by a green lane leading from the West Haddon Road. It belongs to the Parish Council and was long ago earmarked to be excavated for gravel, in the times when parishes were responsible for the upkeep of their own roads. When this responsibility passed to the County Council the land was rented to farmers, but in more recent times, because of the poor soil and the difficulty of access for machinery, it was used less and less. In 1999 the Parish Council decided that it should become a wildlife area and a place that villagers could visit. Thus the Crabtree Pocket Park Committee was formed and work began.&lt;br />&lt;br />It was decided that the park would have 3 distinct areas: woodland, meadow and a pond. &lt;br />&lt;br />Volunteers planted hundreds of trees and most flourished, to the extent that now we are having to coppice them to let in more light to allow a greater bio-diversity to flourish. This year we have received a grant from the Big Lottery Fund which has enabled us to buy a chain saw so that we can carry out the work. The grant also enabled us to buy and plant bluebells in some of the cleared areas.  Pathways have been cut through the trees, enabling visitors to enjoy the different species contained in the woodland area.&lt;br />&lt;br />The meadow area has been planted with natural wild flowers including snowdrops, cowslips, daffodils, yellow rattle, daisies and others. Every Autumn this area is cut and raked by volunteers, so that the flowers are not swamped by grass and the ground does not become to rich for the flowers to grow and multiply.&lt;br />&lt;br />The pond is not a natural one, but was dug out and filled. It is replenished by rainwater and is home to lilies, bullrushes and other plants.&lt;br />&lt;br />The lane from the road leading to the park is lined with snowdrops and aconites, which make  a splendid display in the late January and February. The entry gate has recently been altered to allow for wheelchair access.&lt;br />&lt;br />Within the park are a number of seats and a picnic bench, allowing the visitor to pause and enjoy the calm and peaceful setting, with views towards Guilsborough.&lt;br />&lt;br />Crabtree Pocket Park is an asset for both wildlife and villagers. Even in our village, set within beautiful countryside, the fact that there is a place of such tranquillity which is just a short stroll away is a blessing much appreciated.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>