<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-16/GB-472000-168000-16.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-47-16 GB-472000-168000-16</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-16/GB-472000-168000-16.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-47-16/GB-472000-168000-16.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-472000-168000-16</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436089</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T12:58:58.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T12:58:58.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-472000-168000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>16ECMWF</title>
<content>The European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts (ECMWF) is an intergovernmental organisation supported by 34 States. It provides weather services with medium-range forecasts of global weather (up to 15 days ahead), monthly forecasts, and seasonal forecasts. ECMWF's computer system at its headquarters in Reading, Shinfield Park, is one of the largest for meteorology worldwide and contains the world's largest archive of numerical weather prediction data. It runs the world's most sophisticated medium-range prediction model of the global atmosphere and oceans. &#xd;
&#xd;
ECMWF was established in 1975, in recognition of the need to pool the scientific and technical resources of Europe for the production of medium-range weather forecasts and of the economic and social benefits expected from it.&#xd;
&#xd;
National meteorological services use ECMWF's products for their own national duties, in particular to give early warning of potentially damaging severe weather. &#xd;
&#xd;
The ECMWF strategy puts the early warning of severe weather as its principal goal. Forecasts of severe weather events are vital to warn authorities and the public. The increased time gained by issuing accurate warnings of severe weather will be crucial to save lives, for instance by evacuating a large number of people from endangered areas (such as storm surges in the North Sea), or taking cautionary actions to avoid major threats to goods and services (such as extreme winds). &#xd;
&#xd;
ECMWF's monthly and seasonal forecasts provide early predictions of events such as heat waves, cold spells and droughts, as well as their impacts on sectors such as agriculture, energy and health. &#xd;
&#xd;
.   &lt;br /> Contribution by: Manfred Kloeppel</content>
</page></content></entry>