<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-36/GB-452000-363000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-45-36 GB-452000-363000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-36/GB-452000-363000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-45-36/GB-452000-363000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-452000-363000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412011</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-06T18:00:33.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T18:00:32.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-452000-363000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>212011 changes in Mansfield Woodhouse</title>
<content>Mansfield Woodhouse 2011&lt;br />&lt;br />Rural Landscapes&lt;br />&lt;br />Pleasley Vale has changed as the mill buildings are now mostly disused apart from some small manufacturing units. The area has been made accessible with footpaths and walks for the local community. In Mansfield Woodhouse, several new housing estates have been built on former farmland, particularly along Peafield Lane and the new Peafield Park has also been created on former waste land.&lt;br />&lt;br />Technology &lt;br />&lt;br />Mobile phone technology dominates communications, with most of this area having good reception from mobile phone masts of which there are many. Fibre optic cable or satellite dishes provide TV, broadband internet and phone service to many homes in this area. Social networking by text or Facebook and Twitter are widely used by all age groups. Shopping and all manner of retail items are often ordered via the internet and delivered speedily to homes. Digital TV has recently replaced analogue signal and High Definition picture is now widely available&lt;br />&lt;br />Society &lt;br />&lt;br />There are many opportunities for all ages to get together in Mansfield Woodhouse, with regular activities e.g. Summer Fair on Yeoman Park, Christmas Fair and Community band concerts and quizzes at Turner Hall. Many of the elderly population use battery operated mobility scooters to get around the area, visit family, shop and attend social events. Clothes are mostly casual and of manmade fibres making them easily laundered. Jeans are very popular everyday wear.&lt;br />&lt;br />Towns and Cities&lt;br />&lt;br />Many corner shops, grocery and bakers' shops have disappeared to be replaced with charity shops, hairdressers, beauty shops and betting shops. Morrisons  Supermarket and filling station dominates Mansfield Woodhouse centre. Asda and Tesco have also built large supermarkets  nearby.&lt;br />&lt;br />Work&lt;br />&lt;br />Only one pit remains now, and most of the coal mines have been regenerated into housing , light industry or country parks.  Pleasley Vale Mills are now occupied by small light manufacturing units. People have found new employment further afield, travelling to surrounding areas on a daily basis.&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>