<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-35.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-51 GB-464000-513000-35</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-35.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-51/GB-464000-513000-35.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-513000-35</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449117</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:25.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-513000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>35SUMMARY OF AREA</title>
<content>

The description of Block 04640513 written in 1986 is still largely accurate.  The area is predominantly rural with five small settlements: Charltons, Margove Park, Slapewath, Aysdale Gate and Stanghow.&lt;br />&lt;br />The arterial road bisecting the area is the A171 from Middlesbrough to Whitby and Scarborough.  The southern third of the block is all moorland.  This extends northwards to the A171 between Aysdale Gate and the Lockwood reservoir, with another block of moorland just to the north of the car park shown on the map at the top of Birk Brow.  Wooded valleys descend from the moorland to Charltons and Aysdale Gate with another wooded valley along the Lockwood Beck north of Lockwood Reservoir.  This is no longer used for water supply but is used for fishing. The land to the northeast of the A171 is predominantly farmland with some areas of woodland.  &lt;br />&lt;br />The Spa Mine, the Aysdale Gate Mine, the Slapewath Mine , the Spawood Mine and the Stanghow mine were all ironstone mines operating in the block in the 19th and early 20th centuries.   Some remains can be seen and local businesses are mainly based on their former sites.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Stephen Larkin</content>
</page></content></entry>