<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-37.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-27 GB-464000-270000-37</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-37.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-27/GB-464000-270000-37.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-464000-270000-37</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436855</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-09-16T14:25:11.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-16T14:25:11.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-464000-270000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>37Ravensthorpe and Coton Twenty Five Years On</title>
<content>

The village of Ravensthorpe is a quintessential English village, with a church, village hall, post office and pub. The current population of Ravensthorpe and Coton combined is 656 people with 273 occupied dwellings.&lt;br />&lt;br />Within a special landscape area, the undulating hills provide the village with stunning views in all directions. To the east, west and south the view is looking across open farm land but the best views are to the north where you look over Ravensthorpe reservoir towards the associated hamlet of Coton with its manor house and a small number of dwellings. A total area of 8926 hectares is covered by the two settlements.&lt;br />&lt;br />The reservoir is open for fishing and walking; it attracts wildfowl and a variety of other birds, flora and fauna. In addition to the rural landscape the village has a number of other green areas including a playing field, village green, allotments and in the last 25 years has gained two new public areas the pocket park and Top Ardles wood.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many existing businesses remain but the last 25 years have seen a diversification in employment in the village with local businesses being established at home or in small premises enabled through the internet. Ravensthorpe and Coton are not self-sufficient having to rely on the neighbouring villages for health care and schooling.&lt;br />&lt;br />A 1986 time traveller arriving in Ravensthorpe in 2011 would recognise a lot of the village which has seen a few changes. Most development has been infill of gardens or extensions to already large homes. The village population has doubled in size since 1961 but most of these housing developments were completed in the 60s, 70s and early 80s. The main development has been of affordable homes in the 90s and late 00s, stimulated by concerned that all new developments have created a dominance of executive sized homes.&lt;br />&lt;br />The village has a good sense of community with several social groups such as Womens Institute and well used amenities such as village hall, post office and pub. It has many village events such as fete, garden open days including a scrap challenge, and other fund raising events such as bingo and quizzes, making it a social place to live.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ravensthorpe WI</content>
</page></content></entry>