<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-99/GB-492000-99000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-49-99 GB-492000-99000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-99/GB-492000-99000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-49-99/GB-492000-99000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-492000-99000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412031</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-06T18:07:18.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T18:07:18.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-492000-99000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Bognor Regis in 2011</title>
<content>Bognor has the liveliest nightlife in west sussex owing to its 3 nightclubs and many pubs and bars. The 3 nightclubs are: Club Vision (the biggest one, previously known as Sheiks up to late 2010), Club Shine and Ground Zero many people pre drink at the Hatters inn ( a short 2 min walk away from Vision)  the unicorn or the William Hardwicke before going on to the nightclubs, this lively nightlife comes at a price however as there is always a heavy police presence on friday and saturday nights to deter crime. &lt;br />&lt;br />Bognor is well known for its large amount of eastern european immagrants and is known locally by the nickname "Polski Regis" as a result. There are a few Polish shops selling eastern european goods and it is very common to hear polish being spoken on the streets of Bognor.&lt;br />&lt;br />Bognor was recently mentioned on the news as having one of the worst unemployment rates in west sussex and as a result, the local "Jobcentre plus" is always busy.&lt;br />&lt;br />Bognor has a train station with 3 platforms and is the end of the line for all trains arriving in Bognor, most commuters have to change trains at Barnham due to the fact that Bognor station is a final stop station and is not connected directly to the main lines to London and Portsmouth.&lt;br />&lt;br />Bognor is a suntrap and as a result enjoys a heavy tourist presence in the summer helped by the local Butlins holiday park. 
&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>