<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-46-38 GB-468000-387000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-46-38/GB-468000-387000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-468000-387000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447115</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-25T16:16:21.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-25T16:16:21.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-468000-387000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Restoration of Chapel House</title>
<content>

Chapel House was Grade II listed before the purchase by the Ruff family, who found it in poor state and restored it to habitable condition, although needing to remove the distressed concrete floors of the back upper rooms and the rotten oak beams beneath them.  Their research could not trace the building back before the 1850s, but Malcolm Dolby of Bassetlaw Museum dated it to before 1840 through the presence of the concrete floors (due to government requisitions of wood for wars) and the apparent age of the worn tiling and brickwork.  No better proof of age was found.  Two ranges from the kitchen and the room behind it, were removed for restoration by the local blacksmith but were stolen along with other metal goods.  In digging to install the drainage, a cobbled path and small yard were exposed a foot or so down across the front of the house.  This was replaced by the hexagonal tiles that had to be removed from the kitchen to level up the floors (due to the raised levels of the external pavement above the original).  The ground floor tiles were based on a couple of feet of sand, which was on top of a layer of crushed limestone and cobbles - a natural damp barrier.  When the upper concrete floors were dropped, with great difficulty, dried wheat heads were exposed from within the concrete in perfect condition.  The lowered floor of the pork curing room (now the utility room at the back of the house) was very damp and on removal of part of it, a terrible smell emerged the blood etc had been drained into a soak-away in the floor.  Concrete, shallow sinks were on a shelf along the outside walls.  These were heavy to remove and became planters in the garden.  A brick garage was built in the garden and a conservatory on the eastside.&lt;br />&lt;br />A lady whose grandparents had been employees of the Duke of Portland and who had lived in the house up to 1926 visited during the restoration.  She recalled a gate to a  well in the yard that is now the back garden of the first bungalow on Job Lane and damson, lilac and apple trees still in the garden (very overgrown - had to be cleared).  The site had been split on being originally auctioned in 1983, as it originally was an L-shape, including where the Job Lane bungalow was built - the outside privy was on that site.  Scythe blades were found against the trees, left by Jim Collishaw, the previous tenant, to rust gently over winter, after which they would have been polished up for the next season's "opening up" of the margins of fields around Mattersey.  Jim was such a regular customer of the Blacksmith's Arms on Main Street that the brewery awarded him a pint a night for life when he was 70 and his picture hung over the bar for many years.  The Ruff family moved to the Old Chapel in 1996.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Mrs M Ruff</content>
</page></content></entry>