<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-18/GB-524000-180000-9.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-52-18 GB-524000-180000-9</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-18/GB-524000-180000-9.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-18/GB-524000-180000-9.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-524000-180000-9</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449153</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-524000-180000</dblock_id>
<original_item>7</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>09Maida Vale, much improved.</title>
<content>

Has Maida Vale changed in 25 years? The trees are the same but the demographic is different and it's far busier with more cafes and late night shops including a Starbucks, and a cinema!&lt;br />&lt;br />Maida Vale underground station was refurbished keeping its original features.&lt;br />&lt;br />Wide, previously imposing, London plane tree lined avenues are now largely obscured by two additional lines of parked cars down the centre. The many red brick, early 20th C, mansion blocks of privately owned flats are spruced up with many rented out by their owners at phenomenally high prices (600 pounds a week for 3 bedroom flats). This has impacted on the community now more transient and altered - far younger and often Antipodean Arabic or Indian. The current value of private property in W9 has rocketed by approximately x 7. Three bedroom flats sell for over 700,000 pounds. However, Maida Vale also has many blocks of social housing hence a hugely cosmopolitan diverse population, shops and cafes. In 1986 I knew many of my neighbours, now I know few. The area has gone 'up market' perhaps due to its proximity well heeled Little Venice and St.John's Wood.&lt;br />&lt;br />The cycle track in Paddington Recreation Ground is no more. The park underwent a multi million pound 'makeover' in 1990, to boast a modern running track, hockey and football pitches,cricket nets, tennis courts floodlit at night plus indoor and outdoor gyms, playgrounds, picnic areas as well as a huge central grass "field" enjoyed in the summer by the local community. It is well used by keep fitters.&lt;br />&lt;br />BBC sound studios remain in Delaware Road but rumour has it they will vacate them in due course.&lt;br />&lt;br />Many side, residential roads in the area have been designated for one way traffic, making life much quieter in terms of traffic noise and pollution- a huge improvement. A recent development is the sound of home grocery delivery vans - Tesco, Ocado, Waitrose, Sainsbury's arriving either early morning or in the evening for those who use on-line shopping.&lt;br />&lt;br />We recycle more than we used to and the council collects mixed recycled waste once a week from outside our building and several times a day from large black bins at either end of the road. Locally we can recycle small electrical goods, clothes, glass, paper in separated bins.&lt;br />&lt;br />Public transport in this area is far better than it was. Frequent buses to all corners of London aside from NE and tubes are faster and more reliable if more expensive than they were.&lt;br />&lt;br />.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Ruth Rosenthal</content>
</page></content></entry>