<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-19/GB-540000-195000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-19 GB-540000-195000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-19/GB-540000-195000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-19/GB-540000-195000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-540000-195000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447471</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-28T18:00:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-26T14:41:31.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-540000-195000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21How Loughton has changed</title>
<content>

Loughton has changed dramatically since 1986. I have lived through its change from a small rural village to a become a wealthy suburb and centre of nightlife. There has been an influx of money from the City and entrpreneurs or from celebrity residents like footballers and clubowners. Many of the houses have been expanded or completely rebuilt twice the size they started. Sadly high fashion houses and chains have replaced the old traditional family shops in the high street. The shock of getting a supermarket like Presto is long forgotten; it became Safeway and that in turn became Morrisons and we now we another supermarket as well. The council moved to Epping and its old offices pulled down with a huge new Sainsbury was built in its place. The post office became a pub and the other pubs became restautrants and clubs. People come from miles around to spend an evening in Loughton. The high street has become a permanent traffic jam with big 4x4s with private plates and the people are younger, richer, busier and brasher than they were in 1986. On the bright side,the forest remians timeless as ever and local amenities are much improved. The old swimming pool has become a modern leisure centre, the Olympics have seen a cycle centre and white-water course appear neaby, and our churches have been modernised; St Johns redecorated inside, The Methodist chrch given a modern class frontage and St Mary's rebuilt to be the centre of the town.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>