<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-43/GB-504000-435000-9.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-50-43 GB-504000-435000-9</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-43/GB-504000-435000-9.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-43/GB-504000-435000-9.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-504000-435000-9</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412365</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T20:43:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-504000-435000</dblock_id>
<original_item>7</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>09Thearne / Wawne Ferry</title>
<content>

The Primitive Methodist Chapel in Thearne was built in 1867. After it closed it became a traditional design studio and then a computer-aided design studio. Around 2007 it was converted into a private house by Dave Meakin, a builder who lives in Thearne. He also carried major renovation work on Hall Farm, Thearne and the coach house of Thearne Hall.&lt;br />&lt;br />      Wawne Ferry over the River Hull was operated from the Windham Arms Public House on the Wawne side of the river. The publican and ferryman after 1909 was Donald Brewer. He operated a small punt for foot passengers and cyclists and a pontoon (or raft) that was hauled across the river by chains and used to transport horse drawn vehicles and cars. Foot passengers paid 1d, cyclists 2d and the owners of small cars 6d. People arriving on the Thearne bank of the river had to shout "boat" to get his attention! The opening of a new bridge by Hull Corporation over the River Hull on the new ly constructed Sutton Road in July 1937 probably had an adverse effect on ferry takings. The new bridge was less than three miles downstream of the ferry. Although Wawne Ferry continued to be operated by an increasingly elderly Donald  Brewer, now in his seventies, by 1944 the it was being done by Brewer's nephew Harold Walker. In July 1946 Walker sold the Windham Arms and the ferry rights to Moors and Robson's Brewery in Hull for £3000 and this was finalised in a conveyance dated 19th August 1946.. It was around this time (late August 1946) that the eight hundred year old ferry ceased to operate. The minutes of Woodmansey Parish Council (18th December 1946) held in the East Riding Archive show that protests about the closure of the ferry had already begun by the end of 1946. The chairman of Woodmansey Parish Council was Ronald Dixon who lived at Thearne Hall. He wrote to Moors and Robsons Brewery to complain about the closure of the ferry but was told that the ferry  boat was no longer safe to use and that the cost of repairing or replacing it was too excessive in view of the revenue it would generate. Although an ardent campaigner on behalf of the ferry even Ronald Dixon had to admit that "there was no known law to force a ferry service". Dixon was also a member of Beverley Rural District Council and tried, unsuccessfully, to get them  involved in restoring Wawne Ferry. Neither was East Riding County Council willing to take responsibility for what they considered to be the duty of Moors and Robsons to restore a 'public' ferry service. They wrote to the brewery in January 1948 to tell them this but the brewery's legal advisers seem to have taken the view that "no obligation rested on them or their tenant to maintain the ferry."  &lt;br />&lt;br />The late 1940s were a time of crisis for Britain's smaller river ferries and in 1948 the Ferries Committee of the Ministry of Transport issued a detailed r  eport on the situation. This investigation of thirteen smaller river ferries showed that by 1947 eight of them were no longer operating. Wawne Ferry like many of the others probably became a victim of falling revenue (likely to have been less than £2 a week), of rising maintenance costs and the reluctance of the new tenant of the Windham Arms Public House to operate it during the hours of 6am to 10pm for little reward.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Martin Limon
</content>
</page></content></entry>