<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-55-21/GB-552000-213000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-55-21 GB-552000-213000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-55-21/GB-552000-213000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-55-21/GB-552000-213000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-552000-213000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420835</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-08-15T16:11:50.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-15T12:37:51.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-552000-213000</dblock_id>
<original_item>5</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Our School 2011</title>
<content>

Our school is 112 years old.  The main building has a Victorian front.  There is a block behind built in the sixties and a demountable hut added in the 2000s.  A new hall and 2 additional classrooms were added in1994. In 2010 a new computer room was built which has 30 personal computers for the children to use.  Each class uses the computers twice a week the rest of the time we write on paper usually in books.&lt;br />&lt;br />There are around 210 children who attend the school aged between 4 and 11.  There are 7 classes each with about 30 children.  There are 7 full time teachers and 2 part time, each class has at least one learning support assistant.  We have a headteacher, a site manager, and three administrational staff, cleaners, mid-day assistants and two kitchen staff.  In 2009 the preschool moved from the village hall to a purpose built hut next to the swimming pool.&lt;br />&lt;br />We have lots of different clubs in school and after school including football, bedazzle (performing arts), street dance, netball, a choir, dodgeball, multi skills sports club, orienteering, music lessons, gardening and computer club.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Class 2</content>
</page></content></entry>