<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-20.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-15 GB-544000-153000-20</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-20.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-20.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-153000-20</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449163</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:29.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:29.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-153000</dblock_id>
<original_item>6</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>20Westerham's Famous Formers...</title>
<content>

JOHN FRITH (1503-1533) - Son of Westerham innkeeper Richard Frith, John Frith was educated at Eton and Cambridge and was appointed by Wolsey as a junior canon at Oxford. He helped to translate the New Testament from Latin into English. His reformist views were considered heretical and he was imprisoned in the Tower of London. At age 30 he was publicly burned at the stake as a heretic in Smithfield. St Mary's church contains the font in which he was baptised and a memorial window to him by Edward Burne-Jones&lt;br />&lt;br />JAMES WOLFE (1727-1759) - James Wolfe joined the army at 13 and became a celebrated army officer, famous for his leadership and the way he reformed army training. As General Wolfe he was victorious over the French at Quebec, Canada, though he wasn't to survive the fight. The 250th anniversary of the battle that secured Canada for the Crown was commemorated in the Westerham Wolfe Weekend in September 2009. Visit Quebec House w here he lived and St Mary's church to see the font in which he was baptised and Squerryes Court, home of his close boyhood friend George Warde. &lt;br />&lt;br />WINSTON CHURCHILL (1874-1965) - First Lord of the Admiralty during the First World War. British Prime Minister during World War II and again in the 1950's. Churchill lived at nearby Chartwell with his family from 1922 until his death. As well as an international statesman, Churchill was also a prolific writer of books and an artist. Don't miss the statue on The Green by Oscar Nemon and make time for a visit to Chartwell.&lt;br />&lt;br />COLONEL SIR FRANCIS YOUNGHUSBAND, KCSI, KCIE (1863-1942) - In 1921, at the age of 58,  Francis Younghusband came to live at Currant Hill in Westerham with his wife Helen and daughter Eileen. Younghusband was a fearless explorer and has been dubbed the last great imperial adventurer. As a 24- year-old officer given ‘leave’ by the British Army in India, he found and charted a new route across the vast Gobi desert and descended the supposedly impassable Mustagh Pass. The Royal Geographical Society honoured him with a Gold Medal and made him their youngest-ever member.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Andy McCormick/visitwesterham.org.uk</content>
</page></content></entry>