<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-56-12/GB-568000-129000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-56-12 GB-568000-129000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-56-12/GB-568000-129000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-56-12/GB-568000-129000-21.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-568000-129000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412661</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:12.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-15T14:15:21.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-568000-129000</dblock_id>
<original_item>16</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Bewl Bridge Reservoir 1937-1956.</title>
<content>

In 1937 my parents built Hook House as it is now known.  The water that laps the front of the house covers what was a nine acre field, which at the bottom had the Bewl river flowing, and an old marl pit in it.  When first built the house was named Nine Acres and the attached farm was called Beale's Barn Farm, which the whole property was called at the time of purchase.  The barn is still to be seen and the cottage which was the farmhouse is now part of Bewl Water.  There was no mains water of electricity until after WW2.   The whole farm was some 86 acres with a large amount of ancient woodland much of which can also still be seen.  During the war the farm was a training ground for land-girls, and German POWs would be used to help out on the farm.  My two brothers were born in Hook House and I grew up there.  A Canadian artillery battery were briefly stationed there before D day. There was a pedigree Friesan herd of milking cows called the Betron Herd . I remember the German bombers flying to London and the fires of London could be seen as a glow in the sky. We all left there in 1956.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: David Hawken
</content>
</page></content></entry>