<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-57-14/GB-576000-141000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-57-14 GB-576000-141000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-57-14/GB-576000-141000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-57-14/GB-576000-141000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-576000-141000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448071</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:14.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-576000-141000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Staplehurst - Businesses &amp; Services - Continuity &amp; Change</title>
<content>

Here are some examples of continuity and change in local businesses and services since the 1980s. They are drawn from research by Christopher Sharp, a Time2Give volunteer at Staplehurst Library: Staplehurst Library is still in the same premises in the Parade, but was refurbished in 2006. As well as giving free access to books, Staplehurst Library has a much expanded range of services and activities: Children's activities include baby rhyme time, storytime and craft sessions. The library lends DVDs and audio material, for a small charge. There is free access to computers with internet facilities. There is support for local reading groups and opportunities to volunteer, eg. as a computer buddy. Nat West is now the only bank in the Parade. The Supermarket, formerly Liptons, then Londis, is now a Spar. The village now has four pubs rather than six. They are The Pride of Kent, The Bell, The King's Head &amp; The Railway Tavern. The Post Office in the High St survived a temporary closure in 2010. However, there is no longer a Post Office outlet in Station Rd. The Bower Dental Service, in the High St is an example of a practice that was established in 1986. Peter Jones, The Optician, also in the High St, is an example of long-running local business, (established in neighbouring Cranbrook in 1978.) In September this year, D.K. Holdings Ltd and Sainsbury's used the Youth Club to exhibit proposals to provide a new bespoke factory for D.K. Holdings and a new Sainsbury's store on the Station Rd industrial estate.  There is no doubt that these proposals could be a major influence in the further development of Staplehurst. Staplehurst continues to flourish in 2011. Here's to the next 25 years in 2036!   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>