<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-24/GB-532000-243000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-53-24 GB-532000-243000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-24/GB-532000-243000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-24/GB-532000-243000-22.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-532000-243000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439791</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:07.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-532000-243000</dblock_id>
<original_item>3</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Kneesworth</title>
<content>

You enter Kneesworth by the A1198 or The Causeway or Chestnut Lane.  There has been infilling along the road with houses where the old pub car parks were.  The reservoir is across the fields.&lt;br />&lt;br /> In Kneesworth you can find an Indian Restaurant which was the Red Lion public house and in the barn adjacent is a mixture of things for sale from children and baby clothes, jewellery, second hand retro adult clothes and carpets.  Across the road is a shop that sells wedding dresses, occasion wear and prom dresses.  There is a Farm Shop along Chestnut Lane.  A large employer of local people is Kneesworth House Hospital providing care and treatment, with differing levels of security for people with mental illness or learning disabilities.&lt;br />&lt;br />The bus service is just once every two hours to Royston and once a day to Cambridge, Monday to Saturday only, people living in Kneesworth rely on having a car. We have a telephone box on the A1198 an d a post-box that is collected once a day, Monday to Saturday.  The mobile phone networks connections are poor for most providers and Broadband is slow at 100mbps.The rubbish and recycling is collected fortnightly.&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Anon</content>
</page></content></entry>