<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-15 GB-544000-153000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-22.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-153000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449161</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:29.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:29.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-153000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22About Our Area</title>
<content>

Westerham is a town for all seasons. &lt;br />&lt;br />The village of Westerham has evolved for more than 1000 years from "Domesday and Pilgrims Way, to Motorway", into the town it is today. Close to London and the M25, Westerham is privileged to be surrounded by woodlands and open space, and seems to be built on "on a hill in a valley". Over the centuries, a variety of talented and famous people have been drawn to live in Westerham. Their legacy is here for us to enjoy. Westerham today is a lively town with lots to do, many unusual shops - and wonderful places to eat and drink.&lt;br />&lt;br />Westerham has so many different facets that there is truly something for everyone to enjoy, observe or get involved with. We are very fortunate to have a number of wonderful buildings, old and new, around which the community can thrive.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />Our Stately Homes attract visitors whilst our Schools and Churches cater for locals: the Hall and of course our wonderful cafes and restaurants allow friends, family and strangers to meet and enjoy the atmosphere. We have an excellent local economy, good transport links, fine services, and compared to many, are fairly affluent.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />But it is in the people who dedicate time and effort to the diverse groups, organised or occasional, formal or irregular, that Westerham excels. The rich history of its inhabitants nurtures a deep affection for our town&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Westerham Town Partnership</content>
</page></content></entry>