<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-177000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-17 GB-544000-177000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-177000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-177000-21.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-177000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412377</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2013-08-13T14:49:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T20:51:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-177000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21My home and life in Abbey Wood on the Co-op estate.</title>
<content>

My husband and I live in a Victorian terrace house in Congress road, on the Co-op estate. We have redecorated and modernised our house but still have a downstairs bathroom. I moved here in 2003 from Hastings, I moved here for work, after graduating from Bar school. I own the house. The street has changed over the last 8 years, it was mostly white working class, with a few professionals and some ethnic people, over the years there has been a large increase in African immigrants moving into the area. The street was always clean, quiet and friendly and I always felt safe here, this is changing a bit for the worse, which is very sad and I hope this does not continue. I still love living here, although my enjoyment has decreased due to the above mentioned decline. The street is still quite close knit and friendly between the residents that have been here longer, we tend to look out for each other and this helps to reduce crime and anti-social behaviour. The st reet and the neighbouring streets are very pretty with cherry trees along the pavement and most of the houses and gardens are well kept. I have not suffered any serious crime since living here, other than theft from my motorcycle and attempted theft of the same a few years ago, which were committed by a small street gang, which stopped after a year. It is great living so close to the Station and the bus service is super but it is a shame that nice houses are never built here, just more social housing, when we are already saturated with social houses around us, I am worried that Abbey Wood will just become an undesirable ghetto like Thamesmead, Plumstead and Woolwich. The main street is no longer nice as it’s full of horrible fast food shops and 2 massive betting shops, which attract undesirable people so it’s no longer clean and safe. I hope that Crossrail will attract more desirable people to the area.&lt;br />&lt;br />I met my husband in 2005, we married in 200  7, he moved from North London and drives HGVs for the Council. We are in our 40s and do not have children. We both ride motorcycles and I own a Trike as well. We also own a Motor Home, which we store in the lovely Campsite at the top of our street. There is a strong local motorcycle community in this area. Mostly we socialise outside of the area, attending bike &amp; rockabilly events in central London and all over the UK. There is nowhere to socialise locally due to the ethnic mix and the local pubs are not nice, there are no nice restaurants in the area. If the area does not continue to decline but improves, then we would like to stay here as it still maintains it’s friendly, sense of community atmosphere, amongst the longer standing residents; it would be a shame if this little ‘village’ is allowed to be destroyed further and we are forced to move.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>