<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-25 GB-544000-258000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-23.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-258000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436159</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T15:23:07.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T15:23:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-258000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Lifecraft in Cambridge</title>
<content>Lifecraft&#xd;
Lifecraft started in 1993 at a time when there were very few support groups in Cambridge. Today there are approximately 400 members, and 60% of the management committee are members.  Lifecraft is a self-help organisation for adults who have had or are suffering from mental health issues. Lifecraft runs group activities such as poetry, arts, music, social, women's group, meditation, comedy, computer skills, writing activities. It also provides free counselling and a phone support line. The creative writing and poetry group provides people with the opportunity for self-expression and to write their own books. We have our own anthology, and we can write about what they like. Art exhibitions, poetry presentations and music help to raise funds. We are currently designing our own calendar and cards.  Lifecraft has a website and an online shop, plus some members have their own blog. We have also received funding from Comic Relief, and were winners of the Department of Health Voluntary Sector Mental Health Award. Members feel that it's well run and provides a safe haven. Members updated this information as part of a BBC Domesday Reloaded workshop.&#xd;
   &lt;br />
Lifecraft Members</content>
</page></content></entry>