<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-43.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-17 GB-540000-174000-43</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-43.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-43.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-540000-174000-43</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420831</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-08-15T16:11:48.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-15T12:37:50.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-540000-174000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>43A Day in the Life</title>
<content>

When I got up this morning I can't  remember what I did but I proprably watched telly and went on the computer but I Then  at 10:45 we had to take Jacob to gymnastics. Next we came home for 15 minute and then rushed back to get him. After that we zoomed home really fast because it was the day of the summer fair. When we got home my brother and I got changed.&lt;br />&lt;br />When we got there I saw Robyn in her SpongeBob Square pants clothes. Then I did a raffle and felt a bit annoyed because I won 3 bottles of fizzy pop but I was only allowed 2 so I had to give 1 back. Then Scarlett came and ran to see us. I won 1 sweet doing can you knock over the cans. After that I went on the monkey bars and felt happy because I can't reach them in the junior playground, and I was in the infant playground. &lt;br />&lt;br />Next dad came over to me and said I had 2 minutes left and I felt angry because I'd only had 30 minutes. So I ran onto the field and did 1 more thing. The thing I did was a raffle and I won a little toy cow that was as small as my hand!&lt;br />&lt;br />Afterwards we walked home quickly because we needed to get some food. After a while we dropped Jacob at karate but he said he couldn't go in because his knee really hurt. So then we went into the Glades and down to the newsagents to get some sweets for my brother and me and I was happy.&lt;br />&lt;br />Next Dad said he wanted to go to the bank but it was closed. So then we headed towards the car but we heard music so we went to listen and found out that it was 3 men, 1 was playing a trumpet and 2 were playing accordions so we put money in their case. Jacob said he thought they were from France and Dad said he thought Jacob was right. Then we went home and got changed for gymnastics and my friend took me there. At gym I saw my friends called Yasmine and Belle. I also did balances with my partner called Hannah and we worked really hard so I was out of breath. After 3 hours I took my friend home but mum drove Yasmine to our house so we had to go back again to her house then back to our house again!&lt;br />&lt;br />After that I had I had to eat my tea really quickly because we were going to my mum's concert. My mum used to be in an orchestra but she stopped so she wanted to go to see how everyone   was doing. There was a young pianist who was invited to do a solo. Then I got really tired. I fell asleep because it was late. The orchestra music was soothing so I fell asleep. At the end we went home and got straight into bed.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Pupil of Montbelle</content>
</page></content></entry>