<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-174000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-17 GB-544000-174000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-174000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-544000-174000-19.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-174000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412375</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-09T20:51:24.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T20:51:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-174000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Trade - 2011</title>
<content>

Welling's largest trade stores consist of a newly opened Tesco Superstore at the Bexleyheath end of town where John Newton Court used to stand with it's original range of restaurants and smaller Tesco store on the site.  Opposite, a large Morrison's store stands on the site of what was Co-op for as long as I can remember (1970s at least).&lt;br />&lt;br />The high street has a large range of smaller shops consisting of furniture; carpet; florists; shoe shops; newsagents and Nuxley Toys, which has been there since the 70s along with a large number of pound stores and newer nail bars.  The high street has a large number of welcoming cafes and pubs, the largest being The New Cross Turnpike, situated close to the centre of the street. Welling also offers a large number of popular restaurants covering all world tastes and are a high point for those in the community having a night out.&lt;br />&lt;br />Woolworths which was a popular store and st ood at the center of the High Street near the junction with Upper Wickham Lane closed a few years ago when the whole company went bust and is now a large carpet store.&lt;br />&lt;br />The highstreet also has a large number of local estate agents and popular card shops and bakeries.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>