<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-30/GB-500000-306000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-50-30 GB-500000-306000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-30/GB-500000-306000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-50-30/GB-500000-306000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-500000-306000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436111</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T12:59:04.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T12:59:04.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-500000-306000</dblock_id>
<original_item>12</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Education in Stamford</title>
<content>

In 1987 the two state secondary schools amalgamated and became the Queen Eleanor School on the Fane School split site. Eventually new blocks were built to house technology and more classrooms so the school could be housed on one site.  The school's south site was sold for housing.  After the BBC filmed the classic serial "Middlemarch" at Stamford, some Year 9 pupils from Queen Eleanor School did follow-up work based on the programme and were interviewed for the BBC Radio 4 programme "Kaleidoscope". A tape of the programme was given to the Stamford Museum together with work produced during the project. Unfortunately, the Museum closed in June 2011.  At the time of writing there is a bid in the town to save the museum. &#xd;
&#xd;
Lincolnshire County Council continued to purchase places for a small number of secondary age pupils at the Stamford Endowed Schools (Stamford School and Stamford High School).  This practice ended in 2011. Queen Eleanor School is set to become an academy in September 2011 in collaboration with the Deepings School in the nearby village of Deeping St James.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Retired teacher</content>
</page></content></entry>