<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-25/GB-524000-255000-3.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-52-25 GB-524000-255000-3</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-25/GB-524000-255000-3.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-52-25/GB-524000-255000-3.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-524000-255000-3</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448063</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:13.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-524000-255000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>03Little Gransden</title>
<content>

Since 1986 about 9 older properties (including some prefabricated huts that survived from World War II accommodation) have been demolished and some 30 houses have been built. The older part of the village has been designated a conservation area. The church and village hall continue to flourish: the village hall provides for yoga, ballroom dancing, dance exercise, bowls, badminton, mothers and toddlers, and drama. In the early 1990s Cambridge Gliding Club moved to the World War II airfield, from where it continues to operate. A second airfield also operates in the village. After 70 years a the local coach operator relocated to another village in 2011. Even fewer residents are involved in agriculture than in 1986 - most work in Cambridge and other nearby towns and  in London, and several work from home. There are no cattle in the village now - there are a few sheep from time to time, alpacas and horses - but several residents have gone with the fashion for keeping poultry. Public transport and services such as the mobile library  have been reduced since 1986 - people are even more dependent on the car for travel. Over the past five years or so many residents have tried to save energy in their homes by improving insulation and installing solar panels.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>