<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-24.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-17 GB-540000-174000-24</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-24.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-24.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-540000-174000-24</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>414971</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-07-04T14:23:15.000Z</updated><published>2011-07-04T14:23:15.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-540000-174000</dblock_id>
<original_item>9</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>24A day in the life</title>
<content>

A day in the life&lt;br />&lt;br />I woke up at 7:00am and went downstairs to have my breakfast.&lt;br />&lt;br />Then I rushed upstairs to get washed and dressed. I was excited because today was the Summer Fair and Chloe’s birthday party in my class.&lt;br />&lt;br />After that we went shopping which I found a bit boring. I got a pair of cute hairclips, which I could wear to school so it wasn’t so bad.&lt;br />&lt;br />At home I had some lunch and got ready for the Summer Fair. I was getting nervous and excited because I was wondering if I was going to win the raffle but they had our number so I didn’t matter.&lt;br />&lt;br />At the Summer Fair I ran to the first thing I saw which was the ball pit, that was fun and I won a prize! Next I went on the tombola and I won a bottle of wine, my mum gave me some money to go on more stalls, while my mum was drinking a glass of Pimms.&lt;br />&lt;br />I had a very good time at the Summer Fair, but I had to go to Chloe’s party.&#xd; 
When I arrived at the party, I was excited to find everybody on the bouncy castle, I kicked off my shoes and ran on to the bouncy castle.&lt;br />&lt;br />It was good fun on their bouncy castle, but it was time tea and I was hungry. I had sandwiches and some different types of crisps, which tasted cheesy and spicy.&lt;br />&lt;br />Soon it was time to go home and mum arrived to pick me up, I said to her “I’ve had a good time but I’m tired now!” Mum and I walked home and I said to her “I wonder if I have won anything in the raffle.”&lt;br />&lt;br />Once I was at home, I watched television until it was time for bed-today was very busy and I had enjoyed it.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Pupil-Montbelle School</content>
</page></content></entry>