<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-53-34 GB-532000-342000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-532000-342000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412211</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-06-15T14:37:25.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T11:47:03.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-532000-342000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Boston United hit hard times</title>
<content>

Boston United have been demoted to the Blue Square North Division. &lt;br />&lt;br />The Pilgrims lost their Football League status last season (2006),  but received a further demotion at the Blue Square Premier's annual general meeting. &lt;br />&lt;br />The decision, which means a reprieve from relegation for Altrincham, results from Boston's financial problems. &lt;br />&lt;br />Blue Square Premier chief executive John Moules said: "They're in breach of certain rules, it was felt Blue Square North was the best place for them." &lt;br />&lt;br />Boston were given a 10-point deduction to compound their relegation from the Football League as they went into administration. &lt;br />&lt;br />The terms of the Company Voluntary Liquidation entered into by Boston to go into administration, are behind the club's demotion. &lt;br />&lt;br />Moules said: "The Inland Revenue put a caveat on that CVA that Boston could not pay football creditors. &lt;br />&lt;br />"That breaks Football Association, Football League and Football Conference rules and regulations. &lt;br />&lt;br />"We're giving Boston the opportunity to re-establish themselves as a leading club outside the Football League. &lt;br />&lt;br />"They believe the decision we have made is fair and just, and they are not going to appeal." &lt;br />&lt;br />"We had meetings all day on Friday with Boston United and then informed Altrincham that they were staying up." &lt;br />&lt;br />Boston's financial problems led to charges for former manager Steve Evans and ex-chairman Pat Malkinson of conspiracy to cheat the public revenue. &lt;br />&lt;br />Evans was given a one-year prison sentence, suspended for two years after admitting the offence, Malkinson was given a two-year suspended sentence after admitting a similar offence.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />Source BBC News website;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>