<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-58-21/GB-580000-219000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-58-21 GB-580000-219000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-58-21/GB-580000-219000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-58-21/GB-580000-219000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-580000-219000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>439793</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-10-10T15:55:08.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-10T15:55:07.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-580000-219000</dblock_id>
<original_item>4</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Valentine House (previously The Silver End Hotel)</title>
<content>

In 2000 the Silver End Hotel was converted into a Private residential care home. Run by Atlantic Healthcare Ltd. It provides accommodation for 47 residents.&lt;br />&lt;br />The home has three floors that are accessed by a passenger lift, and residents are accommodated in single bedrooms, all with ensuite facilities.&lt;br />&lt;br />Facilities include lounge areas on all three floors, a large dining room, a number of bathrooms (some with assisted bathing facilities), and a secure garden area with seating, allowing our residents to walk outside safely.&lt;br />&lt;br /> The home is registered to provide 24-hour personal care and support for up to 38 older people (over the age of 65), with or without dementia and 9 adults with learning disabilities.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Residents with or without Dementia are housed within three units; the Primrose, Poppy and Amelia wings.&lt;br />&lt;br /> Residents with learning disabilities are housed within the Willows unit.&#xd;
&#xd;
 Valentine House has the benefit of its own Activities Coordinator who identifies the hobbies and interest of residents and devises individual activity programmes as well as arranging group activities. Activities include Bingo, Quizzes, Arts &amp;#38; Crafts, a Dementia Therapy programme and sing-a-longs. In-house entertainment is also arranged together with outings. PAT dogs visit weekly.&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Contribution by: ken brown</content>
</page></content></entry>