<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-19.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-15 GB-544000-153000-19</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-19.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-15/GB-544000-153000-19.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-153000-19</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>449157</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-153000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>19Westerham Festival, 2-11 September, 2011</title>
<content>

The 2011 Westerham Festival hosted a variety of events - screenings, walks, talks and a brewery open evening - culminating in the Scarecrows and Soldiers weekend:&lt;br />&lt;br />The Scarecrows and Soldiers weekend captured the imagination of the people of Westerham. Photographers recorded almost 100 scarecrows around the town.  The task for the judges was difficult, with so much creativity and effort being put into making scarecrows of all types. Catherine Churchill spoke for all the judges when she said "I thoroughly enjoyed myself - it was wonderful to see how much effort everyone had made".  Tough competition saw excellent scarecrows - even the superb Shrek and Marilyn missed out on prizes.  Fortunately the odd damaged scarecrow didn't stop the judges - they had seen the damaged ones before the vandalism happened!  The scarecrow police are still searching for the kidnapped scarecrow from the bottom of Goodley Stock Road.  The creativity was amazing, with cats being rescued from poles, best not to mention what was happening on the other pole, Mohican Indians, Westerham man, the invisible man, Ghost Busters, Darth Vader, James Bond and killer barbers all playing their part.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />The winning entry was the Churchill School ensemble that is still on display in Chelsea House.  The regulars of the General Wolfe came a close second with their shipwreck on, or rather in, the Long Pond.  The residents of Wells Place came a very creditable third, with the sounds of the sea bringing alive their Pirate of the Caribbean.  The Smith family's "Mr Smith" in the bus stop that has confused so many bus drivers and ambulance men in the past week was very highly commended by the judges.  Scoring was out of 150; over 20 entries scored 130 or more - a huge effort from everyone and great fun for all.  Many rose to the challenge of walking the "Big Trail", but only four people guessed correctly all 16 film titles, the Boyles "Dracula" fooling many people into thinking of "Twilight".&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />The re-enactors of New France Old England brought the crowds to Squerryes Court again.  Over the two days more than 1000 people saw their show.  Afterwards Paul Margott, their events officer, was buzzing with enthusiasm. "I've never known so many people to come into the camp after a battle and ask questions", he said.  "Visitors here seem so much more interested than in some of the other places we go".  In anticipation many of the re-enactors had bought extra 18 Century camp equipment with them and their extra effort was repaid with the interest of the people of Westerham.&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />The list of people to thank for organising the event is long and apologies to anyone who isn't mentioned here, but special mention must be made to: the Warde family for allowing us to use Wolfe Park, the National Trust for sponsoring the event, Charts Edge garden for agreeing free admission for the trail, Westerham Town Council for sponsoring us and letting us take over large parts of the town, James Turner and Hidden Britain for the marvellous publicity; the teams who arranged the fair on the Green and the Barn dance, Richard for his excellent commentary at the fair, the judging panel and Lord Astor for presenting the prizes, but most of all the people of Westerham for taking part so enthusiastically - THANK YOU!&lt;br />&lt;br /> &lt;br />&lt;br />Was the event a success? Well, we've raised over £2,100 for St Mary's Heritage Trust, but perhaps it's best left to the people of Westerham to decide.  If the smiles and community spirit at the fair on Sunday aren't answer enough perhaps the demands that we do a similar event next year give us a clue."&lt;br />&lt;br />  &lt;br />
Andy McCormick/visitwesterham.org.uk</content>
</page></content></entry>