<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-17/GB-536000-171000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-53-17 GB-536000-171000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-17/GB-536000-171000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-17/GB-536000-171000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-536000-171000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412039</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-02T18:10:11.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T18:19:16.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-536000-171000</dblock_id>
<original_item>14</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Forster Park</title>
<content>Forster Park is one of the greenest, most woody parks in the area.  It has two big grassy spaces. The main field is in the centre of the park surrounded by tarmac paths, there are football goalposts set up here and people often use the space for this sport, especially at the weekend.  This field is surrounded on three sides by woody strips with little paths running through them, in the summer when the trees are in full bloom they completely overshadow the paths so they become like little green corridors.  The other grassy space is on the eastern side of the park, the ground is much less flat there and the grass tends to be much longer, most of the time dog walkers are the only people you'll find here but in the summer people also use the space for sunbathing and for picnics.  Along the western side of the park there is a mountain biking track made from wooden planks and piles of earth.  It was rebuilt in the early 2000s, but many of the humps are looking are bit worn now.&lt;br />&lt;br />The old play area on the northern edge of Forster Park was demolished around the turn of the millennium, the area is still full of piles of earth where the old climbing frames were dug up and is now completely overgrown.  New children's play areas have been built adjacent to the main field filled with all sorts of colourful frames, all with moving parts, which do seem popular with the local children.  The old concrete paddling pool is just next to the old play area, it hasn't been used since the late 1990s and is increasingly overgrown, it certainly wouldn't hold water now.  There's a nursery on the other side of the paddling pool from the old play area which consists of a small prefabricated hut and with a fenced patio, this is still in use.  The old play area site, the paddling pool and the nursery are all hidden from view of the main park by a screen of trees.
&lt;br />
Contribution by: David Stell
</content>
</page></content></entry>