<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-45.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-17 GB-540000-174000-45</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-45.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-17/GB-540000-174000-45.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-540000-174000-45</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>420825</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-08-15T16:11:48.000Z</updated><published>2011-08-15T12:37:49.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-540000-174000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>45Day in the life and internet</title>
<content>

A day in the life&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />This Saturday I went to Oxford Street with my Nan. We got there by train but it was pouring with rain as it was all day. The shopping was for my birthday (I chose my own birthday presents). I'm very excited about my birthday. We went to Debenhams and bought 2 SPARKLY tops. Then in Debenhams we went to a place called Dee's diner. We had lunch there I had mayo and lettuce burger with fries, and then I had a Knikerbokerglory (I didn't eat all of it).&lt;br />&lt;br />Then we got on a bus to Harrods, I got a fluffy doggy called westie, I also got hamster for Matthew and a sticker thingy. IT WAS VERY BUSY!&lt;br />&lt;br />When we got out it stopped raining but it was very wet. In Harrods there was a £1,900 6 foot teddy bear for sale (I didn't buy it).it was still wet outside but when we got on bus it started pouring again. But the bus wouldn't move because there was a concert In Trafalgar square, so the roads were closed. It was a long day. We got home at 7pm and my feet were killing me!! &lt;br />&lt;br />By Amy hendrie&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />&lt;br />***************************************************&lt;br />&lt;br />The internet&lt;br />&lt;br />The internet it very useful. It shows images and answers. You can play games, for example Moshi monsters. You can make friends and you can talk to people by sending messages. You can also send gifts to people and get moshlings (pets).  The monsters currency is called rox. YouTube is a website where you can share your videos and pictures. You have to have a YouTube account to share videos and photos though. Facebook is a more adult version of Moshi monsters. But you don't get pets and you are not a monster. You have to be 13 or over to have it. Twitter and msn is the same sort of thing. You can play on games and you don't have to create an account you can just play them. You can watch parts of films for free. You can go on bank websites and check how much money you have in the bank. You can download music of websites. You can listen to music and videos and comment on them. There are different internet sites such as: talk talk msn Bing and the most commonly used Google. EBay is a website where you can sell things and buy things but you need an account to do it. It is cheaper than usual but most of it is second hand. You can buy different things.&lt;br />&lt;br />The internet by Robyn &lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
Pupils of Montbelle</content>
</page></content></entry>