<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-22.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-53-34 GB-532000-342000-22</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-22.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-53-34/GB-532000-342000-22.xml/3" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-532000-342000-22</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412209</as:updateIndex><as:revision>2</as:revision><updated>2011-07-06T12:01:49.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T11:47:02.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-532000-342000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>22Norprint now part of Magnadata Group</title>
<content>

Part of the Magnadata Group, Norprint are one of Europe’s largest labelling and systems companies. The company produces over 7 billion labels per year and can supply a wide range of Print &amp; Apply, Applicators and other bespoke equipment solutions. Norprint focus on a variety of market sectors which include: food, retail, security, commercial and industrial. Supplying leading multi national companies with highly recognised brands.&lt;br />&lt;br />Norprint are one of the few label companies with onsite origination, plate making, laminating &amp; bureau service is constantly on hand to manage change quickly when your clients needs alter, for example, when there is a sudden uplift in sales or new lines are introduced. &lt;br />&lt;br />Our operation is the largest single site unit in the UK, with over 30 presses on site and 24 hour production availability, we can produce to any capacity. We set out to offer organisations the highest standards, s upported by an ethos of technical expertise, continual improvement and a versatility that ensures the best fit to your labelling needs.&lt;br />&lt;br />We were also the first printer in the UK to be awarded the BS5750 for print quality, and now hold the ISO9001 Standard.&lt;br />&lt;br />Who are we?&lt;br />&lt;br />Norprint is one of the largest labelling solutions providers in Europe. We have revenues of £20m and employ more than 200 exceptional people across the UK.&lt;br />&lt;br />Because we have such a large team, we have the breadth of capability to support almost all of your labelling needs.&lt;br />&lt;br />Size isn’t everything!  It’s our people that make us different. We have the depth of technical and business expertise required to deliver and run complex labelling systems. This is why world leading vendors such as ARCA, Toshiba Tec, SATOMicrosoft, Cisco, HP, Oracle and EMC have awarded us their highest accolades and accreditations and trust us as their early adopter partner of choice.&lt;br />&lt;br />(Taken from Norprint website)&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>