<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-51-21/GB-516000-216000-25.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-51-21 GB-516000-216000-25</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-51-21/GB-516000-216000-25.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-51-21/GB-516000-216000-25.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-516000-216000-25</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448061</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T11:27:13.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-516000-216000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>25Kimpton school</title>
<content>

Kimpton School is a Local Authority Primary School. It now has 175 children: a Nursery class of 12 and Reception class form the Foundation Stage; Years 1 and 2 Key Stage1 and Years 3-6 Key Stage 2. Improvements have been made to the building, including a new entrance incorporating a stained glass panel made by children, depicting life in the village. The Victorian Infants' School is still used as a classroom. An eco-garden has been created on the smaller playing field and together with an outdoor classroom offers outdoor learning space: a key element in the bespoke creative curriculum alongside community and the arts as part of the National Curriculum.&lt;br />&lt;br />This year Linden Lodge, a Community Preschool for very young children, has been opened on the site in purpose built accommodation.&lt;br />&lt;br />The activities in school are modified over time but largely remain unchanged. The yearly calendar is observed in traditional ways eg Harvest and Christmas; indoor and outdoor sporting activities are shared with a wide variety on offer. The success in competitive events against other schools is rewarding. During the year Day Outings to a variety of venues are taken to enrich the curriculum. In the summer children take part in the District Sports, Y4 children have swimming lessons and the school holds an Activities Day. Once every two years Y5 and Y6 children go on a week long residential trip to Dorset.&lt;br />&lt;br />The school is a member of the Harpenden District Schools Partnership and Links with a school in India are being planned, through which the children are able to learn about the lives of children from a different culture.&lt;br />&lt;br />   &lt;br />
S.L.Ryder</content>
</page></content></entry>