<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-54-25 GB-544000-258000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-54-25/GB-544000-258000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-544000-258000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436157</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T15:23:06.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T15:23:06.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-544000-258000</dblock_id>
<original_item>10</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21The History of the Bath House</title>
<content>The building was originally a bath house, built in 1927 for the people in the area, which was one of the poorest areas in Cambridge. It was used by most of the people in the local community. In 1978 the St Matthews Neighbourhood Association was founded and sent out  regular newsletters (financed by monthly waste collection), in which the first ideas about community ownership of the Bath House gained momentum. In September 1978 ‘The Bath House’ acquired the premises and agreed to improve the building while negotiations began to obtain a grant from the council. In 1980 Cambridge City Council gave £12,000 towards the conversion of the building for use by different. In 1996 the organisation changed to the Bath House Association and in 1998 gained charity status. From 1998 to 2007 Gingerbread and Community Press were based at The Bath House, followed by Cambridge Dark Room and Action Centre, and for many years a toddlers group. Externally the building has changed little, but inside the space has been reorganised a few times in the recent years. The original boiler room became a dark room and after that the kitchen. The Bath House has been mentioned occasionally in the biographies of famous people who attended Cambridge University and also in fair amount of local  literature. Since 2007 the building has been in  regular use by the two current charities, both very well known in the city:- Cambridge Federation of Tenants, Leaseholders and Residents uses a  suite of offices  and Lifecraft occupies the majority of the building and offers user-led self-help for adults with mental health issues and wellbeing needs. &lt;br />
Contribution by: Lifecraft</content>
</page></content></entry>