<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-60-12/GB-604000-129000-4.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-60-12 GB-604000-129000-4</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-60-12/GB-604000-129000-4.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-60-12/GB-604000-129000-4.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-604000-129000-4</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436161</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-09T15:23:08.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-09T15:23:08.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-604000-129000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>04Some quarter of a centuary later this is an update to my original entry made in 1985</title>
<content>

When I made the original entry in 1985 I was new to the area and toured in my Cortina using CB Radio to talk to varoius residents. 26 years later technology has change greatly, there are now several cell phone masts where there were none in 1985 and CB Radio has all but disappeared. &lt;br />&lt;br />Apart from that the landscape has altered very little although small "Starter Home" estates have been built on released farm land in Newchurch and a new village hall was buit in 1987 with a grant from the Channel Tunnel that was also under construction at the time. The other main employer in New Church, the Agi-Chemical company Chafers closed down its operation inthe early 1990s and the site remained empty for over a decade until a company supplying equestrian goods purchased it in the new milleniumn and it now employs several people. &lt;br />&lt;br />Mixed arable and sheep farming is still the main economic output but dairy herds suffered greatl y after BSE in the 90s, the main herd of Freisians in the village dissapeard in the 1990s and their barn was converted into a luxury house. There are more tourist attractions run by farmers supplementing farming incomes, a popular one beeing the "Maize Maze" that can clearly been seen from the satelite shot on Google Earth in St.Mary's road (The road out of Dymchurch from the coast). Dungeness A nuclear power station closed in 1997 but a host of rural businesses able to operate in the countryside because of broadband access to the internet have migrated from town in to small converted agricultural units and include a company supplying paper products and an art gallery. Soft fruit growing in the area, strawberries in particular, has also increasd in poly tunnel cultivation, the plants are bought in from Holland, often through the Channel Tunnel. . &lt;br />&lt;br />There is a new sea wall constructed by the Environment Agency and incoperating a 100 year time cap sul,  finished in 2011 protecting the area from flood. There are more trees owing to the policy of Parish Councils and a tree planting programme, I am elected to Dymchurch Parish Council and we activly participate, planting over 5000 tress in the last few years. &lt;br />&lt;br />For me personally where I was once a retained Fire Man at Dymchurch Fire Station I am now station commander of the part time station of Dymchurch Fire &amp; Rescue Service and yes, there is still plenty of open water in the drainage dykes for us to use. The saw mill/timber yard in New Church burnt down in 1987, also the year of the hurricane that saw considerable damage to the Marsh Churches. The fire service continues to turn out about 100 times a year but also now operates a "First response" medical service that assists the South East Costal Ambulance Service over 300 times each year, very busy and much needed. Most of the Light &lt;br />&lt;br />Railway level crossings on the Romney H ythe &amp; Dymchurch Light Railway now have automatic barriers, except for the East bridge road, a response to 2 deaths at crossings in the late 90s, early 2000s, 1 at Dungeness and 1 on the Burmarsh road to Newchurch.   &lt;br />
Contribution by: Ian Meyers</content>
</page></content></entry>