<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-64-25/GB-640000-258000-4.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-64-25 GB-640000-258000-4</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-64-25/GB-640000-258000-4.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-64-25/GB-640000-258000-4.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-640000-258000-4</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448073</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T17:14:36.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-28T15:49:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-640000-258000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>04Doomsday update from 1986 to 2011</title>
<content>

The village lies approximately four miles inland of Aldeburgh, just off of the A1094 with Leiston and Saxmundham being a further four miles to the North-East and North-West respectively.&lt;br />&lt;br />The landscape is rural including cultivated farmland, common and woodland.&lt;br />&lt;br />The local Blackheath Estate still owns much of this farmland, some of which is tenanted. &lt;br />&lt;br />The village is relatively unique in that most of the village and much of the surrounding area was still under the ownership of the Blackheath Estate until the early part of the last century when some land and all dwellings started to be sold off. Indeed, there is a document in existence recording the purchase of the freehold of one cottage in 1909 for 12/6d (about 62.5p in new money!).&lt;br />&lt;br />Along with many villages, over the passage of time has been the loss of the shop, Post Office (although there is currently a visiting mobile Post Office in the Village Hall every Friday), School, the recent closure of the Public House and generally less local employment.&lt;br />&lt;br />Due, no doubt, to the close proximity to the very popular town of Aldeburgh, the percentage of non residential homes; either second homes or holiday lets is quite high and houses and house building land is at a premium.&lt;br />&lt;br />Within the village, there is a 11th/12th century church; St Mary the Virgin and a Baptist Chapel, a post windmill built 1811/12 (under restoration) - reputedly the tallest of its kind in Europe, a shelter/seat commemorating  King George V Jubilee; a hand carved wooden village sign commemorating Queen Elizabeth II Silver Jubilee. &lt;br />&lt;br />A decreasing number of long standing village families still live in Friston but houses are often bought up by people retiring from towns. Less and less Villagers work on the land, most now working in local businesses in the nearby towns. &#xd;
   &lt;br />
Bryan Duncan</content>
</page></content></entry>