<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-63-16/GB-636000-162000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-63-16 GB-636000-162000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-63-16/GB-636000-162000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-63-16/GB-636000-162000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-636000-162000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>436661</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-15T14:51:26.000Z</updated><published>2011-09-15T14:51:26.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-636000-162000</dblock_id>
<original_item>13</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21More closures since 1985</title>
<content>

The Motor Museum and Model Village have both closed.&lt;br />&lt;br />The swimming pool which was new in 1985 will soon be closed and a new one built near the new leisure centre. This leisure centre houses a gym and sports hall and was built on the site of the old Thanet College buildings on the High Street. It is run by Thanet Leisure Force.&lt;br />&lt;br />The monkey sanctuary became a art gallery run by IOTA (Isle Of Thanet Arts) for ten years until 2008. It then lay empty for a while but another organisation has recently taken it over to run as a gallery again. &lt;br />&lt;br />The harbour area now has several bars which have pavement seating areas. Pleasurama (the amusement arcade) was destroyed by fire in 1998. The site is still awaiting redevelopment. There are no discos or clubs as in the 1980s. Last year the Customs House was re-opened after refurbishment by the Ramsgate Town Council (which was set up in 2009). There is an information point, a shop and a small cafe which has a pavement seating area. &lt;br />&lt;br />On the East Cliff is a bandstand and the Granville Theatre which provides live entertainment all year round and is the town's only cinema.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>