<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-65-29/GB-652000-297000-23.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-65-29 GB-652000-297000-23</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-65-29/GB-652000-297000-23.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-65-29/GB-652000-297000-23.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-652000-297000-23</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>412383</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-06-09T20:51:24.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-09T20:51:24.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-652000-297000</dblock_id>
<original_item>11</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>23Corton School</title>
<content>

From the school logbook and punishment book. It showed the first headteacher of Corton School to be a male. He was employed by the governors and lived in the school house. Life was not easy for teachers in those days as most of the children in the village were required to work in the fields or at sea at busy times of the year and were reluctant to go to school not least because their parents required them to work. The headteacher had to keep discipline by regular use of the cane. Indeed what was described as "indiscriminate beatings" resulted inn the eventula dismissing of the this head by the Governors. There were records in the punishment book for beatings of both boys and girls for misdemeanors of "answering back" -  "insolence" - "setting fire to the school stock cupboard".&lt;br />&lt;br />The eventual dismissal was brought about by the fathers of 3 girls who were beaten for "insolence" The men worked at a "rocket station" based on Corton Cliffs that fired a mortar with a light line toward ships that were driven aground on Scroby Sands. They complained to the Governors of the school that the girls should never have been beaten so severely and the headteacher was dismissed.
&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>