<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-24-20/GB-248000-201000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-24-20 GB-248000-201000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-24-20/GB-248000-201000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-24-20/GB-248000-201000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-248000-201000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>448959</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-11-01T21:29:10.000Z</updated><published>2011-11-01T21:29:10.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-248000-201000</dblock_id>
<original_item>2</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Local History of Stradey Estate</title>
<content>

The owner of Stradey Castle is Sir David Mansel Lewis,The Lord Lieutenant of Dyfed. Although, since his death, the running of the estate has been handed down to his son, Patrick Charles Archibald Mansel Lewis. &lt;br />&lt;br />Sir David was born into the estate, and spent his life living there. &lt;br />&lt;br />The castle was built between 1850 and 1874. An older castle stood before this though, but was taken down and positioned higher up.   &lt;br />&lt;br /> In 1873 a 4 meter by 3 meter painting depicting Diogenes and Alexander the Great was painted by William De Riviere who taught Charles William Mansel Lewis, the present owner's grandfather. Riviere and the architect Buckner, who designed the magnificent staircase, worked together during 1873 and 1874 on these two complementing masterpieces found in the main hall. There are about 24 room's in the castle, 12 luxuriously decorated bedrooms, and 12 other rooms, such as the Dining Hall and Library. The estate is about 1,500 acres. This includes about 300 acres of woodland, which was planted by Charles William Mansel Lewis for privacy. &lt;br />&lt;br />Usually, visitors can have a look around the garden of the estate, and its woodland, once they have seeked permission from the owner himself, or the groundsman.   &lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>