<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-34/GB-332000-348000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-33-34 GB-332000-348000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-34/GB-332000-348000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-33-34/GB-332000-348000-21.xml/1" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-332000-348000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>447441</as:updateIndex><as:revision>0</as:revision><updated>2011-10-26T14:41:28.000Z</updated><published>2011-10-26T14:41:28.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-332000-348000</dblock_id>
<original_item>1</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Wrexam, for better or worse</title>
<content>

Modernism came to Wrexham, and out went all the markets to be replaced by supermarkets and out of town shopping centres. And so died Wrexham, now a town of pound shops and junk shops that I suppose reflects the aspirations of a poor town, badly managed and run. The once new Industrial estate that many people worked hard to introduce in the wake of the loss of the coal and steel, and textile industries that were once the mainstay of the town is now in decline 40% empty. and ironically thet are now building a new road to it, 50 years too late.&lt;br />&lt;br />The breweries have long gone and Wrexhams only claim to fame "Wrexham Larger" a thing of the past along with the larger houses. The football club a shadow of past european glories, along with the rugby club, now a empty facility that once housed a thriving community of hockey, cricket and squash clubs and the colourful characters there. Thankfully the aerospace factory in nearby Broughton just outside Chester is thriving and the Chester businees park provides jobs as it is a mere 3 miles away or Wrexham would be one of the poorest towns in the UK.   &lt;br />
Stephen</content>
</page></content></entry>