<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:as="http://atomserver.org/namespaces/1.0/"><id>/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-17/GB-316000-174000-21.xml</id><title type="text"> Entry: pages-GB-31-17 GB-316000-174000-21</title><author><name>AtomServer APP Service</name></author><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-17/GB-316000-174000-21.xml" rel="self" /><link href="/electron/atom/v1/domesday/pages-GB-31-17/GB-316000-174000-21.xml/2" rel="edit" /><as:entryId>GB-316000-174000-21</as:entryId><as:updateIndex>411935</as:updateIndex><as:revision>1</as:revision><updated>2011-09-08T16:13:22.000Z</updated><published>2011-06-06T15:05:27.000Z</published><content type="application/xml"><page xmlns="">
<dblock_id>GB-316000-174000</dblock_id>
<original_item>8</original_item>
<year>2011</year>
<title>21Shree Swaminarayan Temple in Grangetown</title>
<content>People from Kutch first arrived in Cardiff around 1964 and found jobs in factories and iron foundries. More people came from Uganda and the Kutchi population greatly increased within few years. In order to maintain their religion and culture they used to gather in people's houses or hired church halls to celebrate religious festivals and other events. &lt;br />&lt;br />In 1978, during his tour of UK H.H. Acharya Shree Tejendra Prasadji Maharaj came to Cardiff and was impressed with the gathering of the Community of Satsangis. He suggested that, as there are many Satsangis, a temple should be established in Cardiff and he gave his blessings that this should happen in a short time. &lt;br />&lt;br />With the permission of Mahant Swami of Bhuj, it was decided that the Temple would be known as Shree Swaminarayan Temple, Cardiff. (Under Shree Narnarayan Dev Temple, Bhuj Kutch). &lt;br />&lt;br />On the first Patotsav celebration in 1983, H.H. Acharya Shree Tejendraprasadji Maharaj and Santos from Ahemdavad visited Cardiff and did the Patotsav Aarti. &#xd;
Another ten years quickly went by when in 2003 H.H. Acharya Shree Tejendraprashadji Maharaj came to Cardiff to invite satsangis to his 60th birthday celebrations in Ahmedabad. He learnt that we were planning to celebrate our 25th Silver Jubilee in 2007 and he expressed his wish that as part of our Silver Jubilee celebrations a murti of Baal Swaroop Ghanshayam Maharaj should be installed in the temple. &#xd;
The temple Committee took up this challenge and asked the Mahant Swami of Bhuj, the late Purani Hariswarupdasji to give his permission. Once he agreed everyone in Cardiff was very excited and was looking forward to the day when Ghanshyam Maharaj would arrive in Cardiff. Three beautifully shaped shikhars, one on each sinhashan, were built on the roof. Smaller domes were also placed on the roof parapet to give the building a palatial appearance. &#xd;
The murti of Bal Swaroop Ghanshyam Maharaj together with new sinhashans came from India and the Pratishtha Celebrations were arranged from 17th September 2007 to 23rd September 2007. H.H. Acharya Shree Koshalendra Prasadji Maharaj, The former Acharya Shree Tejendra Prasadji Maharaj, Mahant Swami of Bhuj Purani Swami Dharmanandan Dasji and other santos arrived to grace this wonderful occasion. A seven day Shikshapatri Bhashya Parayan was organised with the actual Pratistha and Abhishek day on 21st September 2007. A Grand procession through the main city centre was arranged on Saturday 22nd September 2007. Nearly five to six thousand people took part in the procession. This event was like none other and it was well organised, well supported, well disciplined and a very colourful event. &#xd;
In the new temple the Mangla Aarti has been regularly taking place at 07.30 in the morning and the evening Aarti at 06.00 pm. All the festival are celebrated and well attended by all the Satsangis. The arrival of the beautiful marble Murti of Bal Swaroop Ghanshyam Maharaj is the best thing that has ever happened for all the Cardiff Satsangis. &#xd;







&lt;br />
</content>
</page></content></entry>